<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Stephanie Soo Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/107909478287541</link><description>Stephanie Soo Page</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:15:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">25012923361657845us</guid><title>What's Going On With the Charges Brought Up Against Luigi Mangione?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/25012923361657845/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Luigi Mangione is charged in the December 4, 2024 slaying of Brian Thompson, CEO of UnitedHealthcare. His state indictment includes murder and weapons offenses. A judge dismissed the state terrorism-related charges in September 2025 but upheld second-degree murder counts. Separately, a federal indictment from April 2025 adds stalking and firearm charges and makes him eligible for the death penalty.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/25012923361657845.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/25012923361657845.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="525"><media:title>What's Going On With the Charges Brought Up Against Luigi Mangione?</media:title><media:description>Luigi Mangione is charged in the December 4, 2024 slaying of Brian Thompson, CEO of UnitedHealthcare. His state indictment includes murder and weapons offenses. A judge dismissed the state terrorism-related charges in September 2025 but upheld second-degree murder counts. Separately, a federal indictment from April 2025 adds stalking and firearm charges and makes him eligible for the death penalty.</media:description><media:credit>Stephanie Soo Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1940193640171505us</guid><title>Japanese Dad-Daughter Duo's unspeakable murder in LOVE MOTEL</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1940193640171505/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A Dad-Daughter Duo's Unspeakable Acts!</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1940193640171505.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">688002983924057us</guid><title>IShowSpeed Conquered China and Met Jackie Chan!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/688002983924057/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Popular streamer IShowSpeed recently took his content global, visiting China and connecting with fans in a whole new way. During his trip, he had an unforgettable moment meeting legendary actor Jackie Chan.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/688002983924057.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">677824318354391us</guid><title>She Lived a Secret Double Life Online | The Shocking Case of a Masked Streamer and Her Deadly Plan</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/677824318354391/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Secret Identity Unveiled in a Stunning Tale of Revenge</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/677824318354391.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1337709971317804us</guid><title>Baby Emmanuel Haro’s Father Had a Troubling History Before His Son’s Disappearance</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1337709971317804/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The disappearance of baby Emmanuel Haro is one of those cases that leaves more questions than answers. Before Emmanuel went missing, there were already serious concerns about his father’s behavior and past actions. In this video, we take a careful look at the events leading up to Emmanuel’s disappearance, the red flags that were missed, and the heartbreaking search for truth and justice in his case.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1337709971317804.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">838501958832061us</guid><title>No Doctor Has Ever Survived Treating This Mental Asylum Patient. Murder Or Contagious Madness? (BAM)</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/838501958832061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A psychiatrist at a state hospital confronts a notorious patient tied to years of doctor breakdowns. Inspired by “The Patient” Reddit story</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/838501958832061.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">801479576200976us</guid><title>Pregnant Wife Pushed Off 110ft Cliff While Visiting National Park With Loving Husband</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/801479576200976/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>While hiking in a Thai National Park, a pregnant woman fell over 100 feet. Her husband’s story quickly unraveled, revealing a chilling plan behind what first seemed like a tragic accident.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/801479576200976.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1116610600685515us</guid><title>Online Theories Are Swirling About Two Celestes in d4vd’s Life</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1116610600685515/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The discovery of 15-year-old Celeste Rivas Hernandez’s remains in a car registered to singer d4vd has sparked a wave of speculation. One theory involves another young woman named Celeste who posted with the artist years earlier. While authorities have made no charges, fans continue to connect songs, tattoos, and social posts in an attempt to piece together what really happened.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1116610600685515.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1153240899572203us</guid><title>What Happened to Baby Emmanuel Haro?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1153240899572203/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>After Baby Emmanuel Haro was reported missing, investigators began questioning his parents’ story. Their interviews soon revealed inconsistencies that led police to uncover a tragic truth.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1153240899572203.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">780030948356006us</guid><title>When a College Lie Turned Into Tragedy</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/780030948356006/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Sydney, once a model student, was hiding a life-altering secret—she’d been suspended from college. When her mother learned the truth, their confrontation led to a devastating tragedy.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/780030948356006.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1526915525002270us</guid><title>The Strange Parallels Between d4vd’s Music and Celeste’s Disappearance</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1526915525002270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>D4vd’s music explores isolation, heartbreak, and tragedy with cinematic storytelling. Fans have drawn comparisons to mystery and true-crime themes found in classic literature and film.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1526915525002270.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1372093201081900us</guid><title>He Avenged His Mother’s Death 22 Years Later</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1372093201081900/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In China, Zhang Koukou killed three men he said were responsible for his mother’s death 22 years earlier. His actions sparked national debate over justice, morality, and revenge.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1372093201081900.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1173065428077067us</guid><title>The Full Story Behind “Unknown Number”</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1173065428077067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Kendra Licari, a Michigan teacher, was accused of cyberstalking her daughter in a case featured in Unknown Number. Police files reveal disturbing new details Netflix left out of the documentary.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1173065428077067.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">750411944699860us</guid><title>Were d4vd's Posts Showing Signs that Pointed to What Happened to Celeste?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/750411944699860/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The discovery of Celeste Rivas Hernandez’s remains inside a vehicle registered to D4vd has triggered intense investigation. Among the material cited: a previously unreleased track referencing the name “Celeste,” a shared tattoo symbol, and social-media posts that were later removed. Authorities are still determining how she died and what, if any, role the artist may have played.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/750411944699860.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2652578955082876us</guid><title>Foreign Stars Took Over China's Singing Competition</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2652578955082876/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A major Chinese singing competition has gone viral after international contestants dominated the stage, outshining local performers and sparking debate about global talent influence in the country’s entertainment industry.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/thumb_2652578955082876.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1859749441603539us</guid><title>Why Would a Mother Catfish and Cyberbully Her Own Daughter?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1859749441603539/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In Michigan, Kendra Licari sent harassing anonymous messages to her teenage daughter Lauryn and the girl’s boyfriend over many months. She used fake identities, masked her location, and later confessed to the crimes. In 2023, she pleaded guilty to stalking a minor and was sentenced to prison.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1859749441603539.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1112882464163528us</guid><title>Who Is d4vd and How Is He Connected to Celeste Rivas?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1112882464163528/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>d4vd (David Anthony Burke), a rising singer known for hits like Romantic Homicide, is now at the center of a disturbing investigation. The remains of 15-year-old Celeste Rivas were found in a Tesla registered to him in Los Angeles. She’d been missing since April 2024. Authorities have executed search warrants on homes linked to d4vd, seized evidence, and are probing whether there was a connection between him and the teenager, including matching tattoos and rumored prior contact, though no charges have been filed.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1112882464163528.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1796824997871605us</guid><title>She Found Out Husband Was Cheating, Within 48 Hours His Mistress Was Gone! #AntonettaStevens #DeadlyAffair #TrueCrime</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1796824997871605/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What began as a heated love triangle in Georgia took a devastating turn when 30-year-old Ashley Bocanegra was found dead. Investigators say jealousy and betrayal spiraled into violence, leaving a community stunned. As the case unfolded, shocking messages and hidden motives came to light</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1796824997871605.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1365888301913865us</guid><title>AI Chat Bots Told Her That Her Psychiatrist Was in Love With Her</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1365888301913865/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Arizona ADHD coach Kendra Hilty confessed her feelings for her psychiatrist, what followed blurred the line between therapy, technology, and delusion. She claims AI chatbots like ChatGPT and Claude convinced her the love was mutual, sparking viral debates about “AI psychosis” and professional boundaries.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/1365888301913865.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2923814011143750us</guid><title>This Show Might Be Crazier Than Any Reality Show In America</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2923814011143750/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A new Chinese reality series pushes actors to their limits inside a massive indoor “city” where every scene is improvised and judged in real time.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/107909478287541/thumb_2923814011143750.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>