<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Emma Kenny Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/341711569190033</link><description>Emma Kenny Page</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:16:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">716605454531221ie</guid><title>When Jealousy Leads to Obsession | Caroline Reed Robertson</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/716605454531221/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Emma Kenny delves into one of Melbourne's most haunting cases - the tragic murder of young Rachel Barber at the hands of her former babysitter, Caroline Reed Robertson. Venture into the heart of a crime driven by envy, obsession, and misplaced desires. Through Emma's insightful lens, explore the intricate dynamics of a relationship gone terribly wrong and the tragic consequences that followed. Join us as we seek understanding in a story that left an entire community reeling.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/716605454531221.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/716605454531221.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="1114"><media:title>When Jealousy Leads to Obsession | Caroline Reed Robertson</media:title><media:description>Emma Kenny delves into one of Melbourne's most haunting cases - the tragic murder of young Rachel Barber at the hands of her former babysitter, Caroline Reed Robertson. Venture into the heart of a crime driven by envy, obsession, and misplaced desires. Through Emma's insightful lens, explore the intricate dynamics of a relationship gone terribly wrong and the tragic consequences that followed. Join us as we seek understanding in a story that left an entire community reeling.</media:description><media:credit>Emma Kenny Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">842810885327885ie</guid><title>The Tragic End of Annie Kasprzak and the Disturbing Acts of her boyfriend Chris Bagshaw</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/842810885327885/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Immerse yourself in a journey through the shadows with Emma Kenny as she meticulously investigates the heart-wrenching case of Annie Kasprzak, a young life senselessly extinguished. Emma navigates through the chilling details, unraveling Chris Bagshaw’s disturbing acts that led to this unthinkable tragedy. Through in-depth analysis, exclusive insights, and a compassionate narrative, Emma sheds light on the enduring impact on Annie’s community and the relentless pursuit of justice. This episode is a somber reflection on loss, the search for answers, and the hope that truth will prevail.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/842810885327885.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1616963729502245ie</guid><title>Maternal Madness: The Atrocities of Theresa Knorr Unveiled</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1616963729502245/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this chilling episode, psychologist Emma Kenny dissects the terrifying and abhorrent case of Theresa Knorr, a mother who became an embodiment of evil and committed unspeakable acts of violence against her own children.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1616963729502245.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2948514388682634ie</guid><title>When a Mother and Brother Does the Unthinkable</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2948514388682634/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This is the tragic tale of a 15-year-old teen, Timothy Ferguson, who got brutally tortured by his own family. It's heartbreaking and the details of the case is absolutely nauseating... What are your thoughts?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/2948514388682634.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1381386210446252ie</guid><title>Teen's Chilling Reaction After Taking Her FRIEND's Life!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1381386210446252/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Teen's Chilling Reaction After Taking Her FRIEND's Life!</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1381386210446252.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">848660191353487ie</guid><title>She Was Asleep As the Nightmare Unfolded</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/848660191353487/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>As a mum, I cannot imagine Sarah's personal hell when she woke up only to find her boys horrifically murdered as she slept... What do you guys think about this heartbreaking case?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/848660191353487.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1415598933394967ie</guid><title>Took Her Boyfriend's Life on Christmas Day</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1415598933394967/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On Christmas morning in 2024, a quiet village in Staffordshire, England, woke to tragedy. What began as a day of celebration ended in bloodshed — the culmination of a toxic relationship, unchecked jealousy, and a system that saw danger coming but couldn’t stop it. What are your thoughts on this case?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1415598933394967.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1209910277134752ie</guid><title>The Police Were Mortified When She Opened the Trunk!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1209910277134752/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The body cam, to this day, gives me the chills. Knowing that the last moments of those pure, beautiful children were a living hell infuriates me and breaks my heart... Have you guys heard of this case before? What are your thoughts?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1209910277134752.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1928325404560179ie</guid><title>This Teacher Thought She’d Never Get Caught</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1928325404560179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This is one of those cases that really gets under your skin, because it shows how someone who should protect young people can instead become a predator.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1928325404560179.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">730542660102089ie</guid><title>He Said She Drowned, But The Truth Was Far Worse</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/730542660102089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When emergency responders arrived at the scene, they knew that this wasn't a tragic accident. Koralynn was only 2. The injuries covering her body told a harrowing story... What are your thoughts about this infuriating and heartbreaking case?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_730542660102089.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1316056623623602ie</guid><title>She DROWNED Her Twins in the Tub!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1316056623623602/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>We delve into the chilling case of Samantha Ford, a British mother who tragically drowned her own twins in December 2018. The narrative uncovers the horrific incident that occurred in Margate, Kent, when Ford, struggling with the end of her marriage, killed her twins, Jake and Chloe Ford, by drowning them in the bath. What are your thoughts on this absolutely tragic case? - Em x</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1316056623623602.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">827455403622935ie</guid><title>Christmas Turned Into CARNAGE</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/827455403622935/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On Christmas Day in Milton Keynes, Jazwell Brown killed his partner and a neighbouring woman, and seriously injured others in a violent domestic rampage. The case highlighted how extreme violence can erupt in familiar spaces, often after warning signs go unnoticed. Question: Do you think tragedies like this are truly unpredictable — or are there moments where intervention could have changed everything? 💭</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/827455403622935.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1877869953123167ie</guid><title>Judy Malinowski: First Person To Testify At Her Own Trial</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1877869953123167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2015 in Ohio, Judy Malinowski was doused in gasoline and set on fire by her ex, Michael Slager, outside a gas station. She survived nearly two years, enduring dozens of surgeries, and recorded testimony from her hospital bed. After she died in 2017, that testimony helped secure his conviction and a life sentence. How did she find the strength to fight for justice through unimaginable pain?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1877869953123167.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">840669195354542ie</guid><title>He Had to Audacity to Go On TV After What He Did!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/840669195354542/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Lynsey Wilson met Mitchell Quy she wasn’t aware of how controlling and abusive he was going to be. Join me in my latest True Crime episode where I take a deep dive into a story that will shock you to the core. </description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_840669195354542.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">862880229620210ie</guid><title>Daisy Coleman: Assault Allegations &amp; Community Backlash</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/862880229620210/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This case isn’t just about what happened to Daisy Coleman — it’s about what happened after she spoke out. The backlash, the lack of accountability, and the long-term impact of not being believed all played a devastating role in her life. Do you think the justice system failed Daisy more — or did her community? 💭</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/862880229620210.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">878371751306533ie</guid><title>The Keith Jesperson Case | The One with No Remorse</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/878371751306533/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In the early 1990s, Keith Jesperson murdered at least eight women across the United States, earning the nickname “The Happy Face Killer.” A long-haul truck driver, he used constant travel to avoid detection and later taunted police and media with anonymous letters signed with a smiling face. His crimes went unsolved for years before a confession revealed their scope. He is serving multiple life sentences. How was someone able to kill repeatedly while hiding in plain sight for so long?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_878371751306533.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1507398583824272ie</guid><title>Bodycam Captures What a Mother Should Never Do</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1507398583824272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>These cases infuriate me as a mum. What in the world made her think that it would be OKAY in any scenario?!</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1507398583824272.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1217235220307031ie</guid><title>They Found the Bodybags in Their Own SHED!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1217235220307031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Robert Leo Marzejka suffocated, and beat to death his sister, Danielle and her boyfriend Seren Bryan in August 2018 in their mobile home. It is one of the most chilling stories I've ever covered. I cannot imagine how the family must have felt when they came in face to face with that room filled with flies with two big body bags just laying in there... What are your thoughts? Em x</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1217235220307031.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1158353186513573ie</guid><title>The Bungalow Was Hiding a Twisted Truth</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1158353186513573/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When you look at Juliana Redding's case, what do you think is the most unsettling part — the betrayal by people she knew, the role money and influence played, or the way her potential was stolen so abruptly?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1158353186513573.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1194239519345176ie</guid><title>CCTV Captured How Cold-Bloodedly He Did It All!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1194239519345176/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>He only got... 17 YEARS though??</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1194239519345176.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>