<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Emma Kenny Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/341711569190033</link><description>Emma Kenny Page</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 21:00:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1831565734075505ie</guid><title>He Was Caught on Camera Before Doing the Unthinkable</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1831565734075505/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Evelyn Mae Boswell was a 15-month-old toddler from Tennessee whose disappearance in February 2020 sparked a nationwide search. Her mother, Megan Boswell, gave conflicting stories about Evelyn’s whereabouts before the child was found deceased on family property in March 2020. Investigators determined Evelyn had been hidden in a playpen covered with blankets and aluminum foil inside a shed. Megan Boswell was later convicted of felony murder and sentenced to life in prison in 2023. The case drew widespread media attention and calls for stronger protections for vulnerable children.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1831565734075505.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1831565734075505.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="644"><media:title>He Was Caught on Camera Before Doing the Unthinkable</media:title><media:description>Evelyn Mae Boswell was a 15-month-old toddler from Tennessee whose disappearance in February 2020 sparked a nationwide search. Her mother, Megan Boswell, gave conflicting stories about Evelyn’s whereabouts before the child was found deceased on family property in March 2020. Investigators determined Evelyn had been hidden in a playpen covered with blankets and aluminum foil inside a shed. Megan Boswell was later convicted of felony murder and sentenced to life in prison in 2023. The case drew widespread media attention and calls for stronger protections for vulnerable children.</media:description><media:credit>Emma Kenny Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1791446294790054ie</guid><title>Frat Boy Turns into a Feral CANNIBAL!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1791446294790054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Austin Harrouff, known as the “cannibal killer,” was a 19-year-old Florida State University student who, in 2016, murdered John Stevens and Michelle Mishcon in their garage. He attacked with a machete and was found biting Stevens’s face while growling like an animal. Experts later testified he suffered a severe psychotic episode, convinced he was half-man, half-dog and pursued by demons. In 2022, he was found not guilty by reason of insanity and committed indefinitely to a secure mental health facility instead of prison.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1791446294790054.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1754929572057975ie</guid><title>Evil Stepdad Locked Him in a Dog Cage!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1754929572057975/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 20:01:30 GMT</pubDate><description>Jeremiah Valencia suffered horrific abuse at the hands of his stepfather Thomas Ferguson and others, a heartbreaking case that exposed shocking neglect and cruelty.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1754929572057975.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2103809253524206ie</guid><title>Colleen Ritzer Was Killed by Her 14-Year-Old Student</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/2103809253524206/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>At just 14, Philip Chism committed a shocking crime against teacher Colleen Ritzer, a case that stunned a community and raised urgent questions about youth violence.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/2103809253524206.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1555476095419210ie</guid><title>The Tragic Case of Baby Emily</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1555476095419210/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 20:01:26 GMT</pubDate><description>On October 3rd, 10-month-old Emily lost her life after a day marked by her parents’ drinking. This heartbreaking case highlights the devastating impact of neglect and poor choices.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/msn-thumbnails/341711569190033/1555476095419210.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2102642046898080ie</guid><title>Two Beautiful Boys Became the Victims of Their Mum</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/2102642046898080/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Being a mum to 4 children, I genuinely cannot fathom hurting a single hair on their heads. This case that unfolded in Bullitt county , Kentucky is one of terror and sadness. Tiffanie Lucas shot and killed her little boys. Let me take you through the story so you can make your own mind up at the end on what happened to make this mum murder her beautiful little boys.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/2102642046898080.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1283168793419852ie</guid><title>Taylor Parker’s Deadly Obsession with Pregnancy</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1283168793419852/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:30:32 GMT</pubDate><description>Taylor Parker’s disturbing obsession with pregnancies led to a shocking crime that left a community in disbelief and raised awareness about hidden dangers.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1283168793419852.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2009978946493473ie</guid><title>"Say Goodbye to Your Children!" | The Arthur Freeman Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/2009978946493473/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:01:47 GMT</pubDate><description>Arthur Freeman horrified Australia in 2009 when he stopped on Melbourne’s West Gate Bridge and dropped his 4-year-old daughter, Darcey, to her death in front of morning commuters. The act was later described as revenge against his ex-wife during a custody battle. Freeman was sentenced to life in prison, with a minimum of 32 years.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/2009978946493473.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">779739227836514ie</guid><title>How Can Teens Be THIS Evil? *Scott Habermehl*</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/779739227836514/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:00:17 GMT</pubDate><description>In July 2020, former 'Gigolos' star Ash Armand (real name Akshaya Kubiak) was arrested for the death of 29-year-old Herleen Dulai. After consuming psychedelic mushrooms together, Armand claimed he blacked out and attacked Dulai in self-defense. He pleaded guilty to voluntary manslaughter and mayhem, receiving an 8–20 year sentence. The case was featured in the 2025 docuseries 'Sin City Gigolo'.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/779739227836514.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3853638021594491ie</guid><title>The Tragic Case of Danielle and Seren Bryan</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/3853638021594491/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In August 2018, Robert Leo Marzejka killed his sister Danielle and her boyfriend Seren Bryan, hiding their bodies in a shed. Emma Kenny revisits this chilling and heartbreaking case.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/3853638021594491.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2546643342363760ie</guid><title>"I Was in a Trans!" - The Ash Armand Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/2546643342363760/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In July 2020, former 'Gigolos' star Ash Armand (real name Akshaya Kubiak) was arrested for the death of 29-year-old Herleen Dulai. After consuming psychedelic mushrooms together, Armand claimed he blacked out and attacked Dulai in self-defense. He pleaded guilty to voluntary manslaughter and mayhem, receiving an 8–20 year sentence. The case was featured in the 2025 docuseries 'Sin City Gigolo'.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/2546643342363760.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1200789585407326ie</guid><title>Committing The Ultimate Deed On A 3 Year Old</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1200789585407326/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:02:04 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2018, three-year-old Alfie Lamb died after being crushed in the footwell of a car seat in London. His mother’s boyfriend, Stephen Waterson, had pushed his seat back onto the child during a car ride. Waterson was convicted of manslaughter and jailed, while Alfie’s death sparked outrage and calls for justice.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1200789585407326.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2094214791401163ie</guid><title>Enraged Ex Lost It &amp; Took Her Life *911 Call*</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/2094214791401163/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:02:16 GMT</pubDate><description>In August 2023, Columbus, Ohio resident Chance Donohoe broke into his ex-girlfriend Shannon Hiott’s home and fatally stabbed her over 30 times. He then confessed to police and was sentenced in 2024 to life in prison, becoming eligible for parole only after serving at least 31 years.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/2094214791401163.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">700323889635806ie</guid><title>What Takoda Endured in His Short Life Was CHILLING</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/700323889635806/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In December 2019, 10-year-old Takoda Collins died after enduring years of sustained abuse—locked in filthy spaces, forced into painful ‘punishment poses,’ beaten and drowned. His father, Al-Mutahan McLean, and two others pled guilty and were sentenced in 2021. The case sparked major child protection reforms.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/700323889635806.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1088591046813421ie</guid><title>He Wasn't the Innocent Old Man He Seemed To Be</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1088591046813421/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 20:01:41 GMT</pubDate><description>John Getreu lived a double life for decades — a family man on the surface, but secretly a killer. Linked through DNA evidence, he was convicted of two brutal murders in Northern California dating back to the 1970s. This video explores how investigators finally uncovered Getreu’s crimes after more than 40 years, the chilling details of his past, and the justice delivered for his victims.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1088591046813421.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">653347223776883ie</guid><title>He Asked for Donations After Taking His Baby's Life!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/653347223776883/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 14:00:17 GMT</pubDate><description>Ollie Davis was a four-week-old baby from Leicester who tragically died on 21 October 2017. When found unresponsive in his cot, doctors discovered he had suffered a snapped neck and more than 40 fractures, including broken ribs, arms, legs, and skull injuries. Experts compared the trauma to the aftermath of a high-impact car crash. After a six-year investigation, Ollie’s father, Michael Davis, was convicted in March 2024 of murder and grievous bodily harm. He was sentenced to life in prison with a minimum of 22 years. His mother, Kayleigh Driver, was acquitted of murder but found guilty of causing or allowing the death and serious injury of a child, receiving a seven-year sentence. A safeguarding review later criticized social services for missed opportunities and poor information sharing, though it concluded these failures did not directly cause Ollie’s death. The case prompted significant reforms in child protection procedures.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/653347223776883.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1722391261748295ie</guid><title>It Was a Call from God: The Horror of the Turpin Family</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1722391261748295/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 21:01:29 GMT</pubDate><description>The Turpin family case horrified the nation in 2018, when 13 children were rescued from their parents’ home in Perris, California. David and Louise Turpin had kept their kids imprisoned, starved, and abused for years in what authorities later called a “house of horrors.” This video reveals the shocking details of the rescue, the abuse the children endured, and how the justice system brought the Turpins to account.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1722391261748295.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1456882892321761ie</guid><title>The Footage at the Gym Revealed What He DID to His Son!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1456882892321761/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:00:50 GMT</pubDate><description>Christopher Gregor was convicted in the heartbreaking death of his 6-year-old son, Corey Micciolo. Prosecutors revealed disturbing video evidence of Gregor forcing Corey to run on a treadmill just days before the boy’s death in 2021. This video breaks down the abuse Corey suffered, the investigation that exposed Gregor’s actions, and the trial that brought justice for the young boy.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1456882892321761.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">518580281333745ie</guid><title>She Was Only 2 When She Met This Monster</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/518580281333745/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:00:46 GMT</pubDate><description>The tragic case of 2-week-old Caliyah J. Guyton shocked Georgia in 2017. Her parents, Courtney Bell and Christopher McNabb, were charged after Caliyah’s body was discovered hidden in the woods near their home. This video takes a closer look at the disturbing details of the crime, the investigation that followed, and the courtroom trial that led to justice for baby Caliyah.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/518580281333745.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1694156894619728ie</guid><title>He Hid Her Tiny Body Inside a GARBAGE Bin!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/emmakennytv/videos/1694156894619728/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:01:24 GMT</pubDate><description>Maddy Middleton, an 8-year-old girl from Santa Cruz, California, was tragically murdered in July 2015. She was last seen riding her scooter near her family’s apartment complex before disappearing, sparking a community-wide search. The next day, her body was discovered in a recycling bin within the complex. Adrian Jerry Gonzalez, a 15-year-old neighbor, was arrested and charged with her kidnapping, sexual assault, and murder. The case shocked the local community due to Gonzalez’s age and the brutality of the crime. It raised difficult questions about juvenile offenders, community safety, and how such violence could occur in what seemed like a safe, close-knit neighborhood.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1694156894619728.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>