<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Emma Kenny Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/341711569190033</link><description>Emma Kenny Page</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:15:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1828470511146408my</guid><title>Ebony Simpson: The Heartbreaking End of a 9-Year Old</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1828470511146408/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Uncover the chilling case of Ebony Simpson, the angelic 9-year-old whose disappearance united a small Australian town in a search that took a dark and unexpected turn.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1828470511146408.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1828470511146408.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="1045"><media:title>Ebony Simpson: The Heartbreaking End of a 9-Year Old</media:title><media:description>Uncover the chilling case of Ebony Simpson, the angelic 9-year-old whose disappearance united a small Australian town in a search that took a dark and unexpected turn.</media:description><media:credit>Emma Kenny Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2205566456641308my</guid><title>They All Collapsed After THIS Lunch!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2205566456641308/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Erin Patterson, has been jailed for life, with no chance of release for at least 33 years, for murdering three relatives and trying to kill another with a toxic mushroom meal. This case shook a community in Australia and even a Supreme Court judge said Patterson's crimes were the ""worst category"" for offending and involved an ""elaborate cover-up"". What are your thoughts?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_2205566456641308.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1972207166663740my</guid><title>They Had Bruises Under Her Care *Roksana Lecka*</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1972207166663740/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Daycares, schools, kindergartens, these are the places parents send their kids assuming they are going to be safe and happy. But these parents knew something was definitely wrong when their babies showed up with bruises and resisted every time they stopped at the daycare... What are your thoughts on the Roksana Lecka case?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1972207166663740.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1351931270020699my</guid><title>Worst Police Response To A School Invasion *Bodycam*</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1351931270020699/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Not entering the building, taking their sweet time, pepperspraying the brave parents... This all is infuriating and heartbreaking considering that those young lives and teachers could have been saved... What are your thoughts? Em x
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1351931270020699.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">900871669063763my</guid><title>CCTV Captured Their Cruelty Against the Toddler!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/900871669063763/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Watching the footage makes me sick to my stomach... Even more so after knowing the details of what that little darling went through... What do you guys think?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_900871669063763.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">876592851789339my</guid><title>Took Her Husband's Life &amp; Ran for DECADES</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/876592851789339/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>I dive into the case of Linda Darby who murdered her husband and went on the run for 35 years after escaping from prison. Not only she ran away from the consequences of her actions, she also left 5 of her children behind... What are you guys' thoughts on this case? - Em x
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/876592851789339.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1204516845187649my</guid><title>Her Friends Warned Her About Him!</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AyCajS5Wpl4</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this poignant episode, Emma Kenny explores the tragic murder of Claire Inglis in Sterling, Scotland. This case not only sent shockwaves through the local community but also raised serious questions about domestic violence and the hidden dangers that can lurk in intimate relationships.

Emma delves into the background of Claire's life, painting a picture of a woman loved by many, whose life was cut short in a brutal act of violence. She examines the relationship between Claire and the perpetrator, seeking to understand the dynamics that led to such a tragic conclusion.

Through this exploration, Emma sheds light on the broader societal issues surrounding domestic abuse, the challenges victims face in seeking help, and the importance of community awareness and support. She discusses the investigation process, the legal proceedings, and the impact of Claire's loss on her family and friends.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1204516845187649.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1548105346473752my</guid><title>Lucy McHugh Was Helpless!</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xcwXKmXT42E</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this episode of Emma Kenny True Crime Stories, we delve into the heartbreaking case of Lucy McHugh, a vibrant young girl whose life was tragically cut short. Emma Kenny, a psychologist and renowned crime analyst, guides us through the harrowing journey of the investigation into Lucy's murder with sensitivity and insight.

The story begins with the disappearance of 13-year-old Lucy, a case that swiftly spiraled into a major criminal investigation. Emma meticulously unfolds the events that led up to Lucy's tragic demise, bringing to light the ominous signs that were overlooked, and exploring the chilling motivations that led to this unthinkable crime.

Emma discusses the manhunt that followed Lucy's disappearance, culminating in the arrest and subsequent conviction of her killer. Utilising her vast experience in psychological profiling, she uncovers the unsettling mindset of the perpetrator, seeking to comprehend the reasons behind his deplorable actions.

She further explores the deep scars left on the community following Lucy's murder, highlighting the societal and familial impact of this devastating event. This case serves as a stark reminder of the potential dangers that lurk in seemingly safe spaces, prompting important discussions about child safety and the protection of vulnerable individuals in our society.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1548105346473752.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">722681634003507my</guid><title>He Took His Ex's Life for Free Breakfast? - Joshua Davies</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fZVxKZXbkcw</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Joshua Davies murdered his ex girlfriend Rebecca Aylward for a free breakfast. I have covered this on a couple of TV documentaries but join me in my latest True Crime episode where I will give you my personal opinion on this tragic tale. 
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/722681634003507.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1182882856915908my</guid><title>Pregnant Woman Thought She Was Getting Baby Clothes</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1182882856915908/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Dynel Lane posted some baby items for sale on Craig’s list. When Michelle Watkins responded to the advert she eventually visited Dynel’s home to pick up the items. What happened next will take your breath away. Join me in this new true Crime episode where I go through the events that unfolded on that day in 2015. </description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1182882856915908.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1437680001127170my</guid><title>10-Month-Old Met a Nightmarish End</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1437680001127170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This is one of the cases that turns my stomach.. The things I would do to this excuse of a man...
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1437680001127170.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1291685582719597my</guid><title>He's Been Doing This to Kids Since He Was 13!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1291685582719597/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Westley Allan Dodd is a man that will be spending eternity in hell. It's chilling to see that he admits that he'd do it all over again if he were to ever let out. Unbelievable, chilling, heartbreaking. What are your thoughts?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1291685582719597.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1407112414490081my</guid><title>He Wasn't the Innocent Old Man He Seemed To Be</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1407112414490081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What are some of the cold cases that got solved AFTER decades that still stuck with you to this day?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1407112414490081.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1438855157864422my</guid><title>She Thought Her Daughter Was "Attention-Seeking" | Sharon Goldie</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1438855157864422/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This is one of those cases that drive most of us parents INSANE. Incredible that even after she came home, instead of checking on her SICK daughter, she went on and had a nice drink in her garden. I am speechless. Rest in peace Robyn...</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1438855157864422.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1516052412834075my</guid><title>Tori Was Only 8 Years Old...</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1516052412834075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Tori Was Only 8 Years Old...</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1516052412834075.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">870648325929138my</guid><title>He Faked It All to Avoid FBI Investigation!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/870648325929138/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Nicholas Rossi’s story is just bizarre. A convicted s*x offender who faked his own death before running off from the United States, Rossi re-emerged in Scotland under a new identity, claiming to be an entirely different man. In today’s case, I’ll take you through how he got caught due to some very determined people who were literally like dogs to a bone. Em x</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/870648325929138.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1355155549689589my</guid><title>He Took Her Life &amp; Pretended to Be Her</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1355155549689589/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Anastasia Grishman was an OnlyFans model and at 26 years old was becoming successful in her own right. Her husband Dmitry Khamlovsky was harbouring so much jealousy that he eventually snapped and murdered her... What are your thoughts on this chilling case? Seeing the signs beforehand, do you think this could have been somehow prevented?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1355155549689589.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1333774735460822my</guid><title>She Was OBSESSED with Other People's Pregnancies! | Taylor Parker</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1333774735460822/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Taylor Parker  murdered Reagan Simmons-Hancock  in the most barbaric of ways. The lies and deciept that she pushed on the build up to  Reagan's death were unbelievable and her warped reality ended when she did the unthinkable. Join me in my latest true crime episode where we go through this tragic story. Em x</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1333774735460822.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1195242188834751my</guid><title>Evil Babysitter Got Exposed During the Interrogation!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1195242188834751/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Kristie Flood and Jeffrey Meyers were babysitting little Fallon Fridley when she sustained massive injuries. Join me in this latest true crime episode where I take you through the events that led to this little angels death. Em x</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1195242188834751.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1970014143925760my</guid><title>Many Restraining Orders, Yet a Bitter End</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1970014143925760/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Eser was a young, beautiful Turkish woman who was just brilliant. Her life came to an end when she was brutally murdered at the hospital she worked by a man crazed by jealousy and obsession. What do you think could have been done to protect her? - Em x</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1970014143925760.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>