<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Emma Kenny Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/341711569190033</link><description>Emma Kenny Page</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:15:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">916034944441329sg</guid><title>Wrongfully Convicted: Friend's False Testimony Led to Murder Conviction</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/916034944441329/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2001, Ryan Ferguson was convicted of murdering newspaper editor Kent Heitholt in Missouri, largely based on questionable witness testimony. He spent nearly a decade in prison before his conviction was overturned in 2013 after courts ruled prosecutors had withheld evidence and relied on unreliable statements. Ferguson was fully exonerated, and the case became a landmark example of wrongful conviction. How many innocent people remain behind bars because the system got it wrong?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/916034944441329.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/916034944441329.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="1008"><media:title>Wrongfully Convicted: Friend's False Testimony Led to Murder Conviction</media:title><media:description>In 2001, Ryan Ferguson was convicted of murdering newspaper editor Kent Heitholt in Missouri, largely based on questionable witness testimony. He spent nearly a decade in prison before his conviction was overturned in 2013 after courts ruled prosecutors had withheld evidence and relied on unreliable statements. Ferguson was fully exonerated, and the case became a landmark example of wrongful conviction. How many innocent people remain behind bars because the system got it wrong?</media:description><media:credit>Emma Kenny Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1603280964131928sg</guid><title>Prime Example of Why Cruel People Should NOT Be Parents!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1603280964131928/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2017, baby Ollie Davis was killed in Leicester after his father, Michael Davis, broke his neck. While under investigation, Davis publicly asked for donations to a child bereavement charity, attempting to present himself as a grieving parent. After a complex six-year investigation, he was convicted of murder in 2024 and sentenced to life in prison. Ollie’s mother was also found guilty of criminal offences. How can someone hide such violence behind a façade of sympathy for so long?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1603280964131928.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1564396427947855sg</guid><title>Found on the Railroad Tracks | The Vera Jo Reigle Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1564396427947855/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Can you even imagine how disgusting and heartbreaking overall this whole case is? What do you think is the mentality behind all of this that triggers people into committing such heinous and cruel crimes?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1564396427947855.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">848643578177315sg</guid><title>CCTV Caught Her with a SUSPICIOUS Luggage!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/848643578177315/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Jemma Mitchell, an Australian-born former osteopath, was sentenced to life for the shocking murder of her friend, Deborah Chong, in 2021. After a falling out over financial help, Jemma took Deborah's life and drove 200 miles to dispose of her body.
What do you think drives someone to commit such an extreme act after a disagreement?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/848643578177315.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1589834338835018sg</guid><title>UK’s Youngest Killer’s Chilling Confession</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1589834338835018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1992, Sharon Carr was just 12 years old when she stabbed 18-year-old Katie Rackliff to death in London, making her Britain’s youngest known female murderer. The random attack went unsolved until Carr later confessed while in custody for further violent behavior. She was eventually sentenced to life in prison. The case shocked the UK and exposed alarming failures to detect extreme violence in childhood. How can such dangerous warning signs be missed so early?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1589834338835018.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">890865306832803sg</guid><title>A Mother’s Greed Turns Into The Unthinkable - Louise Porton</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/890865306832803/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2018, Louise Porton murdered her two young daughters, Lexi and Scarlett, in Birmingham, England. Prosecutors said she deliberately poisoned the girls with antifreeze before claiming they had fallen ill. Porton showed little remorse and even searched online for ways to fake a child’s death. She was convicted of murder and sentenced to life in prison. The case horrified the UK and raised chilling questions about maternal violence. How can harm come from the person meant to protect most?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/890865306832803.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">890502710034510sg</guid><title>Estranged Husband Finally Did the UNTHINKABLE</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/890502710034510/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>We hear heartbreaking and thrilling and cases solely fueled by jealousy. This is one of those absolutely chilling ones... What are your thoughts on this case?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_890502710034510.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">904840175414946sg</guid><title>Daniel Pelka Became A Scapegoat By His Parents</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/904840175414946/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Daniel Pelka’s mother Magdelena Luczak, and her partner Mariusz Krezolek were not fit to be parents in any way. Join me in my 101st True Crime episode where I take you through the events that unfolded in this sad and tragic story. </description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_904840175414946.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1221819832649268sg</guid><title>So-Called "Best" Friends Did the Unthinkable</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1221819832649268/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Gemma Hayter was a young woman who had various special needs and learning difficulties. All Gemma wanted was to have friends and to be included. Her so called ‘best friend’ Chantelle Booth decided to invite her to her house with a small group of reprobates Joe Boye,  Daniel Newstead, Duncan Edwards and Jessica Lynas and what unfolded that evening will be the story i tell in my latest True Crime episode. Em x</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1221819832649268.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1289671579884374sg</guid><title>Footage Shows Teen Left in the Hot Car for 6 Hours!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1289671579884374/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Can you even imagine putting your DISABLED CHILD into a blistering hot car for 6 hours??? The reaction they gave when they noticed that she's dead?? It is nauseating really. What are your thoughts on this footage?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1289671579884374.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1828470511146408sg</guid><title>Ebony Simpson: The Heartbreaking End of a 9-Year Old</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1828470511146408/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Uncover the chilling case of Ebony Simpson, the angelic 9-year-old whose disappearance united a small Australian town in a search that took a dark and unexpected turn.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1828470511146408.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2205566456641308sg</guid><title>They All Collapsed After THIS Lunch!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2205566456641308/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Erin Patterson, has been jailed for life, with no chance of release for at least 33 years, for murdering three relatives and trying to kill another with a toxic mushroom meal. This case shook a community in Australia and even a Supreme Court judge said Patterson's crimes were the ""worst category"" for offending and involved an ""elaborate cover-up"". What are your thoughts?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_2205566456641308.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1972207166663740sg</guid><title>They Had Bruises Under Her Care *Roksana Lecka*</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1972207166663740/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Daycares, schools, kindergartens, these are the places parents send their kids assuming they are going to be safe and happy. But these parents knew something was definitely wrong when their babies showed up with bruises and resisted every time they stopped at the daycare... What are your thoughts on the Roksana Lecka case?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_1972207166663740.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1351931270020699sg</guid><title>Worst Police Response To A School Invasion *Bodycam*</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1351931270020699/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Not entering the building, taking their sweet time, pepperspraying the brave parents... This all is infuriating and heartbreaking considering that those young lives and teachers could have been saved... What are your thoughts? Em x
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1351931270020699.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">900871669063763sg</guid><title>CCTV Captured Their Cruelty Against the Toddler!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/900871669063763/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Watching the footage makes me sick to my stomach... Even more so after knowing the details of what that little darling went through... What do you guys think?
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/thumb_900871669063763.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">876592851789339sg</guid><title>Took Her Husband's Life &amp; Ran for DECADES</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/876592851789339/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>I dive into the case of Linda Darby who murdered her husband and went on the run for 35 years after escaping from prison. Not only she ran away from the consequences of her actions, she also left 5 of her children behind... What are you guys' thoughts on this case? - Em x
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/876592851789339.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1204516845187649sg</guid><title>Her Friends Warned Her About Him!</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AyCajS5Wpl4</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this poignant episode, Emma Kenny explores the tragic murder of Claire Inglis in Sterling, Scotland. This case not only sent shockwaves through the local community but also raised serious questions about domestic violence and the hidden dangers that can lurk in intimate relationships.

Emma delves into the background of Claire's life, painting a picture of a woman loved by many, whose life was cut short in a brutal act of violence. She examines the relationship between Claire and the perpetrator, seeking to understand the dynamics that led to such a tragic conclusion.

Through this exploration, Emma sheds light on the broader societal issues surrounding domestic abuse, the challenges victims face in seeking help, and the importance of community awareness and support. She discusses the investigation process, the legal proceedings, and the impact of Claire's loss on her family and friends.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1204516845187649.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1548105346473752sg</guid><title>Lucy McHugh Was Helpless!</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xcwXKmXT42E</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this episode of Emma Kenny True Crime Stories, we delve into the heartbreaking case of Lucy McHugh, a vibrant young girl whose life was tragically cut short. Emma Kenny, a psychologist and renowned crime analyst, guides us through the harrowing journey of the investigation into Lucy's murder with sensitivity and insight.

The story begins with the disappearance of 13-year-old Lucy, a case that swiftly spiraled into a major criminal investigation. Emma meticulously unfolds the events that led up to Lucy's tragic demise, bringing to light the ominous signs that were overlooked, and exploring the chilling motivations that led to this unthinkable crime.

Emma discusses the manhunt that followed Lucy's disappearance, culminating in the arrest and subsequent conviction of her killer. Utilising her vast experience in psychological profiling, she uncovers the unsettling mindset of the perpetrator, seeking to comprehend the reasons behind his deplorable actions.

She further explores the deep scars left on the community following Lucy's murder, highlighting the societal and familial impact of this devastating event. This case serves as a stark reminder of the potential dangers that lurk in seemingly safe spaces, prompting important discussions about child safety and the protection of vulnerable individuals in our society.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1548105346473752.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">722681634003507sg</guid><title>He Took His Ex's Life for Free Breakfast? - Joshua Davies</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fZVxKZXbkcw</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Joshua Davies murdered his ex girlfriend Rebecca Aylward for a free breakfast. I have covered this on a couple of TV documentaries but join me in my latest True Crime episode where I will give you my personal opinion on this tragic tale. 
</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/722681634003507.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1182882856915908sg</guid><title>Pregnant Woman Thought She Was Getting Baby Clothes</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1182882856915908/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Dynel Lane posted some baby items for sale on Craig’s list. When Michelle Watkins responded to the advert she eventually visited Dynel’s home to pick up the items. What happened next will take your breath away. Join me in this new true Crime episode where I go through the events that unfolded on that day in 2015. </description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/341711569190033/1182882856915908.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>