<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Kendall Rae Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/104569341322280</link><description>Kendall Rae Page</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:15:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2608904906120263au</guid><title>He Hijacked a Plane Then Jumped with $200K and Vanished | The Unsolved D.B. Cooper Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2608904906120263/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In one of the most mysterious crimes in U.S. history, an unidentified man known as D.B. Cooper hijacked a plane, demanded $200,000 in cash, and then parachuted into the night—never to be seen again. Decades later, the case still fascinates investigators and true crime followers around the world. In this video, we break down what happened that day, the major suspects over the years, and the theories that might finally explain what became of D.B. Cooper.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/2608904906120263.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/2608904906120263.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="913"><media:title>He Hijacked a Plane Then Jumped with $200K and Vanished | The Unsolved D.B. Cooper Case</media:title><media:description>In one of the most mysterious crimes in U.S. history, an unidentified man known as D.B. Cooper hijacked a plane, demanded $200,000 in cash, and then parachuted into the night—never to be seen again. Decades later, the case still fascinates investigators and true crime followers around the world. In this video, we break down what happened that day, the major suspects over the years, and the theories that might finally explain what became of D.B. Cooper.</media:description><media:credit>Kendall Rae Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2002855953846423au</guid><title>She Went to a Doctor’s Appointment and Never Came Back | The Murder of Maria Cruz</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2002855953846423/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Maria Cruz was a driven young woman with a bright future ahead of her. When she went to a doctor’s appointment in New York City and never returned, her loved ones were left terrified and desperate for answers. What followed uncovered a shocking betrayal by someone she trusted. In this video, we look at Maria’s life, the investigation that revealed the truth, and the lasting impact of her story on those who knew and loved her.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/2002855953846423.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1362183001937752au</guid><title>Missing Baby Found After 51 Years | The Incredible Story of Melissa Highsmith</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1362183001937752/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Melissa Highsmith’s story is nothing short of miraculous. Taken as a baby in the early 1970s, she was missing for more than five decades before a DNA match finally reunited her with her family. This emotional case shows the power of hope, persistence, and modern technology in bringing long-awaited answers. In this video, we explore how Melissa was found, how her family never gave up searching, and what her reunion means after 51 long years apart.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1362183001937752.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">848838724450639au</guid><title>This Case Haunted His Brother For 35 Years  | Jacob Jeremiah Landin</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/848838724450639/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In April 1987, nine-month-old Jacob Jeremiah Landin died of a subdural hematoma in New Mexico. Though a confession was allegedly made by the mother’s boyfriend, no charges were ever filed. His brother Eric Carter-Landin has spent over 35 years seeking accountability and justice.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/848838724450639.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1226144922866842au</guid><title>What Happened to Oakley Carlson? | The Unanswered Questions in a Heartbreaking Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1226144922866842/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Oakley Carlson was a bright and loving little girl whose sudden disappearance left an entire community searching for answers. After being returned to her biological parents from foster care, Oakley’s life took a tragic and mysterious turn. This case raises difficult questions about the child welfare system and how things went so wrong. In this video, we go through the timeline of events, the ongoing investigation, and the efforts of those still fighting to find out what happened to Oakley.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1226144922866842.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2318915681886715au</guid><title>Love Triangle Turns Deadly in a Walgreens Parking Lot | The Death of Emmett Corrigan</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2318915681886715/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this tragic case, a secret relationship spirals out of control and ends in heartbreak. Emmett Corrigan, a young attorney and father, became entangled in a dangerous love triangle that would have devastating consequences. What began as a hidden affair soon led to a confrontation that changed multiple lives forever. In this video, we take a closer look at the events leading up to that night, the people involved, and the lessons that can be learned from this heartbreaking story.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/2318915681886715.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1575229853930572au</guid><title>A “Wife Swap” Family’s Unimaginable Tragedy</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1575229853930572/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The Stockdale family, once featured on Wife Swap for their strict household rules, faced an unthinkable tragedy years later. This case reveals how control and fear led to devastating consequences.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1575229853930572.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">25459164650376120au</guid><title>Changing Confessions Lead To A Huge Break! Zoe Campos</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/25459164650376120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2022, a confession by Carlos Rodriguez brought a major turning point in the case of 18-year-old Zoe Campos who vanished in Texas in 2013. Investigators tied Rodriguez to her death and the discovery of her remains after he altered his story multiple times, sparking renewed scrutiny of the long-running missing person investigation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/25459164650376120.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">838309041860982au</guid><title>Dee Dee &amp; Gypsy Blanchard: A Wild Truth Uncovered</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/838309041860982/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Gypsy Blanchard grew up believing she was gravely ill—until the truth unraveled. The lies told by her mother, Dee Dee, led to one of the most shocking and heartbreaking cases in true crime.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/838309041860982.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">638890072493089au</guid><title>What Netflix Left Out of “Unknown Number”</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/638890072493089/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 22:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2018, siblings Danielle Marzejka, 18, and Seren Bryan, 19, were found murdered in a shed behind their family home in Clinton Township, Michigan. The killer, Danielle’s boyfriend Ousmane Diallo, had shot both victims before hiding their bodies in plastic bags. Diallo fled but was soon arrested and later sentenced to life in prison without parole. The tragedy left a community reeling and a family shattered. How can love and trust so easily turn into betrayal and violence?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/638890072493089.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1401491011311575au</guid><title>How Mark Winger Almost Got Away With Murder</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1401491011311575/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Donnah Winger was found murdered, her husband Mark claimed he was protecting her. Years later, evidence revealed a calculated plan — and a chilling cover story that nearly worked.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1401491011311575.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2006572276822469au</guid><title>Held for 8 Months: The Eduardo Valseca Story</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2006572276822469/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Businessman Eduardo Valseca was kidnapped in Mexico and held in a small box for eight months. His resilience and will to survive shocked investigators and inspired global attention.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/2006572276822469.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4852902908269443au</guid><title>Sarah Turney Speaks After Her Father’s Acquittal</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4852902908269443/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Sarah Turney opens up about her sister Alissa’s case after their father, Michael Turney, was acquitted of her murder. She also discusses media exploitation and how it shaped her view of true crime.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/4852902908269443.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1352098263296707au</guid><title>What Actually Happened To Shawn O'Brien?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1352098263296707/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Shawn O’Brien was found unconscious in his Rhodes Island apartment in July 2006 with a severe head injury and died days later. While the official cause of death was ruled “blunt force trauma to the head” with the manner of death listed as undetermined, his family argues the evidence points to homicide—yet no charges have ever been filed.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1352098263296707.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1533009927881013au</guid><title>Non-Human Biologics Recovered?!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1533009927881013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Former U.S. intelligence officer David Grusch testified before Congress in 2023, asserting that the U.S. government possesses non-human biological remains recovered from UFO crash sites. Journalist Ross Coulthart has reported on these claims, interviewing whistleblowers who allege involvement in retrieval programs. Both have faced skepticism, with official agencies denying such programs exist.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1533009927881013.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1521486575524414au</guid><title>A happy ending. Victims FOUND after 10 years</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1521486575524414/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Amanda Berry, Gina DeJesus, and Michelle Knight were rescued in Cleveland in 2013 after being held captive by Ariel Castro for 9–11 years. Their escape brought national attention, led to Castro’s arrest, and reunited the women with their families.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1521486575524414.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1354432596037297au</guid><title>What Happened To Dallas Mom Prisma Reyes?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1354432596037297/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Prisma Denisse Peralta Reyes, a 26-year-old mom from Mesquite, Texas, disappeared on April 17, 2019, after missing her shift and failing to pick up her 6-year-old son from a babysitter. She was last seen on surveillance video in Dallas outside an apartment complex where her ex-boyfriend lived. Her white Jeep was found abandoned there. The case remains unsolved, with no suspects identified, despite multiple tips, released footage, and the family’s efforts to spread awareness.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1354432596037297.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1505678407343356au</guid><title>The True Story of Anna Delvey’s Deception</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1505678407343356/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Anna Delvey posed as a wealthy heiress, scamming New York’s elite out of thousands. Her story of deception and ambition inspired global fascination and the hit Netflix series Inventing Anna.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1505678407343356.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1912587849472689au</guid><title>The Disappearance on Murder Mountain</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1912587849472689/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Garret Rodriguez went to California’s Humboldt County to work on a cannabis farm but never returned. His death exposed the dark underbelly of “Murder Mountain” and the dangers hidden there.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1912587849472689.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">823300626734641au</guid><title>Did She Plot To Get Rid Of Her Husband?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/823300626734641/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2023, beauty queen Lindsay Shiver, her lover Terrance Bethel, and an alleged associate were charged in the Bahamas with a murder-for-hire plot targeting her estranged husband, Robert Shiver. Authorities say text messages and photos showing Lindsay sent orders to “kill him” sparked the conspiracy case. Bethel and Shiver plead not guilty, claiming it was all just venting.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/823300626734641.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>