<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Kendall Rae Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/104569341322280</link><description>Kendall Rae Page</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 23:45:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1034649655435302in</guid><title>A Teen Found Under His Own Truck… Accident or Something Far More Disturbing?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1034649655435302/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 23:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Grant Solomon’s death was ruled a tragic accident, but the evidence has left many questioning what really happened that morning. This video breaks down the timeline, the doubts raised, and why his case continues to spark debate.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1034649655435302.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1034649655435302.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="1114"><media:title>A Teen Found Under His Own Truck… Accident or Something Far More Disturbing?</media:title><media:description>Grant Solomon’s death was ruled a tragic accident, but the evidence has left many questioning what really happened that morning. This video breaks down the timeline, the doubts raised, and why his case continues to spark debate.</media:description><media:credit>Kendall Rae Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1521983412467812in</guid><title>The Unsolved Yoga Retreat Vanishing of Taylor Casey</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1521983412467812/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Taylor Casey disappeared during a yoga retreat, leaving her family desperate for answers. This video looks at the timeline, the search efforts, and the mystery surrounding her disappearance.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1521983412467812.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1521118582442421in</guid><title>The Case Of Laren Sims &amp; Larry McNabney</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1521118582442421/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Larry McNabney, a well-known California attorney, was reported missing in late 2001. Months later, investigators learned that his wife, Laren Sims, had been living under multiple identities and was responsible for taking his life before fleeing the state. Authorities uncovered financial motives, a detailed escape plan, and years of deception tied to Laren’s past. This video breaks down the timeline, key evidence, and how the case ultimately came to a close.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1521118582442421.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">783197898038799in</guid><title>Hit By His Own Truck or Was He Murdered? | The Suspicious Death of Grant Solomon</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/783197898038799/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Grant Solomon’s death was ruled an accident, but inconsistencies raised doubts. This video looks at the evidence, the family’s concerns, and why so many believe the case deserves a deeper investigation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/783197898038799.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">838403245856861in</guid><title>She Called 911 Mid Abduction and They Didn’t Save Her | The Case of Denise Amber Lee</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/838403245856861/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Denise Amber Lee managed to call 911 during her abduction, but crucial mistakes prevented help from reaching her. This video examines the timeline, the system failures, and how her case reshaped emergency response protocols.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/838403245856861.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">626417437127543in</guid><title>Lana Clayton Used Eye Drops to Poison Her Husband? | The Visine Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/626417437127543/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Steven Clayton died suddenly, the cause wasn’t clear. Investigators later discovered he had been poisoned with eye drops, leading to shocking revelations about his wife, Lana.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/626417437127543.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">842153051601965in</guid><title>Unsolved: The Dardeen Family Massacre</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/842153051601965/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1987, the Dardeen family was found murdered under disturbing circumstances. Despite multiple leads and theories, the case remains unsolved.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/842153051601965.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1871529813469702in</guid><title>When Halloween Decorations Go Too Far</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1871529813469702/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Halloween Decorations Go Too Far</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_1871529813469702.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1367872864919565in</guid><title>Did an Activity Tracker Help Solve Her Murder? | The Connie Dabate Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1367872864919565/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Connie Dabate was killed, her husband claimed a home intruder was responsible. But investigators uncovered digital evidence that told a different story.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1367872864919565.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1246088684225502in</guid><title>Murder, Fraud, Privilege, and Corruption | The Murdaugh Family Mystery</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1246088684225502/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The Murdaugh family once held major influence in South Carolina. Then scandals, financial crimes, and multiple deaths came to light.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1246088684225502.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1130954838795713in</guid><title>Did Her Husband Do This To His Family On Purpose?!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1130954838795713/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Did Her Husband Do This To His Family On Purpose?!</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_1130954838795713.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">800710532868122in</guid><title>The Man Who Faked His Own Death | John Darwin</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/800710532868122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>John Darwin staged his own death in a canoe accident to escape financial trouble, leaving his family and the public stunned. This video looks at how the plan unraveled and what happened after the truth came out.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/800710532868122.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">807430815380616in</guid><title>He Poisoned Her Cereal With What?! The Murder of Christina Harris</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/807430815380616/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Christina Harris’s sudden death first appeared to be natural. But investigators uncovered a disturbing truth involving her husband and a hidden toxic substance. This video examines the case, the evidence, and the search for justice.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/807430815380616.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">851676607320268in</guid><title>The Sad Case Of Ryan Poston</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/851676607320268/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On October 12, 2012, 29-year-old attorney Ryan Carter Poston was fatally shot six times in his Highland Heights, Kentucky home by his on-again, off-again girlfriend Shayna Michelle Hubers, who claimed self-defense. After a first murder conviction in 2015, her verdict was overturned and she was retried in 2018, where she was again found guilty and later sentenced to life with parole eligibility after 17–20 years.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/851676607320268.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1117317287228305in</guid><title>Christopher Langan: The Mind That Terrifies Scientists</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1117317287228305/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Christopher Langan claims one of the highest IQ scores ever recorded and created his own theory of reality. Some see him as a genius, others as controversial. This video explores his life, beliefs, and why his ideas spark debate.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1117317287228305.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1885583978834235in</guid><title>A Missing Girl, Family Secrets, and a Shocking Return | The Mary Day Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1885583978834235/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Mary Day vanished in 1983, raising questions within her family for years. Investigators suspected foul play, until a woman claiming to be Mary resurfaced nearly two decades later, leaving the case surrounded by uncertainty.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1885583978834235.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">675881362262928in</guid><title>Unsolved: The Mysterious Deaths of Don Henry and Kevin Ives</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/675881362262928/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1987, best friends Don Henry and Kevin Ives were found dead on train tracks in Arkansas, sparking decades of speculation and controversy. What was first ruled an accident soon raised serious questions when new evidence suggested something much darker may have happened. From local corruption theories to missing evidence, this case has remained one of the most debated mysteries in American true crime history. In this video, we revisit the events leading up to that night, the investigations that followed, and why the truth about what really happened to Don and Kevin still remains unclear today.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/675881362262928.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">781339271559122in</guid><title>Tourists Found Dead Near Their Hotel on Thailand’s Infamous Koh Tao Island | The Case of Hannah Witheridge and David Miller</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/781339271559122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Hannah Witheridge and David Miller traveled to Thailand hoping to enjoy the beauty and excitement of Koh Tao, a destination loved by travelers from around the world. But their trip took a tragic turn when the two were found dead near their hotel, sparking one of the most controversial investigations in recent Thai history. Allegations of police misconduct, wrongful convictions, and the influence of local power figures left many questioning what really happened. In this video, we revisit the case, examine the evidence, and explore why the island has earned such an unsettling reputation among travelers.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/781339271559122.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">668630682709665in</guid><title>Did a Father Intentionally Leave His Son in the Car? | The Cooper Harris Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/668630682709665/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The heartbreaking case of Cooper Harris left the public divided and searching for answers. In 2014, a young boy lost his life after being left in a hot car, and investigators soon turned their attention to his father, Ross Harris. What at first seemed like a terrible accident quickly became one of the most debated court cases in recent years. In this video, we explore the events of that day, the evidence presented in court, and the questions that still surround this deeply emotional case.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_668630682709665.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1967488117365759in</guid><title>Frank Abagnale Jr. The Greatest Conman</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1967488117365759/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Before turning 21, Frank Abagnale Jr. had successfully posed as a pilot, doctor, and lawyer, while cashing millions in fraudulent checks around the world. His unbelievable story of deception and eventual redemption inspired the hit film Catch Me If You Can. In this video, we take a closer look at how Abagnale pulled off his elaborate cons, how the FBI finally caught up with him, and the surprising way he turned his life around to help stop others from doing the same.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1967488117365759.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>