<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Kendall Rae Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/104569341322280</link><description>Kendall Rae Page</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:00:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">756931893363828int</guid><title>Pastor Murdered His “Sister-Wife” After She Gave Birth</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/756931893363828/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Marie Carlson trusted a pastor and his wife when they took her in during a mental health crisis. But after she gave birth to the pastor’s child and tried to leave their secret polygamist relationship, the situation turned deadly.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/756931893363828.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/756931893363828.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="771"><media:title>Pastor Murdered His “Sister-Wife” After She Gave Birth</media:title><media:description>Marie Carlson trusted a pastor and his wife when they took her in during a mental health crisis. But after she gave birth to the pastor’s child and tried to leave their secret polygamist relationship, the situation turned deadly.</media:description><media:credit>Kendall Rae Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1868368157098065int</guid><title>She Ran From Walmart and Vanished Without a Trace</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1868368157098065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>After being confronted for shoplifting, Tiffany Whitton ran out of a Walmart parking lot and was never seen again. This case is filled with addiction, unstable relationships, and unanswered questions that still haunt investigators today.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1868368157098065.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1213191260719444int</guid><title>Mother and Daughter Vanish Without a Trace</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1213191260719444/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Jennifer Wix and her young daughter Adrianna disappeared more than 20 years ago, leaving behind unanswered questions and a family still searching for the truth. This video revisits the case, the last known sightings, and why it remains unsolved today.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1213191260719444.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">848325268008311int</guid><title>She Poisoned Two Husbands and Tried to Frame Her Own Daughter | The Stacey Castor Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/848325268008311/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Stacey Castor appeared to be a grieving wife after two of her husbands died under suspicious circumstances. But investigators soon uncovered a chilling pattern of poisoning, deception, and betrayal. When evidence pointed back to Stacey, she made one final move that shocked everyone by attempting to blame her own daughter for the crimes.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/848325268008311.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1263344985630118int</guid><title>Young Mother Shelley Mook Vanishes After a Custody Exchange With Her Ex</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1263344985630118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Young Mother Shelley Mook Vanishes After a Custody Exchange With Her Ex</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_1263344985630118.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1190044556431403int</guid><title>Foster Son Poisoned With Salt?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1190044556431403/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In October 2006, four-year-old Andrew Burd passed away in a Corpus Christi hospital from a rare condition involving elevated sodium levels in his blood. The boy had been placed with Hannah and Larry Overton, a local couple in the process of adopting him, after entering the foster care system earlier in life. Medical examinations confirmed the cause of death as salt intoxication, prompting an immediate investigation by authorities.Hannah Overton, a mother of four who was pregnant at the time, was arrested and charged with capital murder in 2007. Prosecutors argued that she had intentionally caused the boy's condition, leading to her conviction and a sentence of life without parole. The case drew significant attention due to the unusual circumstances surrounding the death and questions about the evidence presented at trial.Years of appeals followed, with new medical opinions suggesting the possibility of an accidental occurrence linked to the child's behavioral tendencies. In 2014, Texas' highest criminal court overturned the conviction on grounds of ineffective assistance of counsel. Charges were dismissed in 2015, and in 2017, the Nueces County District Attorney officially declared Hannah Overton innocent, closing the case and allowing her eligibility for state compensation for wrongful incarceration.The Overton family has since focused on healing and supporting others through community efforts. The tragic loss of Andrew Burd remains a somber chapter, highlighting complexities in child welfare and legal proceedings. No further developments have been reported in recent years.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1190044556431403.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1377962037133236int</guid><title>He Disappeared After Using His Homemade Time Machine</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1377962037133236/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>He Disappeared After Using His Homemade Time Machine</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1377962037133236.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3394215750730877int</guid><title>She Vanished at Just 5 Years Old and Was Never Seen Again</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3394215750730877/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2004, 5-year-old LeeAnna Warner disappeared from her home in Chisholm, Minnesota, and more than two decades later, her case remains unsolved. Her sudden disappearance sparked an extensive search, but as time passed, troubling questions began to surface about the adults closest to her and what may have happened behind closed doors. In this video, we revisit the timeline of LeeAnna’s last known moments, the inconsistencies that raised red flags, and why investigators still believe someone knows the truth about what happened to this little girl.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_3394215750730877.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1350733309862274int</guid><title>Former FBI Agent and Daughter at the Center of a Shocking Killing</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1350733309862274/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Jason Corbett was killed inside his home by his wife and her father, a former FBI agent. They claimed self defense, but prosecutors said it was a brutal and intentional attack. This video breaks down the evidence, the trial, and the unanswered questions.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1350733309862274.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3898071090497327int</guid><title>Vacation with Friends Turned Fatal | What Really Happened to Shanquella Robinson in Cabo</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3898071090497327/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was supposed to be a fun getaway to Cabo quickly turned into a nightmare. Shanquella Robinson traveled with people she trusted, but she never made it home. Conflicting stories, disturbing videos, and international scrutiny followed as her family searched for answers. In this video, we break down the timeline of the trip, what her friends claimed happened, and why this case sparked global outrage and demands for justice.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/3898071090497327.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1506708918127562int</guid><title>Teenage Girl Vanishes Overnight Without a Trace</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1506708918127562/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2018, Karlie Gusé was getting her school life back on track. She had spent the summer with her new boyfriend and had been introduced to marijuana. After she had been caught using weed on school campus, she was put into mandatory counseling sessions and a program to get her back on track. And while she was doing very well for nearly two months, that all changed when she smoked weed while at a small gathering with friends. She entered a state of psychosis, and her family thought it would be best if she slept it off. But when they woke up the next morning, Karlie was nowhere to be seen. Following years of searches, missing posters, and misinformation, the question remains: where is Karlie Gusé?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1506708918127562.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1154164716879170int</guid><title>She Went Out for a Fun Night in Vegas and Never Came Home | Who Killed Lesly Palacio?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1154164716879170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was supposed to be a fun night out in Las Vegas ended in tragedy for Lesly Palacio. After spending the evening with people she trusted, Lesly was found murdered under suspicious circumstances. Evidence quickly pointed toward someone considered a family friend, yet years later, no arrest has been made. In this video, we break down the timeline of Lesly’s final night, the red flags surrounding the suspect, and why her loved ones are still waiting for justice while her killer remains at large.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1154164716879170.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">820591874219144int</guid><title>Apartment 801 | The Christian Andreacchio Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/820591874219144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Christian Andreacchio was just 21 years old when he was found dead inside Apartment 801 in Meridian, Mississippi. Authorities quickly ruled his death a suicide, but his family and many independent investigators have spent years questioning that conclusion. Conflicting timelines, unexplained evidence, and the behavior of those closest to Christian raised serious red flags that were never fully addressed. In Part One of this case, we take a deep dive into who Christian was, what happened inside Apartment 801, and why so many believe the official story does not add up.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/820591874219144.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">738134825981602int</guid><title>Who Really Killed Influencer Alexis Sharkey? The Truth Behind Her Shocking Death</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/738134825981602/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Influencer Alexis Sharkey was found dead on the side of a Texas road, and the case quickly drew national attention. This video breaks down the investigation, the suspects closest to her, and how the truth finally came to light.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/738134825981602.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1387170699442862int</guid><title>FBI Arrests $50 Million Pastor in Shocking Crimes Exposed</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1387170699442862/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Pastor David E. Taylor built a multimillion dollar empire on bold spiritual claims, but investigators say it hid years of fraud, abuse, and forced labor. This video breaks down the FBI raid, the charges, and how the scheme stayed hidden for so long.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1387170699442862.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1382265076725535int</guid><title>She Was Attacked By a Fellow Soldier and Never Came Home</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1382265076725535/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Denisha Montgomery reported being assaulted by fellow soldiers while stationed in Germany. Weeks later, she was found dead under suspicious circumstances. This video examines her final days and the unanswered questions her family still fights to uncover.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1382265076725535.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3238781559619580int</guid><title>How Baron Li Survived A Brutal Attack Orchestrated By His Ex</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3238781559619580/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Baron Li survived a violent attack planned by his ex, shocking investigators. This video reveals how he escaped, how the case unraveled, and how a murder plot turned into an incredible story of survival.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/3238781559619580.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">794387870270316int</guid><title>Stalked Inside a Store and Taken in Minutes | The Kelsey Smith Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/794387870270316/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A quick trip to a local store turned into a terrifying abduction. This video examines how she was stalked, what happened in the crucial minutes that followed, and how investigators worked to bring answers to her family.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/794387870270316.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">868525329161072int</guid><title>She Pretended To Be Kidnapped To Escape The Truth</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/868525329161072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Chloe Stein vanished on her drive home, triggering a frantic search. But when police uncovered the truth, the case took a shocking turn. This video reveals why she staged the kidnapping and what investigators discovered.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/868525329161072.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4250562778533927int</guid><title>Kidnapped On Her Way To School | The Disappearance of 15 Year Old Sierra LaMar</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4250562778533927/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Fifteen year old Sierra LaMar vanished on her way to the school bus, sparking a massive search and a heartbreaking mystery. This video looks at her final morning, the investigation, and the disturbing clues that changed the case forever.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/4250562778533927.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>