<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Kendall Rae Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/104569341322280</link><description>Kendall Rae Page</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3039485686256174my</guid><title>Husband Found Dead, Suspicion Falls on Wife: The Sandra Garner Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3039485686256174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Police were called to a quiet home after a sudden death that didn’t add up. Conflicting stories, strange behavior, and missing answers quickly put the wife under scrutiny. Was this an accident, or something far darker?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/3039485686256174.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/3039485686256174.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="1104"><media:title>Husband Found Dead, Suspicion Falls on Wife: The Sandra Garner Case</media:title><media:description>Police were called to a quiet home after a sudden death that didn’t add up. Conflicting stories, strange behavior, and missing answers quickly put the wife under scrutiny. Was this an accident, or something far darker?</media:description><media:credit>Kendall Rae Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">879609891668736my</guid><title>Her Final Facebook Post Still Haunts This Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/879609891668736/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Her Final Facebook Post Still Haunts This Case</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_879609891668736.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1550738182804472my</guid><title>Security Footage Captures Costumed Suspect Before Woman Is Killed</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1550738182804472/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Security video shows a person in costume approaching a woman outside her home. Moments later, she is gone and the suspect has never been found.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1550738182804472.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2313055229172068my</guid><title> He Hijacked A Plane Then Jumped with $200K &amp; Vanished</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2313055229172068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A man hijacks a flight, takes $200,000, jumps into the night, and is never found. Was it genius, luck, or a fatal mistake?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_2313055229172068.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">850756191190103my</guid><title>Was She Really Innocent After Her Husband Was Killed by Her Boss?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/850756191190103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Her husband was gunned down, her boss was convicted, and her behavior raised alarms. Was it all coincidence, or did she know more?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/850756191190103.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1233344695342758my</guid><title>Kidnappers Drown During Police Chase In Failed Murder For Hire Plot?!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1233344695342758/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Husband's Murder Plot Backfired When the Kidnappers Drowned After a Chase</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1233344695342758.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1645887076571409my</guid><title>Cruise Ship Mystery: Woman Missing, No Body Ever Found</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1645887076571409/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1998, 23-year-old Amy Lynn Bradley vanished from a Royal Caribbean cruise ship while traveling with her family, sparking one of the most disturbing missing-person cases at sea. She was last seen sleeping on the family’s balcony in the early morning hours, but by sunrise she was gone, with no signs of a fall and no body ever recovered. Despite massive searches by the U.S. Navy, the FBI, and local authorities, Amy was never found, and over the years multiple reported sightings have suggested she may have been abducted and trafficked rather than lost at sea. Nearly three decades later, her disappearance remains one of the most chilling and unexplained cruise ship mysteries in modern history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1645887076571409.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">903455318873734my</guid><title>Ballerina Ashley Benefield Kills Husband in “Self Defense”</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/903455318873734/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Ashley Benefield, a former ballerina and founder of a dance academy, shot and killed her husband Doug Benefield inside their Florida home and told police she acted in self defense, but investigators say the shooting came after months of escalating conflict, financial disputes, and a bitter custody battle over their young daughter; prosecutors argue the killing was intentional and part of a pattern of manipulation and control, while the defense claims Ashley feared for her life after repeated threats and abuse, making this case a high stakes legal fight over whether the shooting was justified or a calculated act of violence.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/903455318873734.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">916383634388038my</guid><title>Danyé Jones’ Mother Says Investigators Were Laughing After Responding to the Scene</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/916383634388038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When 24-year-old Danyé Jones was discovered hanging from a tree in St. Louis County, local police quickly labeled it a suicide. But his mom, Melissa, a fierce frontline activist from Ferguson, had a different story to tell. Her viral post stirred up headlines, alleging her son didn't take his own life but was lynched. Despite efforts to challenge the suicide ruling and seek transparency, authorities maintained their position. The case remains unresolved, leaving unanswered questions about the circumstances surrounding Danyé Jones's death and the pursuit of justice in Ferguson</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/916383634388038.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1196303282697863my</guid><title>Pregnant EMT Murdered By A Firefighter?! The Case Of Melisa Lamesch</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1196303282697863/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Melisa Lamesch was a pregnant EMT who should have been surrounded by people sworn to save lives. Instead, she was found brutally murdered, and the investigation quickly focused on someone from within the same first responder community. As detectives uncovered the details of her personal life, a secret relationship, and mounting tension, the case took a dark turn that shocked her coworkers and the public alike. Was this a crime of passion, a desperate cover up, or something even more calculated? The truth behind Melisa’s final days reveals how betrayal can hide behind a badge and a uniform.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1196303282697863.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">843478265258416my</guid><title> The Horrors Of Room 308: The Case Of Grace Millane</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/843478265258416/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Grace Millane was about to celebrate her birthday abroad, having spent months traveling through South America before exploring Auckland, New Zealand. However, when her family back home in the UK hadn’t heard from her in weeks, they contacted the police in New Zealand. What followed was a strange Tinder date, a hidden identity, and thousands of hours of CCTV footage that all tried to answer the question: what happened to Grace Millane?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/843478265258416.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1880531346187109my</guid><title>The Self-Help Guru’s Sweat Lodge That Became a Crime Scene</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1880531346187109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>For many, the landmark 2006 documentary The Secret was their first introduction to new age spiritualism and the law of attraction. This turned many of the Self-Help gurus featured in the documentary into overnight celebrities, including James Arthur Ray. From his “rockstar,” style seminars and in your face attitude, James rose to prominence by giving his attendees immense challenges, pushing them to breakthrough. But when a sweat lodge ran by James killed three people, the question remained: was he at fault? Did his teachings lead to this? Would he ever face justice or apologize?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1880531346187109.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">880982254638100my</guid><title>Facebook Catfish Murders: The Case Of Billy Payne &amp; Billie Jean Hayworth</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/880982254638100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Billy Payne and Billie Jean Hayworth were attacked in their home after being targeted by someone they believed they knew through Facebook. What started as harmless online interactions turned into a deadly setup, leaving both victims brutally murdered and their young child severely injured. Investigators uncovered a disturbing trail of fake profiles, digital manipulation, and personal betrayal that pointed to someone from their own community. The case exposed how social media can be weaponized, and how a virtual deception can end in real world violence.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/880982254638100.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1188686019592024my</guid><title>What Really Happened to Chelsea Poorman? Found Abandoned on Mansion Porch</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1188686019592024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Chelsea Poorman vanished after a night out in Vancouver, and days later her body was discovered on the porch of a massive waterfront mansion in one of the city’s wealthiest neighborhoods. Police initially treated her death as non suspicious, but her family and the public quickly questioned how a young woman could end up dead on private property without anyone noticing. Surveillance gaps, unanswered calls, and a timeline that does not add up have fueled suspicions of foul play. Years later, the case remains unresolved, leaving one haunting question. How did Chelsea Poorman really die, and who left her on that porch?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1188686019592024.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1204455651094669my</guid><title>Lies Captured On Police Bodycam | The Chacey &amp; Robert Poynter Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1204455651094669/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When police responded to a routine call, bodycam footage captured moments that would later become central to a homicide investigation. Chacey Poynter was reported missing, while her husband Robert told officers a story that quickly began to fall apart. As investigators reviewed surveillance, phone data, and chilling contradictions caught on camera, a disturbing timeline emerged that pointed to violence inside their own home. What first appeared to be a disappearance soon turned into a murder case, raising the question of how long the truth can stay hidden when every word is recorded.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1204455651094669.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1434475468334745my</guid><title>Lauren Cho Walked Off Into the Desert &amp; Her Body Was Found Months Later</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1434475468334745/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In June 2021, 30 year old Lauren Cho vanished after walking away from her friends near the California desert town of Yucca Valley. At first, those with her claimed she simply left to cool off after an argument. But as days turned into months, questions grew about why no one reported her missing right away, what really happened before she walked off, and whether she was truly alone when she disappeared. When her remains were finally found months later, investigators ruled out foul play, but her family and the public are still left wondering how and why she ended up dying in such a harsh and unforgiving landscape.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1434475468334745.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">895469246771674my</guid><title>Was Hurricane Harvey Used As An Excuse To Hide Her Body? | Crystal McDowell</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/895469246771674/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Hurricane Harvey tore through Texas in 2017, chaos and destruction followed. But amid the flooding and emergency evacuations, Crystal McDowell vanished. As the storm dominated headlines, investigators later uncovered evidence suggesting the disaster may have been used to cover up a calculated killing. This video examines the timeline, the suspicious behavior of those closest to Crystal, and why her family believes the storm was not the cause of her disappearance but the perfect distraction.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/895469246771674.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1409059570584861my</guid><title> The Twisted Case Of “G.I. Joe” Gliniewicz: From Police Hero To Police Embarrassment</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1409059570584861/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Lieutenant Joe “GI Joe” Gliniewicz was a beloved cop in Fox Lake, Illinois. As the fearless leader of their Youth Explorers Post, he mentored hundreds of kids and earned plenty of awards. So the community was shocked when their hero cop of 30 years was killed in the line of duty on September 1st, 2015. But an investigation into his death uncovered a scandal that scandalized the town and shocked the entire nation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1409059570584861.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1585320599556413my</guid><title>Only 11 Years Old and Charged With Murder The Shocking Jordan Brown Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1585320599556413/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Jordan Brown was just eleven years old when he was charged as an adult for the murder of his father’s pregnant fiancée. The case stunned the nation and raised disturbing questions about juvenile justice, evidence, and whether a child could truly commit such a crime.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1585320599556413.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">708783222059471my</guid><title>Shocking Scandal: Social Media Star's Fake Cancer Ruse</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/708783222059471/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Belle Gibson rose to international fame in the early 2010s as a social media wellness influencer who claimed she had survived terminal cancer through natural remedies and healthy living. Her story attracted millions of followers and helped launch a successful app and cookbook brand.  In 2015, journalists revealed that Gibson had never been diagnosed with cancer, despite years of public claims and fundraising tied to her story. Multiple investigations found that donations she said would go to charities were either not made or only partially fulfilled.  Australian consumer regulators later took legal action, arguing that Gibson had engaged in misleading and deceptive conduct. In 2017, a federal court ruled against her and imposed significant financial penalties for false claims and misuse of public trust.  The Belle Gibson case became a defining moment in influencer accountability, highlighting the risks of unverified health claims online and prompting wider scrutiny of wellness marketing, charitable transparency, and digital misinformation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/708783222059471.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>