<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Kendall Rae Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/104569341322280</link><description>Kendall Rae Page</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3394215750730877ph</guid><title>She Vanished at Just 5 Years Old and Was Never Seen Again</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3394215750730877/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2004, 5-year-old LeeAnna Warner disappeared from her home in Chisholm, Minnesota, and more than two decades later, her case remains unsolved. Her sudden disappearance sparked an extensive search, but as time passed, troubling questions began to surface about the adults closest to her and what may have happened behind closed doors. In this video, we revisit the timeline of LeeAnna’s last known moments, the inconsistencies that raised red flags, and why investigators still believe someone knows the truth about what happened to this little girl.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_3394215750730877.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/3394215750730877.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="623"><media:title>She Vanished at Just 5 Years Old and Was Never Seen Again</media:title><media:description>In 2004, 5-year-old LeeAnna Warner disappeared from her home in Chisholm, Minnesota, and more than two decades later, her case remains unsolved. Her sudden disappearance sparked an extensive search, but as time passed, troubling questions began to surface about the adults closest to her and what may have happened behind closed doors. In this video, we revisit the timeline of LeeAnna’s last known moments, the inconsistencies that raised red flags, and why investigators still believe someone knows the truth about what happened to this little girl.</media:description><media:credit>Kendall Rae Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1350733309862274ph</guid><title>Former FBI Agent and Daughter at the Center of a Shocking Killing</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1350733309862274/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Jason Corbett was killed inside his home by his wife and her father, a former FBI agent. They claimed self defense, but prosecutors said it was a brutal and intentional attack. This video breaks down the evidence, the trial, and the unanswered questions.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1350733309862274.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1350733309862274.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="571"><media:title>Former FBI Agent and Daughter at the Center of a Shocking Killing</media:title><media:description>Jason Corbett was killed inside his home by his wife and her father, a former FBI agent. They claimed self defense, but prosecutors said it was a brutal and intentional attack. This video breaks down the evidence, the trial, and the unanswered questions.</media:description><media:credit>Kendall Rae Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3898071090497327ph</guid><title>Vacation with Friends Turned Fatal | What Really Happened to Shanquella Robinson in Cabo</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3898071090497327/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was supposed to be a fun getaway to Cabo quickly turned into a nightmare. Shanquella Robinson traveled with people she trusted, but she never made it home. Conflicting stories, disturbing videos, and international scrutiny followed as her family searched for answers. In this video, we break down the timeline of the trip, what her friends claimed happened, and why this case sparked global outrage and demands for justice.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/3898071090497327.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1506708918127562ph</guid><title>Teenage Girl Vanishes Overnight Without a Trace</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1506708918127562/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2018, Karlie Gusé was getting her school life back on track. She had spent the summer with her new boyfriend and had been introduced to marijuana. After she had been caught using weed on school campus, she was put into mandatory counseling sessions and a program to get her back on track. And while she was doing very well for nearly two months, that all changed when she smoked weed while at a small gathering with friends. She entered a state of psychosis, and her family thought it would be best if she slept it off. But when they woke up the next morning, Karlie was nowhere to be seen. Following years of searches, missing posters, and misinformation, the question remains: where is Karlie Gusé?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1506708918127562.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1154164716879170ph</guid><title>She Went Out for a Fun Night in Vegas and Never Came Home | Who Killed Lesly Palacio?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1154164716879170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was supposed to be a fun night out in Las Vegas ended in tragedy for Lesly Palacio. After spending the evening with people she trusted, Lesly was found murdered under suspicious circumstances. Evidence quickly pointed toward someone considered a family friend, yet years later, no arrest has been made. In this video, we break down the timeline of Lesly’s final night, the red flags surrounding the suspect, and why her loved ones are still waiting for justice while her killer remains at large.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1154164716879170.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">820591874219144ph</guid><title>Apartment 801 | The Christian Andreacchio Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/820591874219144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Christian Andreacchio was just 21 years old when he was found dead inside Apartment 801 in Meridian, Mississippi. Authorities quickly ruled his death a suicide, but his family and many independent investigators have spent years questioning that conclusion. Conflicting timelines, unexplained evidence, and the behavior of those closest to Christian raised serious red flags that were never fully addressed. In Part One of this case, we take a deep dive into who Christian was, what happened inside Apartment 801, and why so many believe the official story does not add up.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/820591874219144.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">738134825981602ph</guid><title>Who Really Killed Influencer Alexis Sharkey? The Truth Behind Her Shocking Death</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/738134825981602/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Influencer Alexis Sharkey was found dead on the side of a Texas road, and the case quickly drew national attention. This video breaks down the investigation, the suspects closest to her, and how the truth finally came to light.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/738134825981602.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1387170699442862ph</guid><title>FBI Arrests $50 Million Pastor in Shocking Crimes Exposed</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1387170699442862/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Pastor David E. Taylor built a multimillion dollar empire on bold spiritual claims, but investigators say it hid years of fraud, abuse, and forced labor. This video breaks down the FBI raid, the charges, and how the scheme stayed hidden for so long.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1387170699442862.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1382265076725535ph</guid><title>She Was Attacked By a Fellow Soldier and Never Came Home</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1382265076725535/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Denisha Montgomery reported being assaulted by fellow soldiers while stationed in Germany. Weeks later, she was found dead under suspicious circumstances. This video examines her final days and the unanswered questions her family still fights to uncover.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1382265076725535.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3238781559619580ph</guid><title>How Baron Li Survived A Brutal Attack Orchestrated By His Ex</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3238781559619580/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Baron Li survived a violent attack planned by his ex, shocking investigators. This video reveals how he escaped, how the case unraveled, and how a murder plot turned into an incredible story of survival.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/3238781559619580.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">794387870270316ph</guid><title>Stalked Inside a Store and Taken in Minutes | The Kelsey Smith Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/794387870270316/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A quick trip to a local store turned into a terrifying abduction. This video examines how she was stalked, what happened in the crucial minutes that followed, and how investigators worked to bring answers to her family.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/794387870270316.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">868525329161072ph</guid><title>She Pretended To Be Kidnapped To Escape The Truth</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/868525329161072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Chloe Stein vanished on her drive home, triggering a frantic search. But when police uncovered the truth, the case took a shocking turn. This video reveals why she staged the kidnapping and what investigators discovered.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/868525329161072.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4250562778533927ph</guid><title>Kidnapped On Her Way To School | The Disappearance of 15 Year Old Sierra LaMar</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4250562778533927/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Fifteen year old Sierra LaMar vanished on her way to the school bus, sparking a massive search and a heartbreaking mystery. This video looks at her final morning, the investigation, and the disturbing clues that changed the case forever.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/4250562778533927.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1859950652067300ph</guid><title>The Gucci Empire Killer: The Shocking Plot That Brought Fashion Royalty Down</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1859950652067300/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The murder of Maurizio Gucci exposed a hidden world of betrayal, greed, and a deadly plan inside one of fashion’s most powerful families. This video breaks down the plot, the motive, and the truth behind the story that inspired House of Gucci.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1859950652067300.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">877399877953460ph</guid><title>She Killed Her Uncle Then Appeared in a Horror Film</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/877399877953460/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Tucker Reed admitted to shooting her uncle, claiming self defense. Soon after, she appeared in a horror film, raising unsettling questions about what really happened and what led to the deadly family confrontation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/877399877953460.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">874238425284043ph</guid><title>Beauty Queen’s Death Hides a Dark Secret</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/874238425284043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Michele MacNeill died unexpectedly, her husband’s story fell apart fast. As shocking details surfaced, investigators uncovered a chilling truth behind her death. This video breaks down the case and the twists that exposed a deadly deception.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/874238425284043.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1894315697790631ph</guid><title>Hillsong Exposed: Inside the Celebrity Megachurch Hiding Shocking Secrets</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1894315697790631/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Hillsong’s glamorous image hid years of allegations involving abuse, corruption, and powerful leaders protecting one another. This video uncovers how the church’s rise to fame masked a much darker reality.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1894315697790631.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1492652221851051ph</guid><title>Throuple Gone Wrong: The Disturbing Death of Aileen Seiden</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1492652221851051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Aileen Seiden joined a throuple she believed was loving, but it spiraled into control, abuse, and a deadly betrayal. This video uncovers the toxic dynamics, the violent secrets, and the truth behind Aileen’s tragic final days.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_1492652221851051.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2603007963390264ph</guid><title>Abducted On Her Morning Run By Pure Evil</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2603007963390264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Eliza Fletcher vanished during her routine morning run, triggering a massive search and a terrifying investigation. This video follows the timeline, the suspect, and how the community fought for answers.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/2603007963390264.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">733226349806211ph</guid><title>Tiktoker April Holt’s Death Almost Went Unsolved… Until Her Mom Got Her Killer To Confess</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/733226349806211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>TikToker April Holt was found in a scene that looked like suicide, but her mother believed something far darker happened. Her fight for answers uncovered a disturbing truth and helped expose April’s real killer.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/733226349806211.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>