<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Kendall Rae Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/104569341322280</link><description>Kendall Rae Page</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 18:00:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1188686019592024uk</guid><title>What Really Happened to Chelsea Poorman? Found Abandoned on Mansion Porch</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1188686019592024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Chelsea Poorman vanished after a night out in Vancouver, and days later her body was discovered on the porch of a massive waterfront mansion in one of the city’s wealthiest neighborhoods. Police initially treated her death as non suspicious, but her family and the public quickly questioned how a young woman could end up dead on private property without anyone noticing. Surveillance gaps, unanswered calls, and a timeline that does not add up have fueled suspicions of foul play. Years later, the case remains unresolved, leaving one haunting question. How did Chelsea Poorman really die, and who left her on that porch?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1188686019592024.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1188686019592024.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="739"><media:title>What Really Happened to Chelsea Poorman? Found Abandoned on Mansion Porch</media:title><media:description>Chelsea Poorman vanished after a night out in Vancouver, and days later her body was discovered on the porch of a massive waterfront mansion in one of the city’s wealthiest neighborhoods. Police initially treated her death as non suspicious, but her family and the public quickly questioned how a young woman could end up dead on private property without anyone noticing. Surveillance gaps, unanswered calls, and a timeline that does not add up have fueled suspicions of foul play. Years later, the case remains unresolved, leaving one haunting question. How did Chelsea Poorman really die, and who left her on that porch?</media:description><media:credit>Kendall Rae Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1204455651094669uk</guid><title>Lies Captured On Police Bodycam | The Chacey &amp; Robert Poynter Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1204455651094669/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When police responded to a routine call, bodycam footage captured moments that would later become central to a homicide investigation. Chacey Poynter was reported missing, while her husband Robert told officers a story that quickly began to fall apart. As investigators reviewed surveillance, phone data, and chilling contradictions caught on camera, a disturbing timeline emerged that pointed to violence inside their own home. What first appeared to be a disappearance soon turned into a murder case, raising the question of how long the truth can stay hidden when every word is recorded.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1204455651094669.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1434475468334745uk</guid><title>Lauren Cho Walked Off Into the Desert &amp; Her Body Was Found Months Later</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1434475468334745/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In June 2021, 30 year old Lauren Cho vanished after walking away from her friends near the California desert town of Yucca Valley. At first, those with her claimed she simply left to cool off after an argument. But as days turned into months, questions grew about why no one reported her missing right away, what really happened before she walked off, and whether she was truly alone when she disappeared. When her remains were finally found months later, investigators ruled out foul play, but her family and the public are still left wondering how and why she ended up dying in such a harsh and unforgiving landscape.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1434475468334745.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">895469246771674uk</guid><title>Was Hurricane Harvey Used As An Excuse To Hide Her Body? | Crystal McDowell</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/895469246771674/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Hurricane Harvey tore through Texas in 2017, chaos and destruction followed. But amid the flooding and emergency evacuations, Crystal McDowell vanished. As the storm dominated headlines, investigators later uncovered evidence suggesting the disaster may have been used to cover up a calculated killing. This video examines the timeline, the suspicious behavior of those closest to Crystal, and why her family believes the storm was not the cause of her disappearance but the perfect distraction.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/895469246771674.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1409059570584861uk</guid><title> The Twisted Case Of “G.I. Joe” Gliniewicz: From Police Hero To Police Embarrassment</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1409059570584861/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Lieutenant Joe “GI Joe” Gliniewicz was a beloved cop in Fox Lake, Illinois. As the fearless leader of their Youth Explorers Post, he mentored hundreds of kids and earned plenty of awards. So the community was shocked when their hero cop of 30 years was killed in the line of duty on September 1st, 2015. But an investigation into his death uncovered a scandal that scandalized the town and shocked the entire nation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1409059570584861.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1585320599556413uk</guid><title>Only 11 Years Old and Charged With Murder The Shocking Jordan Brown Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1585320599556413/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Jordan Brown was just eleven years old when he was charged as an adult for the murder of his father’s pregnant fiancée. The case stunned the nation and raised disturbing questions about juvenile justice, evidence, and whether a child could truly commit such a crime.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1585320599556413.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">708783222059471uk</guid><title>Shocking Scandal: Social Media Star's Fake Cancer Ruse</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/708783222059471/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Belle Gibson rose to international fame in the early 2010s as a social media wellness influencer who claimed she had survived terminal cancer through natural remedies and healthy living. Her story attracted millions of followers and helped launch a successful app and cookbook brand.  In 2015, journalists revealed that Gibson had never been diagnosed with cancer, despite years of public claims and fundraising tied to her story. Multiple investigations found that donations she said would go to charities were either not made or only partially fulfilled.  Australian consumer regulators later took legal action, arguing that Gibson had engaged in misleading and deceptive conduct. In 2017, a federal court ruled against her and imposed significant financial penalties for false claims and misuse of public trust.  The Belle Gibson case became a defining moment in influencer accountability, highlighting the risks of unverified health claims online and prompting wider scrutiny of wellness marketing, charitable transparency, and digital misinformation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/708783222059471.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1903218273912247uk</guid><title>Teen Disappears After Surviving House Fire Then Vanishes Without a Trace</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1903218273912247/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Eighteen year old Brookelyn Farthing was last seen after a house fire in rural Kentucky. She made desperate calls for help that night but by morning her belongings were found and she was gone. Did someone take advantage of the chaos or did something else happen after the flames were out</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1903218273912247.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">671718999240137uk</guid><title>A Mother Found Dead After an Overnight Party</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/671718999240137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On November 4, 2018, forty year old Tamla Horsford was invited to an adult slumber party with other football moms in Forsyth County, Georgia. She arrived smiling, carrying her pajamas and a bottle of tequila, ready for a carefree girls’ night. By the next morning, she was dead in the backyard. Authorities ruled her death an accident, claiming Tamla fell from a second story balcony after drinking. But almost immediately, her family and the public questioned the story.  Photos were missing, witnesses contradicted one another, and alleged injuries did not match a simple fall. Why were Tamla’s personal items handled before police arrived? How did a house full of party guests hear nothing? And why were some records sealed and refused to her family for years?  Her loved ones believe something happened that night that was never fully investigated, raising questions of negligence, bias, and a possible cover up. More than five years later, the fight for answers is still ongoing, and one burning question remains: what really happened to Tamla Horsford?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/671718999240137.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2318951255193829uk</guid><title>Where Is Five Year Old Summer Wells?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2318951255193829/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Summer Wells was five years old when she walked into her family's rural Tennessee home on June 15, 2021, and seemingly disappeared into thin air. Within minutes, she was nowhere to be found. Her mother says she was planting flowers outside, her brothers were nearby, and Summer had just gone inside to play. But when her mother came back into the house, Summer was gone. A massive search involving helicopters, dive teams, dogs, and volunteers combed through the woods surrounding the property, yet not a single confirmed trace of Summer has ever been found.  Authorities say every possibility remains on the table: an abduction, an accident, or something far more complicated within the home. Her parents insist she was kidnapped, but conflicting statements, changing timelines, and past issues within the family keep fueling public suspicion. Three years later, despite endless theories, rumors, and online speculation, the case remains unsolved and Summer has never been located. What really happened in those critical minutes, and where is Summer Wells today?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/2318951255193829.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">788914344167914uk</guid><title>Mom of 2 Disappears After Ex Would Not Leave Her Alone: What Happened to Ashley Elkins?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/788914344167914/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On April 30th, 2022, 40-year-old Ashley Elkins stopped answering her phone. Family and friends thought she was laying low, trying to rebuild her life after leaving an ex who would not stop contacting her. But when she missed her daughter’s birthday, panic set in. Investigators quickly learned Ashley had reported being followed and harassed in the weeks leading up to her disappearance. Her abandoned car was later found, her belongings still inside, but Ashley has never been located. With no arrests and no confirmed sightings, the question remains: did Ashley walk away, or did someone finally make good on the threats she feared?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/788914344167914.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">749426018203804uk</guid><title>Colorado Dentist Charged After Allegedly Poisoning Wife’s Protein Shakes</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/749426018203804/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Investigators say Dr. James Craig, a respected Colorado dentist and father of six, secretly ordered potassium cyanide and slipped it into his wife Angela’s protein shakes—only months after allegedly trying to poison her before. As Angela’s mysterious symptoms worsened, police say Craig continued showing up to work as if nothing was wrong, all while exchanging romantic emails with a lover. But when Angela died and the toxicology report came back, the trail of online purchases, chilling searches, and a past pattern of suspected poisoning attempts pointed straight to James. Was this a calculated murder for a new life—or a husband desperate to hide a long history of deception?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/749426018203804.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1303015324927202uk</guid><title>Was He Poisoned at the Bottom of the World? The First Murder in Antarctica</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1303015324927202/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>During Antarctica’s brutal winter of 2000, scientist Rodney Marks suddenly fell ill and died at the South Pole. Months later, toxicology revealed poisoning, raising chilling questions about isolation, motive, and whether a murderer walked free on the ice.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1303015324927202.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1707863463911488uk</guid><title>Mom of Four Vanishes Days Before Abusive Husband’s Trial | The Nikki Cheng Saelee-McCain Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1707863463911488/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Nikki Cheng Saelee-McCain disappeared just before she was set to testify against her abusive husband. A mother of four, she was trying to escape violence when she vanished without a trace. This video examines the timeline and unanswered questions.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1707863463911488.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">756931893363828uk</guid><title>Pastor Murdered His “Sister-Wife” After She Gave Birth</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/756931893363828/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Marie Carlson trusted a pastor and his wife when they took her in during a mental health crisis. But after she gave birth to the pastor’s child and tried to leave their secret polygamist relationship, the situation turned deadly.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/756931893363828.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1868368157098065uk</guid><title>She Ran From Walmart and Vanished Without a Trace</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1868368157098065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>After being confronted for shoplifting, Tiffany Whitton ran out of a Walmart parking lot and was never seen again. This case is filled with addiction, unstable relationships, and unanswered questions that still haunt investigators today.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1868368157098065.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1213191260719444uk</guid><title>Mother and Daughter Vanish Without a Trace</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1213191260719444/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Jennifer Wix and her young daughter Adrianna disappeared more than 20 years ago, leaving behind unanswered questions and a family still searching for the truth. This video revisits the case, the last known sightings, and why it remains unsolved today.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1213191260719444.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">848325268008311uk</guid><title>She Poisoned Two Husbands and Tried to Frame Her Own Daughter | The Stacey Castor Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/848325268008311/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Stacey Castor appeared to be a grieving wife after two of her husbands died under suspicious circumstances. But investigators soon uncovered a chilling pattern of poisoning, deception, and betrayal. When evidence pointed back to Stacey, she made one final move that shocked everyone by attempting to blame her own daughter for the crimes.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/848325268008311.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1263344985630118uk</guid><title>Young Mother Shelley Mook Vanishes After a Custody Exchange With Her Ex</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1263344985630118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Young Mother Shelley Mook Vanishes After a Custody Exchange With Her Ex</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_1263344985630118.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1190044556431403uk</guid><title>Foster Son Poisoned With Salt?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1190044556431403/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In October 2006, four-year-old Andrew Burd passed away in a Corpus Christi hospital from a rare condition involving elevated sodium levels in his blood. The boy had been placed with Hannah and Larry Overton, a local couple in the process of adopting him, after entering the foster care system earlier in life. Medical examinations confirmed the cause of death as salt intoxication, prompting an immediate investigation by authorities.Hannah Overton, a mother of four who was pregnant at the time, was arrested and charged with capital murder in 2007. Prosecutors argued that she had intentionally caused the boy's condition, leading to her conviction and a sentence of life without parole. The case drew significant attention due to the unusual circumstances surrounding the death and questions about the evidence presented at trial.Years of appeals followed, with new medical opinions suggesting the possibility of an accidental occurrence linked to the child's behavioral tendencies. In 2014, Texas' highest criminal court overturned the conviction on grounds of ineffective assistance of counsel. Charges were dismissed in 2015, and in 2017, the Nueces County District Attorney officially declared Hannah Overton innocent, closing the case and allowing her eligibility for state compensation for wrongful incarceration.The Overton family has since focused on healing and supporting others through community efforts. The tragic loss of Andrew Burd remains a somber chapter, highlighting complexities in child welfare and legal proceedings. No further developments have been reported in recent years.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1190044556431403.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>