<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Kendall Rae Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/104569341322280</link><description>Kendall Rae Page</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:00:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1382265076725535us</guid><title>She Was Attacked By a Fellow Soldier and Never Came Home</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1382265076725535/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Denisha Montgomery reported being assaulted by fellow soldiers while stationed in Germany. Weeks later, she was found dead under suspicious circumstances. This video examines her final days and the unanswered questions her family still fights to uncover.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1382265076725535.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1382265076725535.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="575"><media:title>She Was Attacked By a Fellow Soldier and Never Came Home</media:title><media:description>Denisha Montgomery reported being assaulted by fellow soldiers while stationed in Germany. Weeks later, she was found dead under suspicious circumstances. This video examines her final days and the unanswered questions her family still fights to uncover.</media:description><media:credit>Kendall Rae Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3238781559619580us</guid><title>How Baron Li Survived A Brutal Attack Orchestrated By His Ex</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3238781559619580/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Baron Li survived a violent attack planned by his ex, shocking investigators. This video reveals how he escaped, how the case unraveled, and how a murder plot turned into an incredible story of survival.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/3238781559619580.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">794387870270316us</guid><title>Stalked Inside a Store and Taken in Minutes | The Kelsey Smith Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/794387870270316/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A quick trip to a local store turned into a terrifying abduction. This video examines how she was stalked, what happened in the crucial minutes that followed, and how investigators worked to bring answers to her family.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/794387870270316.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">868525329161072us</guid><title>She Pretended To Be Kidnapped To Escape The Truth</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/868525329161072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Chloe Stein vanished on her drive home, triggering a frantic search. But when police uncovered the truth, the case took a shocking turn. This video reveals why she staged the kidnapping and what investigators discovered.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/868525329161072.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4250562778533927us</guid><title>Kidnapped On Her Way To School | The Disappearance of 15 Year Old Sierra LaMar</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4250562778533927/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Fifteen year old Sierra LaMar vanished on her way to the school bus, sparking a massive search and a heartbreaking mystery. This video looks at her final morning, the investigation, and the disturbing clues that changed the case forever.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/4250562778533927.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1859950652067300us</guid><title>The Gucci Empire Killer: The Shocking Plot That Brought Fashion Royalty Down</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1859950652067300/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The murder of Maurizio Gucci exposed a hidden world of betrayal, greed, and a deadly plan inside one of fashion’s most powerful families. This video breaks down the plot, the motive, and the truth behind the story that inspired House of Gucci.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1859950652067300.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">877399877953460us</guid><title>She Killed Her Uncle Then Appeared in a Horror Film</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/877399877953460/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Tucker Reed admitted to shooting her uncle, claiming self defense. Soon after, she appeared in a horror film, raising unsettling questions about what really happened and what led to the deadly family confrontation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/877399877953460.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">874238425284043us</guid><title>Beauty Queen’s Death Hides a Dark Secret</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/874238425284043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When Michele MacNeill died unexpectedly, her husband’s story fell apart fast. As shocking details surfaced, investigators uncovered a chilling truth behind her death. This video breaks down the case and the twists that exposed a deadly deception.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/874238425284043.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1894315697790631us</guid><title>Hillsong Exposed: Inside the Celebrity Megachurch Hiding Shocking Secrets</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1894315697790631/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Hillsong’s glamorous image hid years of allegations involving abuse, corruption, and powerful leaders protecting one another. This video uncovers how the church’s rise to fame masked a much darker reality.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1894315697790631.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1492652221851051us</guid><title>Throuple Gone Wrong: The Disturbing Death of Aileen Seiden</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1492652221851051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Aileen Seiden joined a throuple she believed was loving, but it spiraled into control, abuse, and a deadly betrayal. This video uncovers the toxic dynamics, the violent secrets, and the truth behind Aileen’s tragic final days.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/thumb_1492652221851051.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2603007963390264us</guid><title>Abducted On Her Morning Run By Pure Evil</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2603007963390264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Eliza Fletcher vanished during her routine morning run, triggering a massive search and a terrifying investigation. This video follows the timeline, the suspect, and how the community fought for answers.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/2603007963390264.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">733226349806211us</guid><title>Tiktoker April Holt’s Death Almost Went Unsolved… Until Her Mom Got Her Killer To Confess</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/733226349806211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>TikToker April Holt was found in a scene that looked like suicide, but her mother believed something far darker happened. Her fight for answers uncovered a disturbing truth and helped expose April’s real killer.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/733226349806211.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1603600437291787us</guid><title>Missing Baby Found Alive After 40 Years</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1603600437291787/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Decades after her parents were murdered, baby Holly Clouse was found alive. This video follows the twists that led to her discovery and the unanswered questions that remain.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1603600437291787.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1142176931422300us</guid><title>She Faked Her Daughter’s Cancer for Money?!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1142176931422300/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When young Hannah Milbrandt was said to be gravely ill, her community rushed to help. But investigators uncovered a stunning truth: her mother had staged the entire diagnosis for cash. This video breaks down how the scheme unraveled.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1142176931422300.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1545223940055440us</guid><title>Kayak Killer or Wrongfully Accused? The Chilling Case of Angelika Graswald</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1545223940055440/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When a kayak trip turned deadly, Angelika Graswald was accused of sabotaging her fiancé’s boat. Was it a planned killing or a tragic accident? This video breaks down the evidence, the doubts, and the unanswered questions in this gripping case.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1545223940055440.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3005181829668273us</guid><title>He Left a Note About Meeting Aliens and Vanished Into a Storm</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3005181829668273/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Granger Taylor told loved ones he was embarking on an interstellar journey, then disappeared during a violent storm. This video explores his final note, the clues he left behind, and the mystery that still surrounds his fate.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/3005181829668273.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1034649655435302us</guid><title>A Teen Found Under His Own Truck… Accident or Something Far More Disturbing?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1034649655435302/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 23:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Grant Solomon’s death was ruled a tragic accident, but the evidence has left many questioning what really happened that morning. This video breaks down the timeline, the doubts raised, and why his case continues to spark debate.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1034649655435302.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1521983412467812us</guid><title>The Unsolved Yoga Retreat Vanishing of Taylor Casey</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1521983412467812/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Taylor Casey disappeared during a yoga retreat, leaving her family desperate for answers. This video looks at the timeline, the search efforts, and the mystery surrounding her disappearance.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1521983412467812.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1521118582442421us</guid><title>The Case Of Laren Sims &amp; Larry McNabney</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1521118582442421/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Larry McNabney, a well-known California attorney, was reported missing in late 2001. Months later, investigators learned that his wife, Laren Sims, had been living under multiple identities and was responsible for taking his life before fleeing the state. Authorities uncovered financial motives, a detailed escape plan, and years of deception tied to Laren’s past. This video breaks down the timeline, key evidence, and how the case ultimately came to a close.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/1521118582442421.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">783197898038799us</guid><title>Hit By His Own Truck or Was He Murdered? | The Suspicious Death of Grant Solomon</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/783197898038799/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Grant Solomon’s death was ruled an accident, but inconsistencies raised doubts. This video looks at the evidence, the family’s concerns, and why so many believe the case deserves a deeper investigation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/104569341322280/783197898038799.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>