<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>True Crime Recaps Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/2722876767739321</link><description>True Crime Recaps Page</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:30:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1292002872609378au</guid><title>Unraveling the Evil Plot of Jennifer Faith</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1292002872609378/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Jennifer Lynne Faith admitted to orchestrating the 2020 killing of her husband, Jamie Faith, by persuading her former high-school boyfriend to carry out the shooting and concealing a $600 k life-insurance claim and a GoFundMe fraud.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1292002872609378.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1292002872609378.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="891"><media:title>Unraveling the Evil Plot of Jennifer Faith</media:title><media:description>Jennifer Lynne Faith admitted to orchestrating the 2020 killing of her husband, Jamie Faith, by persuading her former high-school boyfriend to carry out the shooting and concealing a $600 k life-insurance claim and a GoFundMe fraud.</media:description><media:credit>True Crime Recaps Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2928679820853904au</guid><title>"Do You Want Mom to Live?" The Staten Island Case That Shook Detectives</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2928679820853904/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Nineteen-year-old Damien Hurstel was arrested in Staten Island after police say he fatally attacked his mother’s boyfriend, Anthony Casalaspro, inside their West Brighton home. His mother, Alicia Zayas, told investigators her son had a long history of mental-health issues and had recently undergone a medication change. The investigation remains ongoing.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2928679820853904.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">24378248095183423au</guid><title>The Texas Triple Homicide: A Gruesome Tale of DNA and Deception</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/24378248095183423/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On June 17, 1985, Arlington, Texas mother Joanne Lemieux and her two daughters—12-year-old Renee and 14-year-old Danielle—were found murdered along with 17-year-old John Bradley in their home. After years of investigation using evolving DNA methods, neighbor Ronald Steven Trimboli was eventually convicted in 1989. The case is remembered for its brutality, investigative breakthroughs, and enduring questions about forensic science.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/24378248095183423.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1138313098450276au</guid><title>Inside the Louvre Heist That Looked Like a Scene From Ocean's Eleven</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1138313098450276/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On October 19, 2025, a highly coordinated daylight robbery at the Louvre Museum in Paris saw four thieves, disguised as construction workers, break in and steal eight pieces of French crown-jewels worth an estimated €88 million (about $102 million) in under eight minutes. They accessed the gallery via a truck-mounted lift, used a disc cutter on display cases, and fled on motorbikes, all while visitors were inside. Two suspects were later arrested in Paris. The incident has triggered a major investigation into museum security and cultural heritage protection.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1138313098450276.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">828907069734325au</guid><title>Behind the Friendly Neighbor's Door: The Trick-or-Treat Killing That Changed Halloween Forever</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/828907069734325/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On Halloween night 1973 in Fond du Lac, Wisconsin, 9-year-old Lisa Ann French left home to go trick-or-treating alone and never returned. Her neighbor, Gerald Miles Turner Jr., was later convicted of her sexual assault and murder and sentenced to over 38 years in prison. Her disappearance and tragic death changed local trick-or-treating norms and led to stricter sex-offender laws in Wisconsin</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/828907069734325.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1148916094014800au</guid><title>How a Giant Billboard Finally Exposed Florida’s Monster “Boat Man”</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1148916094014800/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1989 the bodies of Joan Rogers and her two teen daughters were found floating in Tampa Bay tied to concrete blocks. Investigators cracked the case after posting Chandler’s handwriting from a note found in the victims’ car on a billboard, a bold move that led a former neighbor to identify the writing and ultimately bring Chandler to justice.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1148916094014800.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1164405435700292au</guid><title>FBI Spent Millions of Dollars to Catch This Guy!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1164405435700292/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Theodore “Ted” Kaczynski conducted a bombing campaign between 1978 and 1995 that killed three people and injured 23 others while living in a remote Montana cabin. The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) mounted a task force of more than 150 full-time agents and invested over $50 million in what became one of the agency’s longest and costliest investigations.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1164405435700292.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1244026040867216au</guid><title>The Exorcism of David Glatzel!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1244026040867216/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1980, 11-year-old David Glatzel’s family in Connecticut called in paranormal investigators Ed Warren and Lorraine Warren after his behavior, including strange outbursts and alleged supernatural phenomena, escalated. The case became central to the infamous 1981 murder trial of Arne Cheyenne Johnson, the first in the U.S. to use a “demonic possession” defense.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1244026040867216.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1531672444680871au</guid><title>The Cruel Case of Channon Christian &amp; Christopher Newsom</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1531672444680871/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In January 2007 in Knoxville, Tennessee, Channon Christian (21) and Christopher Newsom (23) were abducted during a carjacking and taken to a house where they were tortured and murdered. Multiple assailants were convicted, and the case led to legislative changes in Tennessee as the victims’ families continue seeking justice and healing.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1531672444680871.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">788005340668847au</guid><title>When Teen’s Cry for Help Was Ignored, Tragedy Struck!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/788005340668847/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Authorities say multiple warning signs were missed before a deadly school event in Michigan shocked the nation. Despite teachers reporting concerning behavior, no action was taken until it was too late. The case has since sparked major conversations about accountability, prevention, and mental health awareness.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/788005340668847.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1340356574457592au</guid><title>Alabama’s Black Widow Poisoned Those Closest to Her For Sympathy</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1340356574457592/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Rhonda Belle Martin was executed in 1957 in Alabama for the 1951 poisoning of her fourth husband. She had previously confessed to killing her mother, two husbands, and three of her children using rat poison. The case revealed the disturbing nature of her crimes and remains one of the most notorious in U.S. history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1340356574457592.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1225412769619094au</guid><title>Johnny Gosch - One Of The Strangest Cases In History</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1225412769619094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On September 5, 1982, 12-year-old paperboy Johnny Gosch vanished during his route in West Des Moines, Iowa. No arrests were ever made. His case led to major changes in missing-child policy and remains unresolved more than four decades later.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1225412769619094.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1324256629011524au</guid><title>He'll Never Forget What He Saw</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1324256629011524/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Ed Gingerich made history as the first Amish man convicted for a killing after his 1993 attack on his wife Katie in Pennsylvania. Later diagnosed with severe mental illness, the case exposed cracks in how his community handled warning signs. Gingerich died by suicide in 2011, leaving behind a legacy of trauma and unanswered questions.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1324256629011524.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1369244954657699au</guid><title>Christa Pike: She Made History</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1369244954657699/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>At just 18 years old, Christa Gail Pike became the youngest woman sentenced to death in the U.S. after being convicted for the 1995 torture-murder of her classmate. She remains the only woman on death row in Tennessee, and under appeal, her execution date has been set for September 30, 2026.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1369244954657699.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1805136316760341au</guid><title>Harmless Ding-Dong Ditch Prank Went Horribly Wrong</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1805136316760341/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>While playing a common door-bell prank known as ding-dong-ditch in a Houston neighborhood, 11-year-old Julian Guzman was fatally shot after knocking on a house and running away. A 42-year-old man has been arrested, and authorities say the incident does not appear to be self-defense.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/thumb_1805136316760341.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4254769981468593au</guid><title>The Unsettling Story Of A Citizen's Arrest</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4254769981468593/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In May 2019, 62-year-old Kenneth Herring left a crash scene in Georgia when 25-year-old Hannah Payne pursued him, confronted him, and ultimately fatally shot him. Payne claimed self-defense; a jury later convicted her of malice murder, felony murder, aggravated assault, false imprisonment, and weapons charges. The case has drawn attention to vigilantism and racial justice issues.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/4254769981468593.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">793871656761088au</guid><title>Father Makes His Six-Year-Old Son Run On Treadmill Until The End</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/793871656761088/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Six-year-old Corey Micciolo was forced by his father to run on a treadmill while the speed kept increasing, a moment captured on video. Weeks later the boy died and his father was convicted of aggravated manslaughter and child endangerment.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/793871656761088.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1514896529790290au</guid><title>Two Decades of Waiting for Justice in Megan McDonald's Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1514896529790290/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2003, 20 year old Megan McDonald was found bludgeoned to death near Wallkill, New York. More than 22 years later, the accused Edward Holley is set for a retrial after a mistrial, while newly submitted DNA evidence and allegations of prosecutorial conflict have shaken the case’s foundation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1514896529790290.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1711036392925939au</guid><title>A Million-Dollar Home and a Scene Straight From a Horror Film</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1711036392925939/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In May 2014, elderly couple Russell and Shirley Dermond were found murdered in their upscale lakefront home in Georgia — Russell decapitated in the garage, Shirley found tied to cinder blocks in the lake days later. Their bodies lay in a pristine million-dollar home with no apparent robbery or forced entry, and nearly a decade later the case remains unsolved.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1711036392925939.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1819111398699733au</guid><title>This Case Just Kept Getting More Unbelievable</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1819111398699733/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2011, Philadelphia teacher Ellen Greenberg was found dead with over 20 stab wounds, yet authorities ruled her death a suicide. Her parents have long challenged this finding and continue to seek answers as controversy persists over how her case was handled.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1819111398699733.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>