<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>True Crime Recaps Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/2722876767739321</link><description>True Crime Recaps Page</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:00:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1420776726383003ca</guid><title>Bruce McArthur's Chilling Double Life</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1420776726383003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Bruce McArthur was a self employed landscaper in Toronto who worked for years in affluent neighborhoods and had long standing ties to the city’s Gay Village. To many clients and acquaintances, he appeared dependable and unremarkable, blending easily into everyday life.  Between 2010 and 2017, several men connected to Toronto’s LGBTQ community were reported missing. For years, the disappearances were treated as unrelated, and families struggled with limited answers as the cases remained unresolved.  In 2018, investigators arrested McArthur and later uncovered evidence linking him to multiple deaths. In 2019, he pleaded guilty to eight counts of murder, bringing long awaited confirmation to families who had spent years searching for loved ones.  The case led to widespread review of police procedures, particularly around missing persons investigations involving marginalized communities. It remains one of the most significant criminal cases in Canadian history and continues to shape conversations about trust, visibility, and accountability.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1420776726383003.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1420776726383003.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="569"><media:title>Bruce McArthur's Chilling Double Life</media:title><media:description>Bruce McArthur was a self employed landscaper in Toronto who worked for years in affluent neighborhoods and had long standing ties to the city’s Gay Village. To many clients and acquaintances, he appeared dependable and unremarkable, blending easily into everyday life.  Between 2010 and 2017, several men connected to Toronto’s LGBTQ community were reported missing. For years, the disappearances were treated as unrelated, and families struggled with limited answers as the cases remained unresolved.  In 2018, investigators arrested McArthur and later uncovered evidence linking him to multiple deaths. In 2019, he pleaded guilty to eight counts of murder, bringing long awaited confirmation to families who had spent years searching for loved ones.  The case led to widespread review of police procedures, particularly around missing persons investigations involving marginalized communities. It remains one of the most significant criminal cases in Canadian history and continues to shape conversations about trust, visibility, and accountability.</media:description><media:credit>True Crime Recaps Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">903145285708167ca</guid><title>He'll NEVER Forget What He Saw</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/903145285708167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2016, the death of sixteen year old Emma Stutzman inside her Amish family’s Ohio home initially appeared to be a medical emergency. She was found unresponsive, and early explanations offered to authorities did not immediately raise suspicion beyond a sudden illness.  As investigators reviewed the circumstances more closely, inconsistencies began to emerge. The county coroner later ruled Emma’s death a homicide, prompting a deeper investigation that focused on someone within her immediate family and community.  Authorities identified her older brother, Eli Stutzman, as the person responsible for her death. Before the case could proceed through the court system, officials confirmed that Eli died shortly after being named as the suspect, bringing the criminal investigation to an abrupt end.  The case drew national attention due to its setting within a traditionally private Amish community and raised difficult questions about oversight, reporting, and justice in insular societies. Emma Stutzman’s death remains a deeply painful chapter for those who knew her.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/903145285708167.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1100387898741411ca</guid><title>The Saddening Case Of 15-Months-Old Evelyn Boswell</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1100387898741411/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Evelyn Mae Boswell was a 15 month old child from Sullivan County Tennessee whose whereabouts became a concern in early 2020 after family members reported they had not seen her for several months. Authorities later confirmed she had last been seen in December 2019, despite claims that she was staying with relatives. The delay in reporting immediately raised red flags for investigators.  As the search expanded, law enforcement identified inconsistencies in statements given by Evelyn’s mother Megan Boswell and others close to the child. Officials focused on reconstructing Evelyn’s movements and determining who had last confirmed contact with her. Public appeals and search efforts continued as scrutiny intensified.  In March 2020, investigators located Evelyn’s remains on property linked to Megan Boswell. She was later charged with multiple offenses related to false reporting and the handling of evidence, followed by additional charges as the case progressed. The case drew national attention and highlighted the consequences of delayed reporting in missing child investigations.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1100387898741411.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">32862296606749735ca</guid><title>Real-Life "Home Alone" Case With Parents Who Abandoned Their Kids for 9 Days During Christmas</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/32862296606749735/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In December 1992, a case out of Chicago shocked the public after two young sisters were found living alone just days before Christmas. Nine year old Nicole Schoo and her four year old sister Diana were discovered by a neighbor after coming to her door cold and frightened, saying their parents had left town.  The girls told authorities their parents, David and Sharon Schoo, had flown to Acapulco for a nine day vacation. The children were not left with a babysitter or any emergency contact. Instead, they were given frozen meals, cereal, and written instructions on when to eat and when to go to bed.  Emergency responders arrived after reports of a possible fire alarm but found no adults in the home. The girls were placed with their grandmother and later into foster care while police searched for their parents. David and Sharon Schoo were located a week later at an airport in Houston as they were returning to the United States.  Both parents were charged with multiple counts related to child abandonment and endangerment. The case drew nationwide attention and intense public backlash. Ultimately, the couple avoided trial by accepting a plea deal and were sentenced to two years of probation.  The incident led to changes in state law and remains one of the most disturbing examples of parental neglect during the holiday season.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/32862296606749735.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1487572992314813ca</guid><title>The Secrets Under His Backyard!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1487572992314813/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Herb Baumeister was a successful Indiana businessman and family man who lived in a quiet suburban neighborhood during the 1990s. On the surface, his life appeared stable, with a growing company and a large home known as Fox Hollow Farm.  Behind closed doors, Baumeister was allegedly leading a hidden double life. He was known to frequent Indianapolis nightlife and was rumored to seek secret encounters that he carefully concealed from his family. Over time, several men connected to these social circles were reported missing.  In 1996, investigators began searching Baumeisters property after receiving information that raised serious concerns. What they discovered in the wooded area behind his home would later become central to one of Indianas most disturbing investigations, revealing evidence that suggested multiple victims.  Before authorities could fully question him, Baumeister fled the country. Days later, he was found deceased in Canada, leaving many unanswered questions. The discoveries at his home would later confirm that the truth hidden beneath his backyard was far darker than anyone had imagined.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1487572992314813.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">868810326039736ca</guid><title>Fred And Rose West's House Of Horrors</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/868810326039736/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In the mid 1990s, police in Gloucester England began investigating Fred and Rosemary West after renewed focus on long unresolved missing person cases. A search of the family home quickly changed the direction of the inquiry and revealed evidence of serious crimes spanning many years.  Investigators determined that multiple victims were connected to the West household, with offenses occurring across properties linked to the couple. The findings raised urgent questions about how the activity went undetected for so long and prompted a broader review of earlier reports and warnings.  Fred West died before standing trial, while Rosemary West was later convicted and sentenced to life imprisonment. The case became a defining moment in British criminal history, influencing how authorities approach long term abuse, missing persons investigations, and safeguarding failures within communities.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/868810326039736.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1973199309910595ca</guid><title>Is This The Most Evil Person Of The 1900's?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1973199309910595/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Is This The Most Evil Person Of The 1900's?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/thumb_1973199309910595.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1243755920983723ca</guid><title>Love, Loss, and the Unseen Evil</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1243755920983723/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Andrew Bagby was a 28 year old medical graduate found shot multiple times in a Pennsylvania park in November 2001. Investigators quickly focused on his former partner, Shirley Jane Turner, who fled to Canada shortly after his death and later announced she was pregnant with his child, Zachary Turner.  Despite facing extradition to the United States, Turner was granted bail in Newfoundland and awarded custody of Zachary. Authorities and Andrew’s parents repeatedly raised concerns about the child’s safety, but the courts allowed Turner to remain free while legal proceedings continued.  In August 2003, both Shirley Turner and 13 month old Zachary were found deceased in Conception Bay South. A public inquiry later concluded that the system failed to protect Zachary and that his death was preventable, leading to major changes in Canadian bail laws known as Zachary’s Bill.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1243755920983723.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">827786986743212ca</guid><title>The Chilling Story Of The Atlanta Monster!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/827786986743212/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 18:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>From July 1979 to May 1981, authorities in Atlanta investigated the deaths of at least 29 African-American children and young adults, mostly boys. The series began with the discoveries of 14-year-old Edward Hope Smith and 13-year-old Alfred Evans in a wooded area. Most victims died from asphyxiation, with remains often found in remote spots.Notable cases included 9-year-old Yusuf Bell, 12-year-old Angel Lenair, 13-year-old Lubie Geter, and 13-year-old Curtis Walker. The incidents caused widespread concern, leading to community safety measures and a large-scale task force investigation.Wayne Williams was convicted in 1982 of two adult murders and linked to several child cases through evidence, though not charged in them. In 2019, officials began re-examining preserved evidence with modern DNA methods.As of late 2025, no new public findings from the re-testing have been announced. The cases remain an important part of Atlanta's history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/827786986743212.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">693444597181167ca</guid><title>The Rise, Fall, and Redemption of Milli Vanilli</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/693444597181167/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In the late 1980s, German producer Frank Farian formed the duo Milli Vanilli with performers Fab Morvan and Rob Pilatus. Their debut album Girl You Know It's True achieved massive success in 1989, selling millions and earning a Grammy for Best New Artist in 1990. Hits like Blame It on the Rain dominated charts worldwide.In November 1990, Farian revealed that Morvan and Pilatus did not sing on the recordings, with vocals provided by session singers. The duo had lip-synced performances. The Grammy was revoked, marking the first such action, and public backlash followed as lawsuits emerged from fans seeking refunds.Morvan and Pilatus attempted a comeback as Rob &amp; Fab in 1993 with an album featuring their own vocals, but it saw limited release. Pilatus faced personal challenges and passed away in 1998 from an accidental overdose at age 32, just before a planned Milli Vanilli reunion project.Surviving member Fab Morvan has pursued music and shared the story through a 2023 documentary and his 2025 memoir. In November 2025, Morvan received a Grammy nomination for the audiobook version, highlighting ongoing interest in the duo's legacy.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/693444597181167.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1718482765795695ca</guid><title>A Son Tried to Save His Father and Everything Went Wrong</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1718482765795695/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In June 2021, authorities in Duxbury, Massachusetts, responded to reports of a missing person near Island Creek Pond. Scott Callahan, aged 57, was located submerged in the water and pronounced deceased at a local hospital. The medical examiner determined the cause of death as drowning, with the manner ruled homicide.Jack Callahan, then 19 and Scott's son, had traveled to Boston earlier that evening to retrieve his father, who had a history of substance abuse issues. The pair returned via rideshare and were dropped off near the pond area. A physical altercation occurred between them prior to the incident.Jack Callahan was arrested and initially charged with murder. Following an eight-day trial in April 2024, a jury in Brockton Superior Court convicted him of involuntary manslaughter after extended deliberations.In May 2024, Jack Callahan received a sentence of four to six years in state prison. The case involved investigations by Massachusetts State Police and local authorities, focusing on the events leading to Scott Callahan's death.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1718482765795695.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1795699467801836ca</guid><title>Inside the Dog Breeding Ring That Led to Diane Whipple's Death</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1795699467801836/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In January 2001, Diane Whipple, a 33 year old lacrosse coach, was killed in the hallway of her San Francisco apartment building after being attacked by two large dogs. The animals belonged to Marjorie Knoller and Robert Noel, attorneys who were caring for the dogs on behalf of a convicted felon connected to an underground dog breeding operation.  The dogs, Bane and Hera, were Presa Canarios linked to a network that bred and trained aggressive dogs for protection and intimidation. Evidence later revealed that the animals had a documented history of violent behavior and that repeated warnings about their danger were ignored.  Whipple was attacked when she encountered Knoller in the hallway while returning home from grocery shopping. Despite attempts to intervene, the attack lasted several minutes and resulted in fatal injuries.  The case led to a highly publicized trial. In 2002, Knoller was convicted of second degree murder, later reduced to voluntary manslaughter, while Noel was convicted of involuntary manslaughter. The case sparked national debate over dangerous dog ownership, underground breeding rings, and legal responsibility for animal attacks.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1795699467801836.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1576171903522017ca</guid><title>The case of Jill Dando </title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1576171903522017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On April 26, 1999, television presenter Jill Dando returned to her home in Fulham, London, where she was discovered with a serious injury outside the property. A neighbor found her shortly after 11:30 a.m., and medical assistance was called immediately. Dando, aged 37, was pronounced deceased upon arrival at hospital.The Metropolitan Police launched one of the largest investigations in its history, interviewing thousands of individuals and pursuing numerous leads. Local resident Barry George was arrested in 2000 and convicted in 2001, but his conviction was quashed on appeal in 2007 due to concerns over forensic evidence. A retrial in 2008 resulted in his acquittal.Various theories emerged over the years, including potential links to international events, though none led to further charges. The case attracted significant public attention, given Dando's prominent role on programs such as Crimewatch.As of late 2025, the investigation remains open but inactive, with police stating they would assess any new realistic lines of enquiry. No individual has been successfully prosecuted, and the circumstances continue to be reviewed periodically using advances in forensic techniques.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1576171903522017.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1804771956842762ca</guid><title>Clue to Asha Degree Case Buried Deep Underground!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1804771956842762/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Nine-year-old Asha Degree vanished from her Shelby, North Carolina home in the early hours of February 14, 2000, during a stormy night. Witnesses reported seeing a child matching her description walking along nearby Highway 18. Her packed bookbag disappeared with her, and she was last reportedly seen near a vehicle of interest.In 2001, authorities recovered Asha's bookbag buried along Highway 18 in Burke County, approximately 30 miles north of her home. The bag contained some of her belongings along with other items. Investigations continued over the years, with the FBI joining efforts and announcing potential vehicle leads in 2016.Significant developments occurred in September 2024 when law enforcement executed search warrants on properties in Cleveland County, seizing items including a green vehicle resembling one long sought in the case. Additional warrants in early 2025 targeted cellphones and revealed communications among individuals connected to the properties. Authorities have stated they believe Asha was a victim of homicide.The Cleveland County Sheriff's Office and FBI continue active investigations, reporting progress through retested evidence and new leads as of mid-2025. No charges have been filed, and the search for answers in this case remains ongoing. The community continues to support efforts to resolve the matter.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1804771956842762.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2099727797441122ca</guid><title>The Strange Story Behind Richard John Bingham - Earl of Lucan</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2099727797441122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Richard John Bingham, known as the Earl of Lucan, was a British aristocrat whose name became synonymous with one of the United Kingdom’s most enduring mysteries. In November 1974, the children’s nanny at his former family home in Belgravia, London, was found dead, and Lucan’s estranged wife was discovered injured nearby.  Police quickly focused their investigation on Lucan, who had been involved in a bitter custody and divorce dispute. Evidence at the scene pointed toward a targeted attack, and Lucan was named as the primary suspect. Just days later, he vanished without a trace, leaving behind his car abandoned in southern England.  Despite extensive searches and international leads, Lucan was never located. Over the years, reported sightings emerged from countries including India, Australia, and South Africa, but none were confirmed. His disappearance fueled decades of speculation about whether he died shortly after fleeing or managed to live under a false identity.  In 1999, a coroner’s inquest concluded that Lucan had committed the killing, despite his absence. In 2016, he was legally declared dead. The case remains one of Britain’s most puzzling unsolved stories, blending privilege, violence, and a disappearance that has never been fully explained.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2099727797441122.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">838910482081828ca</guid><title>The Homecoming King With a Deadly Obsession</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/838910482081828/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Berry Bryant was an 18 year old from Idaho whose disappearance in late 2021 quickly turned into a tragic investigation. After she failed to return home, family members reported her missing, prompting search efforts in Bonner County and surrounding areas.  Days later, Berry’s body was discovered in a remote wooded area near Priest River, Idaho. Authorities confirmed her death was suspicious, but early details were limited as investigators worked to piece together her final movements and determine who she had last been with.  For more than two years, the case remained unresolved while detectives reviewed evidence, conducted interviews, and followed up on leads connected to the days before Berry vanished. Her family continued to push for answers, keeping public attention on the case.  In 2024, law enforcement announced that an arrest had been made in connection with Berry Bryant’s death. The development marked a significant moment in a case that had long haunted her family and community, bringing renewed focus on accountability and justice for Berry.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/838910482081828.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4270555036511501ca</guid><title>An Example Of How Money Can Tear Families Apart</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4270555036511501/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>An Example Of How Money Can Tear Families Apart</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/thumb_4270555036511501.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1540963497104002ca</guid><title>His Own Cameras Exposed the Abuse He Put His Wife and Family Through</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1540963497104002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Authorities in Oklahoma City are investigating the death of 34 year old Shawntae Lynn Brown, following the arrest of her husband, Joshua Brown.  According to a probable cause affidavit, Joshua Brown told investigators that an argument escalated inside the couple’s home. He admitted to physically assaulting Shawntae Brown and later stated that he “went too far.” Emergency responders were called to the scene, where Shawntae was pronounced deceased.  Police took Joshua Brown into custody and charged him in connection with his wife’s death. Investigators say the case remains active as authorities continue reviewing evidence and statements.  Court records indicate Brown is being held while legal proceedings move forward. Officials have not released additional details at this time.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/thumb_1540963497104002.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1255681973284618ca</guid><title>His EVIL Christmas Plans For His Family</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1255681973284618/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In December 1987, authorities in Arkansas uncovered a severe family tragedy involving Ronald Gene Simmons, a middle aged man living in the small town of Dover. What initially appeared to be a private household matter quickly expanded into a major criminal investigation spanning multiple locations in Pope County.  Investigators determined that Simmons had been living an increasingly isolated life with his family, largely disconnected from schools, neighbors, and community services. Court records later revealed long standing issues inside the home that had gone unnoticed for years, raising questions about how warning signs can be missed in closed family environments.  After leaving his residence, Simmons traveled to Russellville, where additional incidents occurred at a former workplace, prompting a large scale law enforcement response. He was taken into custody the same day without resistance.  The case resulted in multiple convictions and remains one of the most studied examples of how prolonged isolation, lack of oversight, and unreported domestic abuse can escalate into extreme outcomes. Today, it is referenced in academic, legal, and prevention focused discussions about family safety and early intervention.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1255681973284618.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1825873661400127ca</guid><title>Genius Turned Psychopath, Peter Madsen!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1825873661400127/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Peter Madsen was a Danish engineer and entrepreneur once known for his work on homemade submarines and rockets. He gained public attention for ambitious projects that drew support from volunteers and curiosity from international media. That image changed in August 2017 after journalist Kim Wall boarded his privately built submarine for an interview.  Wall never returned from the trip, and authorities launched a large scale search in Danish waters. Investigators later confirmed that she had died during the voyage. Madsen initially gave conflicting explanations before evidence presented in court contradicted his accounts.  In 2018, a Danish court convicted Madsen of murder and related charges after weeks of testimony and forensic analysis. Prosecutors established that the crime occurred inside the submarine and rejected claims that the death was accidental. He was sentenced to life in prison, the harshest penalty under Danish law.  The case shocked Denmark and the global science community, raising questions about how someone celebrated for technical skill was able to conceal violent behavior. It also prompted broader discussion about trust power dynamics and accountability within unconventional innovation circles.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1825873661400127.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>