<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>True Crime Recaps Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/2722876767739321</link><description>True Crime Recaps Page</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:00:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">793871656761088in</guid><title>Father Makes His Six-Year-Old Son Run On Treadmill Until The End</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/793871656761088/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Six-year-old Corey Micciolo was forced by his father to run on a treadmill while the speed kept increasing, a moment captured on video. Weeks later the boy died and his father was convicted of aggravated manslaughter and child endangerment.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/793871656761088.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/793871656761088.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="568"><media:title>Father Makes His Six-Year-Old Son Run On Treadmill Until The End</media:title><media:description>Six-year-old Corey Micciolo was forced by his father to run on a treadmill while the speed kept increasing, a moment captured on video. Weeks later the boy died and his father was convicted of aggravated manslaughter and child endangerment.</media:description><media:credit>True Crime Recaps Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1514896529790290in</guid><title>Two Decades of Waiting for Justice in Megan McDonald's Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1514896529790290/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2003, 20 year old Megan McDonald was found bludgeoned to death near Wallkill, New York. More than 22 years later, the accused Edward Holley is set for a retrial after a mistrial, while newly submitted DNA evidence and allegations of prosecutorial conflict have shaken the case’s foundation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1514896529790290.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1711036392925939in</guid><title>A Million-Dollar Home and a Scene Straight From a Horror Film</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1711036392925939/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In May 2014, elderly couple Russell and Shirley Dermond were found murdered in their upscale lakefront home in Georgia — Russell decapitated in the garage, Shirley found tied to cinder blocks in the lake days later. Their bodies lay in a pristine million-dollar home with no apparent robbery or forced entry, and nearly a decade later the case remains unsolved.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1711036392925939.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1819111398699733in</guid><title>This Case Just Kept Getting More Unbelievable</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1819111398699733/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2011, Philadelphia teacher Ellen Greenberg was found dead with over 20 stab wounds, yet authorities ruled her death a suicide. Her parents have long challenged this finding and continue to seek answers as controversy persists over how her case was handled.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1819111398699733.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2001485447254576in</guid><title>She Lost Her Twin and Married the Man Accused of Killing Her</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2001485447254576/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On July 16 2010, 19-year-old Johana Casas was found shot dead outside Pico Truncado in Argentina. A local court later convicted her ex-boyfriend of the killing. Years later, Johana’s twin sister Edith married the convicted man, a move that sparked outrage and raised questions about loyalty, grief, and justice</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2001485447254576.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1479539886425590in</guid><title>Professor Snaps During Faculty Meeting After Being Denied Tenure</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1479539886425590/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A university professor’s frustration over a denied tenure decision escalated into tragedy during a faculty meeting. The incident shocked the academic community and raised questions about stress, pressure, and mental health in higher education.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1479539886425590.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1377743337043969in</guid><title>Father Throws His Two Kids off the Balcony for His Mistress!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1377743337043969/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Zhang Bo and his girlfriend Ye Chengchen were executed in January 2024 for the fatal 2020 murder of his 2-year-old daughter and 1-year-old son in Chongqing. The children were thrown from the 15th floor. Prosecutors said Ye pressured Zhang to kill them so they wouldn’t stand in the way of his new relationship.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1377743337043969.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1108700611427741in</guid><title>The Fatal Hit-and-Run by a Wealthy Socialite</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1108700611427741/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Rebecca Grossman was convicted of two counts of second-degree murder, gross vehicular manslaughter, and hit-and-run after her Mercedes struck brothers Mark (11) and Jacob (8) Iskander in a marked crosswalk in Westlake Village in 2020. Key evidence: her car’s data showed speeds up to 81 mph in a 45-mph zone. In June 2024, she was sentenced to 15 years-to-life in prison.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1108700611427741.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2198914894275155in</guid><title>The Lies and Deceit of Pam Hupp!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2198914894275155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Before being convicted of a 2016 murder, Pam Hupp repeatedly gave false stories and changed her accounts in investigations. Prosecutors allege she killed her friend Betsy Faria to collect life insurance and framed others in the process. Despite long legal battles, she remains in prison and now faces fresh charges in Faria’s death, with authorities seeking the death penalty.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2198914894275155.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1516427106223043in</guid><title>When Reality Becomes Unbelievable: The Bizarre Case of Lacey Fletcher</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1516427106223043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2022, 36-year-old Lacey Fletcher was found in devastating conditions inside her parents’ Louisiana home. Investigators later determined she had been left without proper care for years, despite clear signs she needed help. Her parents, Clay and Sheila Fletcher, were held accountable for extreme neglect. The case has since sparked national outrage</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1516427106223043.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1165563025512724in</guid><title>The Dark Legacy of the Cremation King of California</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1165563025512724/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What started as a trusted family business turned into one of California’s most disturbing scandals. The “Cremation King,” once known for his success in the funeral industry, was hiding a horrifying secret behind closed doors. When investigators uncovered what was really happening at his facilities, it exposed years of deceit, greed, and unimaginable neglect — leaving families to wonder what truly happened to their loved ones.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1165563025512724.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">833726855756477in</guid><title>The Man Who Helped Carry Her Casket Is Now Charged With Her Demise</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/833726855756477/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Decades after carrying Karen Snider’s casket, a former pallbearer has been arrested and charged with her 1966 murder, following new DNA evidence linking him to the crime.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/833726855756477.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">807873274944271in</guid><title>He Locked Her Up For 24 YEARS!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/807873274944271/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Josef Fritzl kept his daughter hidden in a secret basement beneath his home in Austria for 24 years. The shocking case came to light in 2008, leading to his arrest and life sentence. Decades later, it remains one of Europe’s most disturbing criminal cases.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/807873274944271.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2040383096703831in</guid><title>Detectives Say They Know Who Did This to Him After 14 Years</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2040383096703831/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>After 14 years, Newnan police arrested Scotty Elliot Smith, 38, who confessed to killing 17-year-old Blake Chappell in 2011. Smith faces felony murder, aggravated assault, and tampering with evidence charges. The case was reopened in 2024 following new evidence and a 2023 anonymous tip.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2040383096703831.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2660379717645318in</guid><title>Diddy’s ‘Wild King Nights' EXPOSED! </title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2660379717645318/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Sean "Diddy" Combs was sentenced on October 3, 2025, to 50 months (just over 4 years) in federal prison for two counts of transportation for the purpose of prostitution, violating the Mann Act. He was acquitted of more serious charges, including racketeering and sex trafficking. The sentence also includes a $500,000 fine and five years of supervised release.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2660379717645318.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">829283413120876in</guid><title>Ed Gein: REAL Life Leatherface</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/829283413120876/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Ed Gein, a Wisconsin man in the 1950s, committed crimes that would shock the nation. Known for grave robbing and making objects from human remains, Gein’s actions inspired iconic horror characters in films like Psycho and The Texas Chainsaw Massacre. His case revealed the chilling effects of isolation, mental illness, and a twisted upbringing, leaving a lasting mark on true crime history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/829283413120876.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">803523012625151in</guid><title>He Left a Trail of Horror in His In-Laws’ House While Sleepwalking</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/TrueCrimeRecapsVideos/videos/803523012625151/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1987, Kenneth Parks drove 14 miles, entered his in-laws’ home, and left behind a horrifying scene, all while claiming he was asleep. His defense? Sleepwalking. What followed was one of the most shocking and controversial trials in Canadian history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/803523012625151.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4157484967905126in</guid><title>5-Year-Old VANISHED Without a Trace</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/TrueCrimeRecapsVideos/videos/4157484967905126/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Summer Wells, a 5-year-old girl from Hawkins County, Tennessee, was reported missing on June 15, 2021. Despite extensive search efforts and over 6,500 leads, her whereabouts remain unknown. Authorities continue to investigate, and the Tennessee Bureau of Investigation maintains an active Amber Alert in hopes of bringing Summer home.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/4157484967905126.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">781835051368248in</guid><title>Heavy Metal Band Sacrifices Freshman Elyse Pahler to Make Their Band Famous</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/781835051368248/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1995, 15-year-old Elyse Pahler was killed by three classmates in California. The case drew national attention due to the unusual circumstances and was later solved through police investigation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://scontent-sof1-1.xx.fbcdn.net/v/t15.5256-10/558094096_1818030075470194_148138482286465164_n.jpg?stp=dst-jpg_p160x160_tt6&amp;_nc_cat=100&amp;ccb=1-7&amp;_nc_sid=810293&amp;_nc_ohc=DT5JtjsxRrgQ7kNvwGha5y4&amp;_nc_oc=AdlMWOIWNx2uA3Eu7ouzQzVxuUxfEfoqpP9CG2My6MGHpd6gbZBsdMaInlvcMRLB7kqpb1OP1d8x0URbCz_RpXQc&amp;_nc_zt=23&amp;_nc_ht=scontent-sof1-1.xx&amp;edm=APRAPSkEAAAA&amp;_nc_gid=4DBucosYDcoQK6DMKqgyzg&amp;oh=00_AfefDyfJjovHorzKbIgsHkks1-3cUWuGKK4p9eVdNYgoOw&amp;oe=68E4DA02" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">805339622247387in</guid><title>Austin’s Most Disturbing Cold Case Remains Unsolved</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/TrueCrimeRecapsVideos/videos/805339622247387/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1991, four teenage girls were killed in a yogurt shop in Austin, Texas. Decades later, DNA and investigative work have identified a likely suspect, offering new insight into this long-unsolved case</description><media:thumbnail url="https://scontent-sof1-2.xx.fbcdn.net/v/t15.5256-10/538913104_4231485820470046_3983919163198152601_n.jpg?stp=dst-jpg_p160x160_tt6&amp;_nc_cat=111&amp;ccb=1-7&amp;_nc_sid=810293&amp;_nc_ohc=tVJHXGWrZhwQ7kNvwErmBod&amp;_nc_oc=AdlDVZC3yp83pEgMr8vEgLPIJIbmEHQab2sxhuTX_bTkaeO-QhUN0bPx1Zlm1iLL8w40VJAkIZUOV-MunBA9n2Pb&amp;_nc_zt=23&amp;_nc_ht=scontent-sof1-2.xx&amp;edm=APRAPSkEAAAA&amp;_nc_gid=cghNJXfeXdX25zxTvaDPaw&amp;oh=00_Afbpm_3-a8SVNQawYhJkxdHnYjy6eYJHRr-JqXTiGVzUfw&amp;oe=68E3656E" /></item></channel></rss>