<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>True Crime Recaps Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/2722876767739321</link><description>True Crime Recaps Page</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 21:00:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1531672444680871my</guid><title>The Cruel Case of Channon Christian &amp; Christopher Newsom</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1531672444680871/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In January 2007 in Knoxville, Tennessee, Channon Christian (21) and Christopher Newsom (23) were abducted during a carjacking and taken to a house where they were tortured and murdered. Multiple assailants were convicted, and the case led to legislative changes in Tennessee as the victims’ families continue seeking justice and healing.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1531672444680871.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1531672444680871.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="630"><media:title>The Cruel Case of Channon Christian &amp; Christopher Newsom</media:title><media:description>In January 2007 in Knoxville, Tennessee, Channon Christian (21) and Christopher Newsom (23) were abducted during a carjacking and taken to a house where they were tortured and murdered. Multiple assailants were convicted, and the case led to legislative changes in Tennessee as the victims’ families continue seeking justice and healing.</media:description><media:credit>True Crime Recaps Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">788005340668847my</guid><title>When Teen’s Cry for Help Was Ignored, Tragedy Struck!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/788005340668847/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Authorities say multiple warning signs were missed before a deadly school event in Michigan shocked the nation. Despite teachers reporting concerning behavior, no action was taken until it was too late. The case has since sparked major conversations about accountability, prevention, and mental health awareness.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/788005340668847.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1340356574457592my</guid><title>Alabama’s Black Widow Poisoned Those Closest to Her For Sympathy</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1340356574457592/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Rhonda Belle Martin was executed in 1957 in Alabama for the 1951 poisoning of her fourth husband. She had previously confessed to killing her mother, two husbands, and three of her children using rat poison. The case revealed the disturbing nature of her crimes and remains one of the most notorious in U.S. history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1340356574457592.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1225412769619094my</guid><title>Johnny Gosch - One Of The Strangest Cases In History</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1225412769619094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On September 5, 1982, 12-year-old paperboy Johnny Gosch vanished during his route in West Des Moines, Iowa. No arrests were ever made. His case led to major changes in missing-child policy and remains unresolved more than four decades later.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1225412769619094.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1324256629011524my</guid><title>He'll Never Forget What He Saw</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1324256629011524/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Ed Gingerich made history as the first Amish man convicted for a killing after his 1993 attack on his wife Katie in Pennsylvania. Later diagnosed with severe mental illness, the case exposed cracks in how his community handled warning signs. Gingerich died by suicide in 2011, leaving behind a legacy of trauma and unanswered questions.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1324256629011524.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1369244954657699my</guid><title>Christa Pike: She Made History</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1369244954657699/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>At just 18 years old, Christa Gail Pike became the youngest woman sentenced to death in the U.S. after being convicted for the 1995 torture-murder of her classmate. She remains the only woman on death row in Tennessee, and under appeal, her execution date has been set for September 30, 2026.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1369244954657699.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1805136316760341my</guid><title>Harmless Ding-Dong Ditch Prank Went Horribly Wrong</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1805136316760341/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>While playing a common door-bell prank known as ding-dong-ditch in a Houston neighborhood, 11-year-old Julian Guzman was fatally shot after knocking on a house and running away. A 42-year-old man has been arrested, and authorities say the incident does not appear to be self-defense.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/thumb_1805136316760341.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4254769981468593my</guid><title>The Unsettling Story Of A Citizen's Arrest</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4254769981468593/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In May 2019, 62-year-old Kenneth Herring left a crash scene in Georgia when 25-year-old Hannah Payne pursued him, confronted him, and ultimately fatally shot him. Payne claimed self-defense; a jury later convicted her of malice murder, felony murder, aggravated assault, false imprisonment, and weapons charges. The case has drawn attention to vigilantism and racial justice issues.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/4254769981468593.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">793871656761088my</guid><title>Father Makes His Six-Year-Old Son Run On Treadmill Until The End</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/793871656761088/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Six-year-old Corey Micciolo was forced by his father to run on a treadmill while the speed kept increasing, a moment captured on video. Weeks later the boy died and his father was convicted of aggravated manslaughter and child endangerment.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/793871656761088.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1514896529790290my</guid><title>Two Decades of Waiting for Justice in Megan McDonald's Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1514896529790290/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2003, 20 year old Megan McDonald was found bludgeoned to death near Wallkill, New York. More than 22 years later, the accused Edward Holley is set for a retrial after a mistrial, while newly submitted DNA evidence and allegations of prosecutorial conflict have shaken the case’s foundation.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1514896529790290.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1711036392925939my</guid><title>A Million-Dollar Home and a Scene Straight From a Horror Film</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1711036392925939/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In May 2014, elderly couple Russell and Shirley Dermond were found murdered in their upscale lakefront home in Georgia — Russell decapitated in the garage, Shirley found tied to cinder blocks in the lake days later. Their bodies lay in a pristine million-dollar home with no apparent robbery or forced entry, and nearly a decade later the case remains unsolved.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1711036392925939.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1819111398699733my</guid><title>This Case Just Kept Getting More Unbelievable</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1819111398699733/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2011, Philadelphia teacher Ellen Greenberg was found dead with over 20 stab wounds, yet authorities ruled her death a suicide. Her parents have long challenged this finding and continue to seek answers as controversy persists over how her case was handled.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1819111398699733.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2001485447254576my</guid><title>She Lost Her Twin and Married the Man Accused of Killing Her</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2001485447254576/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On July 16 2010, 19-year-old Johana Casas was found shot dead outside Pico Truncado in Argentina. A local court later convicted her ex-boyfriend of the killing. Years later, Johana’s twin sister Edith married the convicted man, a move that sparked outrage and raised questions about loyalty, grief, and justice</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2001485447254576.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1479539886425590my</guid><title>Professor Snaps During Faculty Meeting After Being Denied Tenure</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1479539886425590/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A university professor’s frustration over a denied tenure decision escalated into tragedy during a faculty meeting. The incident shocked the academic community and raised questions about stress, pressure, and mental health in higher education.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1479539886425590.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1377743337043969my</guid><title>Father Throws His Two Kids off the Balcony for His Mistress!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1377743337043969/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Zhang Bo and his girlfriend Ye Chengchen were executed in January 2024 for the fatal 2020 murder of his 2-year-old daughter and 1-year-old son in Chongqing. The children were thrown from the 15th floor. Prosecutors said Ye pressured Zhang to kill them so they wouldn’t stand in the way of his new relationship.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1377743337043969.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1108700611427741my</guid><title>The Fatal Hit-and-Run by a Wealthy Socialite</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1108700611427741/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Rebecca Grossman was convicted of two counts of second-degree murder, gross vehicular manslaughter, and hit-and-run after her Mercedes struck brothers Mark (11) and Jacob (8) Iskander in a marked crosswalk in Westlake Village in 2020. Key evidence: her car’s data showed speeds up to 81 mph in a 45-mph zone. In June 2024, she was sentenced to 15 years-to-life in prison.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1108700611427741.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2198914894275155my</guid><title>The Lies and Deceit of Pam Hupp!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2198914894275155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Before being convicted of a 2016 murder, Pam Hupp repeatedly gave false stories and changed her accounts in investigations. Prosecutors allege she killed her friend Betsy Faria to collect life insurance and framed others in the process. Despite long legal battles, she remains in prison and now faces fresh charges in Faria’s death, with authorities seeking the death penalty.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2198914894275155.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1516427106223043my</guid><title>When Reality Becomes Unbelievable: The Bizarre Case of Lacey Fletcher</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1516427106223043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2022, 36-year-old Lacey Fletcher was found in devastating conditions inside her parents’ Louisiana home. Investigators later determined she had been left without proper care for years, despite clear signs she needed help. Her parents, Clay and Sheila Fletcher, were held accountable for extreme neglect. The case has since sparked national outrage</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1516427106223043.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1165563025512724my</guid><title>The Dark Legacy of the Cremation King of California</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1165563025512724/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What started as a trusted family business turned into one of California’s most disturbing scandals. The “Cremation King,” once known for his success in the funeral industry, was hiding a horrifying secret behind closed doors. When investigators uncovered what was really happening at his facilities, it exposed years of deceit, greed, and unimaginable neglect — leaving families to wonder what truly happened to their loved ones.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1165563025512724.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">833726855756477my</guid><title>The Man Who Helped Carry Her Casket Is Now Charged With Her Demise</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/833726855756477/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Decades after carrying Karen Snider’s casket, a former pallbearer has been arrested and charged with her 1966 murder, following new DNA evidence linking him to the crime.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/833726855756477.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>