<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>True Crime Recaps Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/2722876767739321</link><description>True Crime Recaps Page</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:00:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">830580633363093nz</guid><title>Debunking the Outlandish Internet Rumor About Garth Brooks</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/830580633363093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Online rumors have circulated making serious claims about singer Garth Brooks without evidence. No criminal charges or verified investigations support these allegations. Authorities have not confirmed any wrongdoing. The situation matters as misinformation can spread quickly and cause reputational harm without factual basis.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/830580633363093.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/830580633363093.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="639"><media:title>Debunking the Outlandish Internet Rumor About Garth Brooks</media:title><media:description>Online rumors have circulated making serious claims about singer Garth Brooks without evidence. No criminal charges or verified investigations support these allegations. Authorities have not confirmed any wrongdoing. The situation matters as misinformation can spread quickly and cause reputational harm without factual basis.</media:description><media:credit>True Crime Recaps Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1197838275890650nz</guid><title>The Disappearance of Ana Walshe and the Case Against Brian Walshe</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1197838275890650/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In January 2023 Ana Walshe was reported missing from her home in Cohasset Massachusetts. Prosecutors allege her husband Brian Walshe misled investigators and later charged him in connection with her death. The case underscores how digital evidence and timelines shape modern missing person investigations.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1197838275890650.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2072139933579506nz</guid><title>Single Mom With a Secret Double Life</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2072139933579506/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Single Mom With a Secret Double Life</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/thumb_2072139933579506.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2273925463086191nz</guid><title>The Mysterious Case of Anni Dewani</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2273925463086191/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In November 2010 Anni Dewani died after a taxi hijacking in Cape Town while on her honeymoon with husband Shrien Dewani. Authorities later charged Shrien in connection with the incident though he was acquitted in 2014. The case drew global attention to criminal investigations involving foreign nationals and cross border justice.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2273925463086191.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1227315832827179nz</guid><title>A Dark Secret Unveiled: The Larry and Bianca Rudolph Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1227315832827179/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Bianca Rudolph died during a hunting trip in Zambia in 2016 after a gun discharged. Her husband Larry Rudolph reported it as an accident. Years later US investigators charged him and he was convicted. The case matters for how international deaths are reviewed and prosecuted.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1227315832827179.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">855209484089154nz</guid><title>Dad Left His 18-Month-Old Son With Girlfriend and She Did the Unthinkable</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/855209484089154/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In March 2023 eighteen month old Trinity Poague was left in the care of her father’s girlfriend while at a home in West Virginia. Authorities later determined the child suffered fatal injuries while alone with the woman. The case raised serious concerns about child safety and caregiver responsibility.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/855209484089154.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1621237092390129nz</guid><title>Monique Tepe's Ex-Husband Drove Hundreds of Miles to End Their Lives</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1621237092390129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Investigators said Monique Tepes ex husband drove hundreds of miles before the crime, raising questions about planning and intent.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1621237092390129.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1376744174203897nz</guid><title>What Did Kenneth Smith Do to Face the Ultimate Penalty?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1376744174203897/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Kenneth Smith was convicted for his role in the 1988 killing of Elizabeth Sennett in Colbert County, Alabama. Prosecutors said Smith was hired as part of a plot connected to Sennett’s husband, who later died before trial. Smith was found guilty of capital murder based on evidence presented in court.

During the trial, the jury recommended a sentence of life in prison without parole. However, the presiding judge overrode that recommendation, a practice allowed under Alabama law at the time, and imposed a death sentence instead. Smith’s conviction and sentence were upheld through multiple appeals over the following decades.

Smith’s case drew renewed attention due to legal challenges related to the method of execution and changes in state procedures. Courts reviewed those challenges while maintaining the validity of his conviction and sentence under existing law.

After years of litigation, Alabama officials moved forward with carrying out the sentence. Smith’s case became one of the most closely watched capital punishment cases in the state, highlighting ongoing legal and procedural debates surrounding death penalty enforcement.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1376744174203897.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">884686237618850nz</guid><title>A Horrid Case: The Cruelest Kids Ever?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/884686237618850/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A Horrid Case: The Cruelest Kids Ever?</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/thumb_884686237618850.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2045016342945421nz</guid><title>Justice or Cover-Up: The Heartbreaking Case Of Sean Daugherty</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2045016342945421/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In April 2022, 12 year old Sean Daugherty was found dead in the backyard of his home in Yorktown, Virginia. Authorities stated that after reviewing the scene, evidence, and medical examiner findings, the death was classified as a suicide. Sean was a middle school student and had been home earlier that day before he was discovered.

Sean’s family has publicly challenged the official determination, expressing concerns about the timeline and circumstances surrounding his death. They have called for the case to be reexamined, stating they believe key questions remain unanswered. Their concerns have drawn public attention to the case.

Local law enforcement has maintained that the investigation was conducted according to standard procedures. Officials have stated that all available evidence was reviewed and that the conclusion reached was supported by investigative findings. Authorities have also said that some claims circulating publicly do not align with the case record.

As of the latest updates, no criminal charges have been filed, and the manner of death has not been changed. The case has not been formally reopened, and the official classification remains in place while the family continues to seek further review.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2045016342945421.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">774359339011029nz</guid><title>Famous Model Abby Choi and Her Gruesome End!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/774359339011029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In February 2023, Hong Kong model and influencer Abby Choi was reported missing after she failed to pick up her child from school. Authorities later confirmed she had been killed, and the case was classified as a homicide following discoveries made during the police investigation.

Law enforcement arrested several individuals connected to Choi, including her former husband, his father, and his brother, who were charged with murder. Her former mother in law was charged with obstructing justice. Police stated the investigation focused on financial disputes linked to Choi and her former in laws.

Searches conducted by authorities led to the recovery of some of Choi’s remains at a rural property in the Tai Po district. Officials confirmed that not all remains were recovered, and the investigation continued as evidence was processed and reviewed.

The accused were held in custody as legal proceedings moved forward. As of the latest updates, no final verdicts had been announced, and the case remains under the jurisdiction of the Hong Kong courts.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/774359339011029.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1432221098332728nz</guid><title>Berry Bryant Thought She Was Safe on Campus Until She Met Levi Collen</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1432221098332728/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Berry Grace Bryant was a first year college student at Truman State University in Missouri when she was reported missing in January 2020 after failing to return to her residence hall. Her disappearance prompted a multi-agency search involving campus police and county authorities. Investigators later located her body off-campus, and a medical examiner confirmed she had been killed.

Law enforcement arrested 22-year-old Levi Collen in connection with Bryant’s death. Prosecutors stated that evidence collected from surveillance footage, digital records, and witness information linked Collen to the area where Bryant was last seen and to the crime itself. Collen was not a student at the university but had been seen in the vicinity around the time Bryant disappeared.

In court Collen was charged with first degree murder and other related offenses. Prosecutors argued the evidence showed intentional causation of Bryant’s death. The defense did not dispute certain factual elements but raised questions about aspects of the investigation. A jury later found Collen guilty on the murder charge.

Collen was sentenced under Missouri law to a term reflecting the severity of the crime. Authorities stated the conviction brought legal resolution to the homicide, and no additional suspects have been publicly identified in connection with Bryant’s death.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1432221098332728.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4352437204991685nz</guid><title>The Cruelest Mother Ever: Mitchelle Blair</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4352437204991685/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2015, police in Detroit discovered the bodies of two children concealed inside a freezer at an apartment complex. The children were identified as siblings who had previously lived in the residence. The discovery followed an investigation into neglect and unsafe living conditions involving the family.  Mitchelle Blair, the children’s mother, was arrested and later charged in connection with their deaths. Prosecutors stated that the children had died years earlier and that their deaths were concealed. The case involved extensive review of housing records, prior child welfare contacts, and medical findings.  In 2019, Blair pleaded guilty to multiple charges, including first degree murder and child abuse. During court proceedings, she admitted responsibility for the deaths. The court accepted the plea, concluding the case without a trial.  Blair was sentenced to life in prison without the possibility of parole. Authorities stated the case underscored failures in oversight and prompted reviews of child welfare response procedures in the city.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/4352437204991685.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3819997308302217nz</guid><title>She Was Found At The School Bathroom - Ta'ir Rada</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3819997308302217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In December 2006, thirteen year old Ta ir Rada was found dead inside a bathroom at her school in Katzrin, Israel. The discovery prompted a nationwide investigation and intense public attention. Authorities confirmed she had been killed while still on school grounds.  In 2010, Roman Zadorov, an immigrant from Ukraine who worked as a contractor at the school, was convicted of murder based largely on a confession and circumstantial evidence. He was sentenced to life in prison. From the outset, the case generated controversy, with questions raised about the investigation and the reliability of the confession.  Over the years, legal appeals and new forensic reviews led to growing doubt about the conviction. In 2021, Israel’s Supreme Court ordered a retrial, citing issues with the original proceedings and evidence. In 2023, Zadorov was acquitted after the court ruled the prosecution had not proven guilt beyond a reasonable doubt.  The case remains one of the most debated criminal investigations in Israel’s history. Authorities have stated that Ta ir Rada’s killing is still unresolved, and no alternative suspect has been formally charged.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/3819997308302217.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2327280164401336nz</guid><title>Thought DNA Would Be Used To Clone Him?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2327280164401336/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Lisa Ziegert was a 24 year old clothing store manager who was abducted after closing a shop in Agawam, Massachusetts, in December 1992. Her body was found days later in a wooded area near her workplace. The case remained unsolved for more than two decades despite extensive investigation.  In 2017, Gary Schara was arrested and charged with murder after advances in DNA testing linked him to the crime. Prosecutors stated that forensic evidence connected him to Ziegert and the scene. Schara pleaded not guilty and the case proceeded to trial.  In 2019, a jury convicted Schara of first degree murder. He was sentenced to life in prison without the possibility of parole. Authorities stated the conviction brought long awaited resolution to a case that had deeply affected the local community.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2327280164401336.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1623272832417396nz</guid><title>Betrayed by His Family</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1623272832417396/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In June 2021, Maggie Murdaugh and her son Paul were found shot to death at the family’s rural property in Colleton County, South Carolina. Their husband and father, Alex Murdaugh, reported discovering the bodies and initially denied involvement. The case drew national attention due to the family’s long standing legal influence in the region.  In March 2023, Alex Murdaugh was convicted of two counts of murder following a jury trial. Prosecutors presented evidence placing him at the crime scene shortly before the killings, including video recordings and digital data. The defense argued the evidence was circumstantial, but jurors returned guilty verdicts after deliberation.  Murdaugh was sentenced to two consecutive life sentences without the possibility of parole. The court found the crimes were motivated by mounting financial pressure and exposure of extensive financial misconduct. Separate civil lawsuits related to those financial matters remain active.  Since the conviction, Murdaugh has filed appeals seeking a new trial, citing alleged issues with jury conduct and trial procedure. As of now, the convictions stand, and he remains incarcerated while the appeals process continues.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1623272832417396.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">857796100481245nz</guid><title>She Was Only 13 Years Old! - Tabitha Tuders</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/857796100481245/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On April 29, 2003, 13 year old Tabitha Tuders left her home in Nashville, Tennessee to walk to her school bus stop. She never made it to school and was never seen again.  Tabitha was described as a quiet, kind hearted girl who loved music and art. That morning, multiple witnesses reported seeing her walking alone, but after that, she seemed to vanish without a trace. No confirmed sightings were ever reported after she reached the area near her middle school.  The case immediately raised concerns about foul play, but investigators struggled with a lack of physical evidence. Over the years, several persons of interest were questioned, including a known offender who lived nearby, yet no charges were ever filed. Searches, tips, and renewed investigations have all failed to bring definitive answers.  More than two decades later, Tabitha Tuders remains missing. Her case continues to haunt her family and community, serving as a painful reminder of how quickly a life can disappear and how long the search for truth can last.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/857796100481245.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1110133397757148nz</guid><title>Insane Case of Billy Payne &amp; Billie Jean Hayworth</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1110133397757148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In March 2012, Billy Payne and Billie Jean Hayworth were found dead inside their home in Union County, Tennessee. The discovery came after a family member went to check on them and alerted authorities, launching a homicide investigation in the rural community.  Early in the case, attention turned toward members of the couple’s extended family. Investigators uncovered evidence suggesting a dispute involving money and control over property, which helped narrow the focus of the inquiry as more details emerged.  Prosecutors ultimately charged Payne’s cousin, Chris Newsom, and his girlfriend, Amber Bowman, in connection with the killings. Court records showed that the case relied heavily on forensic evidence and testimony gathered during the investigation.  In 2014, both defendants were convicted and sentenced to life in prison without the possibility of parole. The case brought long awaited answers to the victims’ families and remains one of the most widely discussed criminal cases in eastern Tennessee history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1110133397757148.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1420776726383003nz</guid><title>Bruce McArthur's Chilling Double Life</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1420776726383003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Bruce McArthur was a self employed landscaper in Toronto who worked for years in affluent neighborhoods and had long standing ties to the city’s Gay Village. To many clients and acquaintances, he appeared dependable and unremarkable, blending easily into everyday life.  Between 2010 and 2017, several men connected to Toronto’s LGBTQ community were reported missing. For years, the disappearances were treated as unrelated, and families struggled with limited answers as the cases remained unresolved.  In 2018, investigators arrested McArthur and later uncovered evidence linking him to multiple deaths. In 2019, he pleaded guilty to eight counts of murder, bringing long awaited confirmation to families who had spent years searching for loved ones.  The case led to widespread review of police procedures, particularly around missing persons investigations involving marginalized communities. It remains one of the most significant criminal cases in Canadian history and continues to shape conversations about trust, visibility, and accountability.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1420776726383003.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">903145285708167nz</guid><title>He'll NEVER Forget What He Saw</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/903145285708167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2016, the death of sixteen year old Emma Stutzman inside her Amish family’s Ohio home initially appeared to be a medical emergency. She was found unresponsive, and early explanations offered to authorities did not immediately raise suspicion beyond a sudden illness.  As investigators reviewed the circumstances more closely, inconsistencies began to emerge. The county coroner later ruled Emma’s death a homicide, prompting a deeper investigation that focused on someone within her immediate family and community.  Authorities identified her older brother, Eli Stutzman, as the person responsible for her death. Before the case could proceed through the court system, officials confirmed that Eli died shortly after being named as the suspect, bringing the criminal investigation to an abrupt end.  The case drew national attention due to its setting within a traditionally private Amish community and raised difficult questions about oversight, reporting, and justice in insular societies. Emma Stutzman’s death remains a deeply painful chapter for those who knew her.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/903145285708167.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>