<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>True Crime Recaps Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/2722876767739321</link><description>True Crime Recaps Page</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:00:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1623956098573035ph</guid><title>The Horrifying Secrets of Robert Pickton's Pig Farm</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1623956098573035/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Robert Pickton was a Canadian pig farmer whose property in Port Coquitlam British Columbia became the focus of a major police investigation in the early 2000s. Authorities began examining the farm after years of reports involving missing women many of whom were last seen in the Vancouver area.  In 2002 police executed a search warrant on Pickton’s property following allegations unrelated to homicide. During that search investigators uncovered evidence that led them to believe the farm was connected to multiple disappearances. The findings prompted one of the largest and most complex investigations in Canadian history.  Pickton was later charged and convicted in connection with the deaths of several women based on forensic evidence witness testimony and his own statements introduced at trial. Prosecutors argued that the crimes occurred over an extended period while Pickton lived a largely unnoticed life.  The case raised serious questions about how vulnerable people are protected and how long patterns of violence can go undetected. Pickton was sentenced to life in prison and the investigation led to public inquiries into police response and systemic failures surrounding missing persons cases in Canada.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1623956098573035.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1623956098573035.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="659"><media:title>The Horrifying Secrets of Robert Pickton's Pig Farm</media:title><media:description>Robert Pickton was a Canadian pig farmer whose property in Port Coquitlam British Columbia became the focus of a major police investigation in the early 2000s. Authorities began examining the farm after years of reports involving missing women many of whom were last seen in the Vancouver area.  In 2002 police executed a search warrant on Pickton’s property following allegations unrelated to homicide. During that search investigators uncovered evidence that led them to believe the farm was connected to multiple disappearances. The findings prompted one of the largest and most complex investigations in Canadian history.  Pickton was later charged and convicted in connection with the deaths of several women based on forensic evidence witness testimony and his own statements introduced at trial. Prosecutors argued that the crimes occurred over an extended period while Pickton lived a largely unnoticed life.  The case raised serious questions about how vulnerable people are protected and how long patterns of violence can go undetected. Pickton was sentenced to life in prison and the investigation led to public inquiries into police response and systemic failures surrounding missing persons cases in Canada.</media:description><media:credit>True Crime Recaps Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">869433488868180ph</guid><title>John Lennon's Life Cut Short By CRAZED Fan</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/869433488868180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On the night of December 8, 1980, John Lennon returned home to the Dakota building in Manhattan after a recording session with Yoko Ono. As the couple approached their entrance, a man who had been waiting outside stepped forward and opened fire. Lennon was rushed to Roosevelt Hospital, but doctors were unable to save him. His death was confirmed within minutes of arrival.  The attacker was Mark David Chapman, a fan who had traveled from Hawaii to confront Lennon. Throughout the day, he lingered outside the Dakota, even having Lennon sign an album hours before the shooting. Chapman remained at the scene afterward, reading a book until police arrested him without resistance. He later admitted to planning the act in advance, and he was ultimately convicted and sentenced to 20 years to life.  The news of Lennon’s death spread instantly, prompting an outpouring of grief around the world. Fans gathered outside hospitals, radio stations played Beatles and solo songs nonstop, and global memorials formed in the days that followed. Lennon had just reentered the music scene with a new album, leaving many to wonder what artistic chapters had been cut short.  More than four decades later, the case remains one of the most talked-about tragedies in music history. It changed how the public viewed celebrity safety, and it highlighted the dangers of obsessive behavior toward public figures. Lennon’s legacy continues through his music, his activism, and the cultural impact he left behind.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/869433488868180.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1545276533183663ph</guid><title>What Really Happened in Anna Kepner’s Stateroom on that Cruise Ship?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1545276533183663/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>18-year-old Anna Kepner was found unresponsive inside a stateroom aboard the Carnival Horizon during a family cruise. According to investigators, Anna had suffered fatal head trauma, and evidence in the room led authorities to identify a suspect who was later charged in connection with her death. The case raised serious concerns about onboard safety procedures and how incidents at sea are handled by law enforcement agencies.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1545276533183663.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3755451674764425ph</guid><title>The Chilling Story Of The Lady In The Dunes</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3755451674764425/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>For nearly 50 years, investigators struggled to identify the woman found in the dunes of Provincetown, Massachusetts in 1974. Known only as the “Lady in the Dunes,” her case became one of America’s most haunting cold mysteries. In 2022, advanced genetic genealogy finally revealed her name: Ruth Marie Terry. The breakthrough reopened long-buried questions about her life, her final days, and who may have been responsible for her death.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/3755451674764425.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">863400879494455ph</guid><title>The Story Behind 'Take Care of Maya'</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/863400879494455/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>When 10-year-old Maya Kowalski was hospitalized in Florida, her family’s fight to get her proper medical care spiraled into a legal crisis that none of them expected. Doctors questioned her rare illness, the state intervened, and Maya was kept from her parents for months. The ordeal, later documented in Take Care of Maya, revealed a complex battle between medical authority and parental rights that still raises difficult questions today.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/863400879494455.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">893631806440159ph</guid><title>People Are Still Confused By This At Sea Mystery</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/893631806440159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 1998, 23-year-old Amy Lynn Bradley vanished from a Royal Caribbean cruise ship while traveling with her family near Curaçao. Despite extensive searches, reported sightings, and years of investigation, no confirmed answers have ever emerged. Amy’s disappearance remains one of the most puzzling maritime mysteries, leaving her family and the public still searching for clarity decades later.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/893631806440159.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">630689376799845ph</guid><title>essie Blodgett Didn't Realize Her So-Called Friend Would Betray Her in an Unthinkable Way</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/630689376799845/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2013, nineteen year old musician and actress Jessie Blodgett was found dead in her Wisconsin home the morning after a theater performance. Detectives soon uncovered evidence pointing to someone shockingly close to her life, her friend Daniel Bartelt. Surveillance footage, forensic findings and his own violent attack on another woman led investigators directly to him. Bartelt was convicted and sentenced to life in prison. Jessies case remains a heartbreaking reminder that danger can come from the people we least expect.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/630689376799845.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1189181426498074ph</guid><title>The SECRET CULT of Xavier Dupont de Ligonnès</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1189181426498074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2011, Xavier Dupont de Ligonnès vanished after his wife and four children were found buried under the family home in Nantes, France. Investigators uncovered financial collapse, hidden debt, and Xavier’s growing involvement in fringe religious groups, fueling theories about secret beliefs, extremist influence, and a possible planned disappearance. Despite an international manhunt, Xavier has never been found, and the mystery surrounding his final days continues to raise questions about what he believed, who he trusted, and how he disappeared without a trace.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1189181426498074.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">717700447562716ph</guid><title>Not a Single Car Stopped While She Was Running for Her Life on a Busy Highway</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/717700447562716/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In the early 1970s, three young girls from the Rochester, New York area were abducted and killed, each sharing matching initials in both their first and last names — a pattern that earned the murders national attention as the “Alphabet Murders.” Despite large-scale searches, interviews and multiple suspects over the decades, no one has ever been charged. The case remains unsolved, with investigators still unsure whether the pattern was intentional or a disturbing coincidenc</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/717700447562716.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1249233650381242ph</guid><title>The SUSPICIOUS Nurse Case </title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1249233650381242/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Lucy Letby, a neonatal nurse in the U.K., was convicted in 2023 of murdering and harming infants under her care at the Countess of Chester Hospital. Prosecutors described a pattern of unexplained collapses, concerning medical notes and altered records that pointed to deliberate actions. Letby has maintained her innocence and is appealing her convictions, while independent reviews continue examining hospital procedures and oversight. The case has become one of the most closely scrutinized medical crime investigations in recent British history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1249233650381242.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">692291350606213ph</guid><title>Levi King Went on a Rampage and Destroyed Families Just To Feel Something</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/692291350606213/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2005, Levi King crossed through Missouri and Texas on a violent spree that left multiple victims dead within a matter of hours. Investigators later revealed King had stolen weapons, broken into homes and attacked complete strangers with no personal motive, describing his actions as driven by impulse and emotional detachment. He was later captured in El Paso, confessed to the killings and received multiple life sentences. The case remains a chilling example of how a single night of unchecked violence shattered several families forever.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/thumb_692291350606213.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1362400595333795ph</guid><title>Larry Hall: Was It Fact Or Fantasy?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1362400595333795/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Larry Hall, a quiet cemetery worker from Indiana, confessed to dozens of kidnappings and murders across several states, but investigators struggled to separate truth from imagination. Some details matched real disappearances, while others shifted each time he retold them. Hall was ultimately convicted in 1995 for the abduction of Jessica Roach, yet many believe he may have far more victims than confirmed. To this day, the line between what Hall actually did and what he fabricated remains one of the most debated mysteries in modern true crime.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1362400595333795.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3129016023936066ph</guid><title>My Friend Plotted To Take My Unborn Baby!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3129016023936066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2011, pregnant teen Angelique Robledo invited another “pregnant” teen, Kassandra Toruga, into her home, unaware Toruga was faking her pregnancy. A fire broke out in Angelique’s room, and a hidden bag containing knives was found. Police later confirmed Toruga planned to harm Angelique and take her baby. Toruga was committed for treatment, and Angelique survived, later sharing her story to raise awareness about fetal-abduction dangers.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/3129016023936066.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2720042045009990ph</guid><title>Meet the Roofman Robbed Fast-Food Joints and Lived Above a Toys “R” Us</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2720042045009990/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Jeffrey Allen Manchester, known as the Roofman, carried out a string of fast food robberies across multiple states in the 1990s and early 2000s. After escaping from a North Carolina prison in 2004, he hid inside an abandoned Toys “R” Us in Charlotte, secretly living in the building for months while planning additional robberies. He was eventually captured after being recognized at a nearby gym, ending one of the most unusual fugitive stories in recent criminal history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/2720042045009990.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1867708740525476ph</guid><title>Nobody Could Explain Joan Risch's Vanishing Without a Trace</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1867708740525476/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Thirty-one-year-old Joan Risch disappeared from her home in Lincoln, Massachusetts, on October 24, 1961. Her baby was found unharmed in the house, her daughter was seen wandering outside, and the kitchen showed signs of a possible struggle with blood matching her type. Neighbors reported seeing Joan walking along the road that afternoon, but she was never found. Decades of investigation produced no confirmed sightings, no evidence of foul play, and no clear explanation for what happened, leaving her disappearance one of New England’s most enduring unsolved mysteries.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1867708740525476.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1947755219115282ph</guid><title>The Perfect Neighbor Left Out Another Disturbing Twist in the Case</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1947755219115282/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On June 2, 2023, in Ocala, Florida, Susan Lorincz shot and killed her neighbor Ajike “AJ” Owens through a locked front door after months of escalating disputes over children playing nearby. Claims of self-defense under Florida’s Stand-Your-Ground law failed to convince a jury, who found Lorincz guilty of manslaughter and sentenced her to 25 years. The crime is now the focus of the Netflix documentary The Perfect Neighbor, which uses body-cam footage to examine the breakdown of community, race and self-defense.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1947755219115282.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1625682778598459ph</guid><title>He Ended The Life Of His Pregnant Girlfriend</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1625682778598459/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>He Ended The Life Of His Pregnant Girlfriend</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/thumb_1625682778598459.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1526166095472792ph</guid><title>BIZARRE Relationship Between Mother &amp; Son</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1526166095472792/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Between 1978 and 1981, Spokane, Washington was terrorized by a man authorities later identified as Frederick “Kevin” Coe. For years, dozens of women were attacked in the same upscale neighborhood, leaving the city on edge until a series of identifications finally led investigators to Coe. The case only grew stranger as details emerged about his background, his powerful family, and his mother’s extreme attempts to defend him—even plotting retaliation against officials. Multiple trials, overturned convictions, and a landmark legal battle eventually resulted in Coe being confined as a sexually violent predator, where he remains today.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/1526166095472792.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4250513958602761ph</guid><title>The Terrifying Story Of Peter Keller</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4250513958602761/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In 2012, investigators in Washington State searched for Peter Keller after discovering that his wife and daughter had been found deceased inside the family home. As authorities pieced together his plans and movements, they uncovered a hidden bunker Keller had built deep in the woods, stocked with supplies and recording equipment. This video examines the timeline, the investigation, and how the search for Keller ultimately ended.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/4250513958602761.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">742946614724408ph</guid><title>Aileen Wuornos Was Trapped by a System That Exploited Her Trauma</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/742946614724408/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Aileen Wuornos is often remembered only for the crimes she was convicted of, but her life story shows a long pattern of instability, abuse, and poverty that began in childhood. Before her arrest in 1991, she spent years without stable housing, support, or access to meaningful help. Prosecutors, investigators, and people around her later acknowledged that her circumstances and trauma shaped nearly every part of her life. Her case raises ongoing questions about how vulnerable individuals move through systems that are not equipped to protect them, and how those gaps can lead to tragic outcomes for everyone involved.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/2722876767739321/742946614724408.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>