<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>American Veterans Center Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/198826014046</link><description>American Veterans Center Page</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:15:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4191703694430665ca</guid><title>Using My .45 Against Japanese Banzai Charge</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4191703694430665/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What happens when the enemy overwhelms your position? This powerful memoir shares a veteran's story of close-quarters combat and the desperate use of his .45 sidearm to survive a Banzai charge.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/4191703694430665.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/4191703694430665.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="31"><media:title>Using My .45 Against Japanese Banzai Charge</media:title><media:description>What happens when the enemy overwhelms your position? This powerful memoir shares a veteran's story of close-quarters combat and the desperate use of his .45 sidearm to survive a Banzai charge.</media:description><media:credit>American Veterans Center Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1879242009677304ca</guid><title>How I Survived Four Different Concentration Camps</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1879242009677304/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 22:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This powerful memoir shares a survivor's unflinching account of the Holocaust. The veteran recounts the physical hardship and mental resilience required to endure four different concentration camps.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1879242009677304.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">838747121855572ca</guid><title>It Was a Miracle I Made It Off Omaha Beach</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/838747121855572/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside the brutal reality of D-Day. This video documents a soldier's experience navigating the intense fire and obstacles on Omaha Beach, detailing the courage and luck that brought him safely off the sand.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_838747121855572.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1504003164154886ca</guid><title>They Trained For Everything, But That Was Different</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1504003164154886/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside the reality of a soldier's experience. This powerful memoir documents a time when military training was not enough, detailing the unique challenges and unexpected variables of a difficult mission.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_1504003164154886.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1236081738570915ca</guid><title>Soldiers Thought They'd Be Safe Staying in the Landing Craft</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1236081738570915/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside a high-stakes combat landing. This veteran recounts the critical, early moments of the assault and the profound, deadly shock when the soldiers realized they were exposed inside the landing craft.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_1236081738570915.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1457452972014933ca</guid><title>Courage, Sacrifice, and the Battle of the Bulge</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1457452972014933/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside one of WWII's toughest fights. Veterans share their first-hand accounts of the extreme cold and intense fighting that defined the Battle of the Bulge, revealing the profound cost of courage.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1457452972014933.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1235037818447436ca</guid><title>Flamethrower Combat on IWO JIMA with a WWII MARINE</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1235037818447436/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 22:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside the brutal reality of Iwo Jima. This Marine veteran shares his first-hand account of the terrifying moments and the critical role of flamethrowers in breaking through Japanese defenses.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1235037818447436.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">816384994539658ca</guid><title>We Were Credited With Eliminating an NVA Regiment</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/816384994539658/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was the scale of this decisive victory? This powerful memoir shares a veteran’s story of the high-stakes mission that led to their unit being credited with defeating an entire NVA Regiment in combat.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/816384994539658.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1251482143678943ca</guid><title>Meet the Psychologist Behind America's Special Forces</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1251482143678943/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 22:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Who is the psychologist shaping the elite mindset of America's toughest soldiers? This video explores the rigorous selection, mental conditioning, and psychological strategies behind the training of Special Forces.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1251482143678943.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">803899272528353ca</guid><title>Nightfall in Vietnam: Choosing to Dig In for the Night</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/803899272528353/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside the psychological reality of combat. This video documents a veteran’s experience, detailing the courage and planning required to secure a position and dig in for the night during the Vietnam War.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/803899272528353.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4219630278292875ca</guid><title>My First Steps On Omaha Beach on D-Day</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/4219630278292875/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was it like to take the first steps on Omaha Beach? This veteran shares his powerful, first-hand account of the landing, detailing the intense fire and courage required during the initial moments of D-Day.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/4219630278292875.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1557308815403274ca</guid><title>The Fighting Conditions We Faced in the Pacific</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1557308815403274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was it truly like to fight in the Pacific theater of WWII? This video shares a veteran's powerful, first-hand account of the brutal fighting conditions, detailing the heat, terrain, and challenges faced by soldiers.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1557308815403274.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2019547371783491ca</guid><title>An Easy Company actor reflects on the epic series.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/2019547371783491/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Ross McCall, who portrayed Easy Company veteran Joseph Liebgott in HBO’s epic miniseries ‘Band of Brothers’ explains what it meant to be apart of the series.

On November 7 &amp; 8 in Washington, DC, AVC will bring together nearly FORTY living heroes of World War II - plus legends of the last 80 years of history - and you can see it all for FREE!

From D-Day to Iwo Jima. Chosin Reservoir to Ia Drang. The famed ODA 595 ‘Horse Soldiers’ to U.S. Navy SEALs. The AVC’s 28th Annual American Valor Heroes &amp; Legends Conference brings together the greatest living stories of American history, all to share their stories and lessons in a one of a kind Veterans Day special event.

And YOU are invited. Join the full weekend of events, or register to attend the AVC Conference at link here: https://secure.anedot.com/american-veterans-center/avc2025dailyspeakersessions

For questions about the event or how to register, e-mail conference@avcmail.org.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_2019547371783491.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">850895817913914ca</guid><title>Blood Was Coming Out of Me Like an Oil Well</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/850895817913914/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This powerful memoir shares a veteran's unflinching account of being severely wounded in combat. He recounts the urgent fight for survival and the incredible courage required to stay alive under fire.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/850895817913914.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1463470724711110ca</guid><title>Guardians of the Skies: Aerial Triumph in Vietnam</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1463470724711110/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to secure the skies? This video documents the unflinching courage of pilots in Vietnam, detailing the advanced tactics and aerial triumph that defined their critical missions.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1463470724711110.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1229515685664229ca</guid><title>How I Prepped for "Forrest Gump" and "Apollo 13"</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1229515685664229/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go behind the scenes of two iconic films. This video shares the detailed process of how an actor prepared for their roles in 'Forrest Gump' and 'Apollo 13', detailing the research, training, and mindset required to bring those characters to life.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1229515685664229.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1948820065964182ca</guid><title>WWII Veteran Don Graves had 300 men in his company that fought on the island of Iwo Jima. Only Don and 7 other men walked off the island.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1948820065964182/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>WWII Veteran Don Graves shares his profound and somber memoir of the Battle of Iwo Jima. He recounts the brutal reality of the fighting, where only eight men from his 300-man company survived.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1948820065964182.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3731590400482409ca</guid><title>The Best Job Ever in The Marine Corps</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3731590400482409/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Every Marine has a story. This video documents a veteran's deep reflection on his specific role, explaining the unique mission and responsibility that he considers the best assignment in the entire Corps.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_3731590400482409.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2671602159850017ca</guid><title>Secrets of the Ghost Army</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2671602159850017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Who were the Ghost Army? This documentary reveals the true story of the top-secret WWII unit that used inflatable tanks, sound effects, and theatrical deception to trick the German military and save thousands of lives.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/2671602159850017.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2309745196113967ca</guid><title>Why I Cooked My Grenades Before Throwing Them</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2309745196113967/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What is the technical reason a soldier would intentionally delay a grenade? This powerful memoir shares a veteran's story, explaining the strategic necessity and the safety procedure behind this critical combat tactic.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/2309745196113967.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>