<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>American Veterans Center Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/198826014046</link><description>American Veterans Center Page</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:15:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3912227302408258ie</guid><title>A Soldier's 42-Day Story for Survival</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3912227302408258/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to survive for 42 days in a life-or-death situation? This video tells the powerful story of a soldier’s resilience and endurance in the face of impossible odds.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_3912227302408258.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/3912227302408258.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="511"><media:title>A Soldier's 42-Day Story for Survival</media:title><media:description>What does it take to survive for 42 days in a life-or-death situation? This video tells the powerful story of a soldier’s resilience and endurance in the face of impossible odds.</media:description><media:credit>American Veterans Center Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">849704970827457ie</guid><title>The Impressive Firepower on the Battleship New Jersey</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/849704970827457/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What made the USS New Jersey a naval powerhouse? This video breaks down the battleship's massive armament, detailing the size, range, and destructive power of its legendary guns.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/849704970827457.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1888622122011228ie</guid><title>I Dropped The Ramp and Machine Gun Bullets Tore Into Us</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1888622122011228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What happens when a mission instantly turns into an ambush? This powerful memoir documents a veteran’s first-hand account of dropping the ramp and facing immediate, heavy machine gun fire from the enemy.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1888622122011228.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">801176485866552ie</guid><title>We Were Exposed and Taking Fire in Fallujah</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/801176485866552/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What happens when a unit is suddenly caught in the open under attack? This powerful memoir documents a veteran’s first-hand account of being exposed and taking heavy fire during a critical mission in Fallujah.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/801176485866552.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1351694836510581ie</guid><title>The Legacy of Bull Randleman: More Than Just a Role!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1351694836510581/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go beyond the screen to the real hero. This documentary explores the powerful legacy of Sergeant William "Bull" Randleman, detailing the courage, leadership, and sacrifice that inspired his famous story.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1351694836510581.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">832047719195692ie</guid><title>"Band of Brothers" Medic Reflects on Combat in Europe</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/832047719195692/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was it like to serve as a medic with Easy Company? This powerful memoir shares a veteran's first-hand account of the profound challenges of treating wounded soldiers during intense combat across Europe.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/832047719195692.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">838279382191711ie</guid><title>WWII veteran marries at 100: the first dance.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/838279382191711/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Can you imagine getting married at 100 years old? That’s exactly what WWII Veteran Harold Terens did. We remember when both he and his wife both got to enjoy their first dance at our Annual Veterans Conference.

For the past 28 years the AVC has brought together dozens of notable veterans of the last 80 years of history for our Annual Veterans Conference, where they share their lessons and experiences with an audience of several hundred students from each of the military service academies &amp; ROTC programs from across the country. Participants range from surviving heroes of WWII to recipients of the Medal of Honor to young Special Operations veterans of today’s military. The weekend of programming concludes with American Valor: A Salute to Our Heroes, a black-tie gala filmed as a Veterans Day television special, airing on ABC, CBS, NBC and Fox stations across the country, and to all military personnel around the world on American Forces Network. We look forward to our 28th Annual Conference &amp; Gala this coming November!</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/838279382191711.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1125506529793566ie</guid><title>One Man, an Army: Medal of Honor's Daring Charge</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1125506529793566/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to charge an entire enemy position alone? This video tells the powerful, true story of a soldier's unflinching bravery and the heroic actions that earned him the Medal of Honor.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1125506529793566.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">809374165163231ie</guid><title>I Told The Medic "Don't Waste Your Time On Me!"</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/809374165163231/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What happens when a wounded soldier faces impossible odds? This powerful memoir shares a veteran's story, recounting the difficult decision he made to tell the medic to prioritize others during intense combat.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/809374165163231.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1392652738883554ie</guid><title>Ball turret gunner forced to bail out of his B-17.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1392652738883554/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>WWII Veteran Lester Schrenk joined the U.S. Army Air Forces on his 19th birthday in November 1942. He was assigned to the only open position left - a ball turret gunner on a B-17 bomber. He shares an experience where he was forced to bail out of his B-17 bomber.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1392652738883554.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1989679668482739ie</guid><title>Losing One of my Marines in Fallujah</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1989679668482739/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This powerful memoir documents the immense personal cost of the Battle of Fallujah. A veteran shares his heartfelt story of losing one of his Marines and the profound impact of that loss.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1989679668482739.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">802012119274624ie</guid><title>Marine Combat in the the Pacific’s Battle of Peleliu!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/802012119274624/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside one of the toughest battles of WWII. This video documents the unflinching courage and the sheer intensity of combat faced by Marines during the Battle of Peleliu.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/802012119274624.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">789961467242130ie</guid><title>The Legacy of Bull Randleman: More Than Just a Role!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/789961467242130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 19:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The iconic role was based on a true hero. This video shares the unfiltered story of Bull Randleman, explaining the immense impact of his service and why his name is legendary in military history.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_789961467242130.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1348027786941606ie</guid><title>What It Means to Be a Ranger in Vietnam!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1348027786941606/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside the experience of an elite soldier. This video documents the challenging missions and psychological realities faced by Army Rangers deployed during the Vietnam War.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1348027786941606.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1121333240114821ie</guid><title>Where Army Rangers Got Their Famous Motto</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1121333240114821/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What is the secret history behind the Army Rangers' famous motto? This video explores the true story of its creation, detailing the courage and spirit that inspired the legendary phrase.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1121333240114821.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1828325881895815ie</guid><title>A Holocaust survivor's daring story of survival.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1828325881895815/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Holocaust survivor Ben Lesser was born in Kraków, Poland in 1928. After the German army invaded Poland in 1939, Ben and his family were subject to countless acts of violence by Nazi soldiers and forced to live in the Bochnia Ghetto. He shared a story with us on how he hid diamonds in his shoes from Nazi soldiers.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1828325881895815.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">822257326857930ie</guid><title>Capturing the Famous "Blue Marble" Photo of Earth</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/822257326857930/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to capture a photo of our entire planet? This video goes behind the scenes of the famous "Blue Marble" photo, detailing the historic mission and the impact of the incredible image.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/822257326857930.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1507157663942793ie</guid><title>Last Living D-Day Pathfinder Pilot on the Mission That Changed the War</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1507157663942793/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 21:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside the cockpit for the mission that changed the war. The last surviving D-Day Pathfinder pilot shares his powerful, first-hand account of the crucial drop that set the stage for the Normandy invasion.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1507157663942793.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2051836558914206ie</guid><title>'Forrest Gump' Star Gary Sinise on Real Life Military Inspiration</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2051836558914206/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>The role of Lt. Dan changed his life. Gary Sinise discusses the profound impact that meeting and working with real soldiers had on his career and his later life's work as a veteran advocate</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/2051836558914206.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1909629969614986ie</guid><title>Why Navy Seal Doesn't Wear Trident</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1909629969614986/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Ever wonder why you see Navy SEALs without their Trident insignia? This video breaks down the specific reasons, covering official protocol, operational security, and the personal choice of the veteran.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1909629969614986.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>