<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>American Veterans Center Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/198826014046</link><description>American Veterans Center Page</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:16:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1557308815403274my</guid><title>The Fighting Conditions We Faced in the Pacific</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1557308815403274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was it truly like to fight in the Pacific theater of WWII? This video shares a veteran's powerful, first-hand account of the brutal fighting conditions, detailing the heat, terrain, and challenges faced by soldiers.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1557308815403274.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1557308815403274.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="53"><media:title>The Fighting Conditions We Faced in the Pacific</media:title><media:description>What was it truly like to fight in the Pacific theater of WWII? This video shares a veteran's powerful, first-hand account of the brutal fighting conditions, detailing the heat, terrain, and challenges faced by soldiers.</media:description><media:credit>American Veterans Center Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2019547371783491my</guid><title>An Easy Company actor reflects on the epic series.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/2019547371783491/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Ross McCall, who portrayed Easy Company veteran Joseph Liebgott in HBO’s epic miniseries ‘Band of Brothers’ explains what it meant to be apart of the series.

On November 7 &amp; 8 in Washington, DC, AVC will bring together nearly FORTY living heroes of World War II - plus legends of the last 80 years of history - and you can see it all for FREE!

From D-Day to Iwo Jima. Chosin Reservoir to Ia Drang. The famed ODA 595 ‘Horse Soldiers’ to U.S. Navy SEALs. The AVC’s 28th Annual American Valor Heroes &amp; Legends Conference brings together the greatest living stories of American history, all to share their stories and lessons in a one of a kind Veterans Day special event.

And YOU are invited. Join the full weekend of events, or register to attend the AVC Conference at link here: https://secure.anedot.com/american-veterans-center/avc2025dailyspeakersessions

For questions about the event or how to register, e-mail conference@avcmail.org.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_2019547371783491.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">850895817913914my</guid><title>Blood Was Coming Out of Me Like an Oil Well</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/850895817913914/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This powerful memoir shares a veteran's unflinching account of being severely wounded in combat. He recounts the urgent fight for survival and the incredible courage required to stay alive under fire.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/850895817913914.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1463470724711110my</guid><title>Guardians of the Skies: Aerial Triumph in Vietnam</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1463470724711110/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to secure the skies? This video documents the unflinching courage of pilots in Vietnam, detailing the advanced tactics and aerial triumph that defined their critical missions.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1463470724711110.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1229515685664229my</guid><title>How I Prepped for "Forrest Gump" and "Apollo 13"</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1229515685664229/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go behind the scenes of two iconic films. This video shares the detailed process of how an actor prepared for their roles in 'Forrest Gump' and 'Apollo 13', detailing the research, training, and mindset required to bring those characters to life.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1229515685664229.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1948820065964182my</guid><title>WWII Veteran Don Graves had 300 men in his company that fought on the island of Iwo Jima. Only Don and 7 other men walked off the island.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1948820065964182/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>WWII Veteran Don Graves shares his profound and somber memoir of the Battle of Iwo Jima. He recounts the brutal reality of the fighting, where only eight men from his 300-man company survived.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1948820065964182.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3731590400482409my</guid><title>The Best Job Ever in The Marine Corps</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3731590400482409/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Every Marine has a story. This video documents a veteran's deep reflection on his specific role, explaining the unique mission and responsibility that he considers the best assignment in the entire Corps.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_3731590400482409.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2671602159850017my</guid><title>Secrets of the Ghost Army</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2671602159850017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Who were the Ghost Army? This documentary reveals the true story of the top-secret WWII unit that used inflatable tanks, sound effects, and theatrical deception to trick the German military and save thousands of lives.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/2671602159850017.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2309745196113967my</guid><title>Why I Cooked My Grenades Before Throwing Them</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2309745196113967/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What is the technical reason a soldier would intentionally delay a grenade? This powerful memoir shares a veteran's story, explaining the strategic necessity and the safety procedure behind this critical combat tactic.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/2309745196113967.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1125631686307097my</guid><title>Actor Rob Riggle Tells Us About His Time in the Marine Corps</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1125631686307097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What's the story behind the uniform? Comedian and actor Rob Riggle shares his personal experience and lessons learned during his time serving in the Marine Corps, revealing a side of the actor most people don't know</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1125631686307097.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1481542909743521my</guid><title>Band of Brothers star reflects on the iconic series.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1481542909743521/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Ross McCall is a Scottish actor best known for his roles as T-5 Joseph Liebgott in the HBO miniseries ‘Band of Brothers’ and as Matthew Keller in the hit series ‘White Collar’.

In 2001 McCall would join an ensemble cast and portray Easy Company veteran Joseph Liebgott in HBO’s epic miniseries ‘Band of Brothers’. The series found immediate success and has stood the test of time as one of most pivotal and influential creative works surrounding World War II.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_1481542909743521.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1211223027644242my</guid><title>Switching From Strategic to Tactical Missions in The Air</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1211223027644242/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 02:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go inside a pivotal moment in military history. This video explains the difference between strategic and tactical air missions, and why a pilot's role might change based on the mission.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_1211223027644242.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1471670184127422my</guid><title>The Silence That Screamed an Unseen Storm</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1471670184127422/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This video explores the profound experience of intense, stressful quiet—the eerie calm before a major event or the terrifying stillness during a high-stakes moment that signals imminent danger.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1471670184127422.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3912227302408258my</guid><title>A Soldier's 42-Day Story for Survival</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/3912227302408258/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 22:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to survive for 42 days in a life-or-death situation? This video tells the powerful story of a soldier’s resilience and endurance in the face of impossible odds.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/thumb_3912227302408258.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">849704970827457my</guid><title>The Impressive Firepower on the Battleship New Jersey</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/849704970827457/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What made the USS New Jersey a naval powerhouse? This video breaks down the battleship's massive armament, detailing the size, range, and destructive power of its legendary guns.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/849704970827457.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1888622122011228my</guid><title>I Dropped The Ramp and Machine Gun Bullets Tore Into Us</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1888622122011228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What happens when a mission instantly turns into an ambush? This powerful memoir documents a veteran’s first-hand account of dropping the ramp and facing immediate, heavy machine gun fire from the enemy.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1888622122011228.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">801176485866552my</guid><title>We Were Exposed and Taking Fire in Fallujah</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/801176485866552/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What happens when a unit is suddenly caught in the open under attack? This powerful memoir documents a veteran’s first-hand account of being exposed and taking heavy fire during a critical mission in Fallujah.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/801176485866552.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1351694836510581my</guid><title>The Legacy of Bull Randleman: More Than Just a Role!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1351694836510581/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Go beyond the screen to the real hero. This documentary explores the powerful legacy of Sergeant William "Bull" Randleman, detailing the courage, leadership, and sacrifice that inspired his famous story.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1351694836510581.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">832047719195692my</guid><title>"Band of Brothers" Medic Reflects on Combat in Europe</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/832047719195692/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was it like to serve as a medic with Easy Company? This powerful memoir shares a veteran's first-hand account of the profound challenges of treating wounded soldiers during intense combat across Europe.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/832047719195692.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">838279382191711my</guid><title>WWII veteran marries at 100: the first dance.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/838279382191711/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Can you imagine getting married at 100 years old? That’s exactly what WWII Veteran Harold Terens did. We remember when both he and his wife both got to enjoy their first dance at our Annual Veterans Conference.

For the past 28 years the AVC has brought together dozens of notable veterans of the last 80 years of history for our Annual Veterans Conference, where they share their lessons and experiences with an audience of several hundred students from each of the military service academies &amp; ROTC programs from across the country. Participants range from surviving heroes of WWII to recipients of the Medal of Honor to young Special Operations veterans of today’s military. The weekend of programming concludes with American Valor: A Salute to Our Heroes, a black-tie gala filmed as a Veterans Day television special, airing on ABC, CBS, NBC and Fox stations across the country, and to all military personnel around the world on American Forces Network. We look forward to our 28th Annual Conference &amp; Gala this coming November!</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/838279382191711.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>