<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>American Veterans Center Page</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/198826014046</link><description>American Veterans Center Page</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:45:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1467900224423688us</guid><title>A Ranger explains the purpose of the Mogadishu mission.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1467900224423688/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>On this day in 1993, the Battle of Mogadishu began in Somalia and became well-known from the film Black Hawk Down. 18 U.S. soldiers were killed and 73 were left wounded after 18 hours of intense fighting. Despite the battle being viewed as a failure by the general public at the time, the mission was accomplished after they successfully arrested two members of Mohammed Farah Aidid’s clan.

Major Jeff Struecker is a former U.S. Army Ranger who took part in the 1993 Battle of Mogadishu and here he explains what the purpose of their mission was.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1467900224423688.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1467900224423688.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video" duration="57"><media:title>A Ranger explains the purpose of the Mogadishu mission.</media:title><media:description>On this day in 1993, the Battle of Mogadishu began in Somalia and became well-known from the film Black Hawk Down. 18 U.S. soldiers were killed and 73 were left wounded after 18 hours of intense fighting. Despite the battle being viewed as a failure by the general public at the time, the mission was accomplished after they successfully arrested two members of Mohammed Farah Aidid’s clan.

Major Jeff Struecker is a former U.S. Army Ranger who took part in the 1993 Battle of Mogadishu and here he explains what the purpose of their mission was.</media:description><media:credit>American Veterans Center Page</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1216235336976461us</guid><title>What I Felt The Moment I Ejected Out of my Plane</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1216235336976461/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description> In this powerful, first-hand account, a pilot shares his experience of an emergency ejection. He recounts the physical and sensory reality of the moment he was launched from his plane and the subsequent parachute landing.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1216235336976461.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1757302741590982us</guid><title>D-Day Veteran on Mines on Omaha Beach</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/1757302741590982/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What was the landing at Omaha Beach truly like? This veteran shares his powerful, first-hand account of navigating the treacherous obstacles and mines under heavy fire on D-Day.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1757302741590982.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1290265375668424us</guid><title>A WWII soldier's story of loss in Italy.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1290265375668424/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 21:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>We are saddened to hear about the passing of WWII Veteran Rocco Telese. Rocco was a combat veteran of the 85th Infantry Division who arrived in Italy late in 1943. Moving north through Italy, Rocco would experience combat along the Gustav and Gothic lines.

During the battle of Monte Bibele, Rocco would lose his entire squad and witnessed a close friend lose his life in an intense skirmish with a German soldier. May he rest in peace.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1290265375668424.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">789169320377718us</guid><title>WWII Combat Medic Jacob Ruser shares a story of one night where he was knocked unconscious by a German tank and was at one point considered dead.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/789169320377718/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this powerful account, WWII Combat Medic Jacob Ruser recounts the traumatic night he was seriously injured in a German tank attack and mistakenly believed to be a casualty.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/789169320377718.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1075557474605131us</guid><title>When Eating Pages Became a Choice in Vietnam</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/1075557474605131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does extreme deprivation do to the human spirit? This powerful memoir shares a veteran’s experience in a Vietnam POW camp, recounting the desperate choices and the extreme measures taken simply to stay alive.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://scontent-sof1-2.xx.fbcdn.net/v/t15.5256-10/393067131_664288999144278_631267667900850735_n.jpg?stp=dst-jpg_s160x160_tt6&amp;_nc_cat=103&amp;ccb=1-7&amp;_nc_sid=810293&amp;_nc_ohc=Zo_SqK2gQSQQ7kNvwEGiWXQ&amp;_nc_oc=AdluRKp-bTJMoEJgvsWFT2-_UIxiarRA825I9LJSetIPXsLNCcHdJA2or7WJe8a7azl_ma5oALeEP9mnfR26RB8x&amp;_nc_zt=23&amp;_nc_ht=scontent-sof1-2.xx&amp;edm=APRAPSkEAAAA&amp;_nc_gid=9RmtX4rTyB39vWC8IjUqfA&amp;oh=00_AfZTd2r9FrkNEfYW6W4wB-lTD7DQf5GUaJcMNp4XmnF4Kg&amp;oe=68E20B50" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1132160189010475us</guid><title>A pilot's heroic rescue of 51 men.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1132160189010475/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>During his second tour of duty in Vietnam, Major (later Major General) Patrick Henry Brady, was assigned to the 54th Medical Detachment – Helicopter Ambulance. While commanding a UH-1H ambulance helicopter, Brady flew dangerous rescue missions deep in enemy-held territory which was heavily defended and often blanketed by dense fog.

On January 6, 1968, Brady was off duty but volunteered to rescue wounded men from four sites in enemy territory. Throughout that day, Brady utilized three helicopters to evacuate a total of 51 seriously wounded men. For these actions, he was awarded the Medal of Honor.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1132160189010475.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1983019065828281us</guid><title>How We Learned to Kill the Enemy in Fallujah</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/1983019065828281/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to survive urban combat? This powerful memoir shares a soldier’s story of the intensive training and tactical discipline required to operate in the Battle of Fallujah.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1983019065828281.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1869563213592601us</guid><title>F-105 Pilot's Terrifying Escape Over Vietnam</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/1869563213592601/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to survive an emergency over enemy territory? This powerful memoir documents the high-stakes ejection of an F-105 pilot and his struggle for survival.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1869563213592601.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1284579316329122us</guid><title>The legacy of Lt. Col. George Hardy.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1284579316329122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>We’re saddened to learn that our friend, Lt. Col. George Hardy, who was the last surviving Tuskegee Airmen to fly combat missions, passed away on September 25, 2025 at the age of 100.

The Tuskegee Airmen were a group of primarily African-American military pilots and airmen who fought in World War II. Before the Tuskegee Airmen, no African American had ever been a United States military pilot.

Hardy deployed in early 1945 to Italy joining the African American 99th Fighter Squadron, 332nd Fighter Group. He flew 21 combat missions over Germany and occupied Europe piloting P-51 Mustang aircraft, often escorting heavy bombers. Following World War II, Hardy flew 45 combat missions during the Korean War as the pilot of a bomber and 70 missions piloting an AC-119K gunship during the Vietnam War.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1284579316329122.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2218335911925427us</guid><title>WWII Veteran Manny Carvalho explains the motivation in fighting behind someone like General George Patton.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2218335911925427/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 21:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>WWII Veteran Manny Carvalho explains the motivation in fighting behind someone like General George Patton.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/2218335911925427.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">836406618810818us</guid><title>We Could Smell The Camps Before We Saw Them</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/836406618810818/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This is the deeply moving story of a soldier who liberated a concentration camp. He recounts the somber reality that greeted them before they ever set foot inside the gates.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/836406618810818.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2787251478291042us</guid><title>Super Bowl Champ Injured in Intense Vietnam Battle</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/2787251478291042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>This powerful memoir shares the story of a Super Bowl champion who was wounded during an intense Vietnam battle. He recounts his injury and the courage it took to recover and return home.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/2787251478291042.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">797255369915055us</guid><title>Digging a Foxhole on a Frozen Battleground</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/797255369915055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to survive on a frozen battlefield? This powerful memoir shares a soldier’s story of the sheer physical struggle and the urgency of digging a foxhole in rock-hard, freezing ground.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://scontent-sof1-1.xx.fbcdn.net/v/t15.5256-10/555512601_794387279971508_1385742179820457426_n.jpg?stp=dst-jpg_p160x160_tt6&amp;_nc_cat=100&amp;ccb=1-7&amp;_nc_sid=810293&amp;_nc_ohc=Vc3REhOuUrAQ7kNvwFAsfWt&amp;_nc_oc=Adm0vNzQd5E4iSh-e0YZq0O-eGfqxSMqsOfMDgLf5scvuAlz2IqIO15SULaC-BSDVXQKjWOIGrNA0PS7OxZs-1sr&amp;_nc_zt=23&amp;_nc_ht=scontent-sof1-1.xx&amp;edm=APRAPSkEAAAA&amp;_nc_gid=xn8WAXt1GgiOufOdFaKW2Q&amp;oh=00_AfYYa8WdWvh1KNBZ1LQT6y0BHgVUUOEKPtKYv7YpeBMZ2w&amp;oe=68DF2A74" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1497099461594096us</guid><title>Holding Off Germans with a Grease Gun</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/1497099461594096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this powerful account, a veteran recounts a high-stakes moment in battle. He shares the story of his ingenious defense and the courage it took to face the enemy with an unconventional weapon.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1497099461594096.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1190310072929300us</guid><title>We Waited For The Enemy to Group Up and Then Hit Them</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/1190310072929300/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this powerful account, a veteran recounts a high-stakes mission. He shares the story of how his unit used precise timing and courage to successfully engage a difficult target.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1190310072929300.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">778577624883553us</guid><title>The Journey of an Air Force Ace!</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/778577624883553/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>What does it take to become an Air Force Ace? This powerful documentary traces the incredible journey of a decorated pilot, highlighting their most challenging missions and their lasting legacy.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://scontent-sof1-2.xx.fbcdn.net/v/t15.5256-10/461292631_471302289241615_7179517813928341577_n.jpg?stp=dst-jpg_p160x160_tt6&amp;_nc_cat=103&amp;ccb=1-7&amp;_nc_sid=810293&amp;_nc_ohc=f9seD8_91HgQ7kNvwEeRzpw&amp;_nc_oc=AdlQbktoenmQ6pZ3r0WfANw1s6vDSAQdrFVGoKqMbdt6Fsv2lPbdaxx-TmT_ryFWWHiMELT5ex7tTzWFFNjvOlN5&amp;_nc_zt=23&amp;_nc_ht=scontent-sof1-2.xx&amp;edm=APRAPSkEAAAA&amp;_nc_gid=Ew5SYag6oqcLWobMbFAv7w&amp;oh=00_AfZjVj-Td9hKzNP4H_cvpbUhytL9sVFiqIUIOA-g_H1FXw&amp;oe=68DCEEE3" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1374558194265949us</guid><title>Exactly How Close Is Close-Quarters Combat?</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/1374558194265949/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Ever wonder what defines "close" in close-quarters combat? This video breaks down the tactics, distances, and dynamics of CQC, explaining the high-stakes reality for soldiers and special forces.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/1374558194265949.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">2319556145169447us</guid><title>Honoring the women warriors of Special Forces.</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/reel/2319556145169447/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Remembering when the Distinguished Women Warriors of the U.S. Special Operation Forces were honored at American Valor.

For the past 28 years the AVC has brought together dozens of notable veterans of the last 80 years of history for our Annual Veterans Conference, where they share their lessons and experiences with an audience of several hundred students from each of the military service academies &amp; ROTC programs from across the country. Participants range from surviving heroes of WWII to recipients of the Medal of Honor to young Special Operations veterans of today’s military. The weekend of programming concludes with American Valor: A Salute to Our Heroes, a black-tie gala filmed as a Veterans Day television special, airing on ABC, CBS, NBC and Fox stations across the country, and to all military personnel around the world on American Forces Network. We look forward to our 28th Annual Conference &amp; Gala this coming November!</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/2319556145169447.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">793817126942091us</guid><title>I Was Knocked Unconscious When Our Chopper Crashed</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/americanveteranscenter/videos/793817126942091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A veteran recounts a moment that would change his life forever. This is the true story of a devastating chopper crash and the courage and resilience it took to survive.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/198826014046/793817126942091.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>