<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Brooke Makenna</title><link>https://www.facebook.com/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws</link><description>Brooke Makenna</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:01:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">853e7faec90f402dsg</guid><title>Airport Ride, Then She Was Gone - MacKenzie Lueck</title><link>https://facebook.com/reel/32809296982002208/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A college student vanished after landing safely at the airport. Hours later, her phone went dark - and the truth behind her final ride would leave everyone stunned.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws/853e7faec90f402d.jpg" /><media:content url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws/853e7faec90f402d.mp4" type="video/mp4" medium="video"><media:title>Airport Ride, Then She Was Gone - MacKenzie Lueck</media:title><media:description>A college student vanished after landing safely at the airport. Hours later, her phone went dark - and the truth behind her final ride would leave everyone stunned.</media:description><media:credit>Brooke Makenna</media:credit></media:content></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">38f45e961db845afsg</guid><title>Daughter Entangled In Boyfriend’s Plot Against Family</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KC69z59ISq8</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Two confessions. One truth that shattered everything. What they finally admitted would change how the entire city remembered this case.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws/38f45e961db845af.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">3ef8938d4e294d41sg</guid><title>Family Fights For Answers In Jackson Solace Case</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dhm3KluxzeM</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>Three years after 20-year-old Jackson Solace was found in a San Francisco high-rise, his loved ones say they still have more questions than answers. In this video, I walk through the timeline of his final night, the official findings, and why his family believes the response from authorities fell short. Together we talk about bias, accountability, and how you can support their call for a full, transparent review of his case.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws/3ef8938d4e294d41.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">98ae2a45af67499dsg</guid><title>The 5-Year-Old Who Vanished and Grew Up Beside Her Captor</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2hDmxShjxqI</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In this video, I explore the life of Suzanne, a little girl taken at five and forced to grow up under a false identity beside the man who took her. Decades later, that same man reappears under new names, a young mother is found on a roadside, and a six-year-old boy disappears from his classroom. Together we follow the investigations that finally uncover who Suzanne really was, what happened to her missing brother, and how a web of aliases hid the truth for years, while honoring the courage of the children and families at the center of this story.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws/98ae2a45af67499d.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">5161cad77bbd4182sg</guid><title>Cheesecake, a Stolen Identity, and a Stranger Who Looked Just Like Her</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lCj7fWF5M2Q</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>I break down the real-life story of a Queens lash artist who accepted a slice of cheesecake from a familiar client and later discovered her passport, cash, and valuables missing. In this deep dive, I explore how investigators tied that dessert to a powerful tranquilizer, uncovered an international warrant, and followed the case all the way to a 2023 jury verdict. Along the way, I focus on how Olga rebuilt her life and what this story says about trust, instinct, and staying aware of the people around us.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws/5161cad77bbd4182.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">ee4a277226b14838sg</guid><title>Did a 15 year old Ended His Mother &amp; Brother?</title><link>https://facebook.com/reel/667040722747578/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>In March 2025, a heartbreaking discovery was made inside a Saratoga Springs home - a mother and young boy found lifeless under mysterious circumstances. As new evidence emerges, attention turns toward the family’s teenage son. Brooke Makenna explores the clues, the unanswered questions, and the deep search for truth in a case that continues to shock an entire community.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws/ee4a277226b14838.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">9818ee248bfc46ecsg</guid><title>She Recognized Herself In A Stranger’s Face</title><link>https://facebook.com/reel/4121314684801296/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>One woman’s journey of discovery begins the moment she sees a reflection of herself in someone she had never met before.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws/9818ee248bfc46ec.jpg" /></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">82a5fdf99cb94878sg</guid><title>A Selfie Solved It - Baby Reunited After 17 Years</title><link>https://facebook.com/reel/777531425177534/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>A single selfie cracked the mystery - leading to an emotional reunion between a mother and her baby, 17 years later.</description><media:thumbnail url="https://storage.googleapis.com/trendly_facebook_videos/sr-vid-ct60ea7upq6m3bppdg2ac9544yqea0yur2v4ihk7fpf68jerb9ws/82a5fdf99cb94878.jpg" /></item></channel></rss>